[{"question": "Every timpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Stella is a numpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Is Stella a vumpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Stella is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jompus, so Stella is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "chorpus", "boompus", "jompus", "timpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 13], [14, 11], [12, 19], [1, 18], [14, 10], [0, 17], [15, 17], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Sam is a gerpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Is Sam a yimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rompus, so Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a timpus, so Sam is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "rompus", "lorpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [4, 9], [10, 9], [4, 14], [11, 15], [0, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Is Wren a sterpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "gwompus", "gorpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "grimpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [9, 11], [12, 14], [11, 9], [15, 11], [8, 13], [11, 15], [13, 12], [9, 15], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Sam is a rompus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Sam is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Is Sam a shumpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "storpus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "rompus", "felpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 15], [0, 11], [14, 15], [12, 13], [2, 9], [0, 14], [17, 14], [4, 15], [16, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Tom is a jompus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Is Tom a dumpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gwompus, so Tom is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a quimpus, so Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus."], "answer": "Tom is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "sterpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "rompus", "jelpus", "storpus", "boompus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [2, 12], [6, 12], [3, 9], [0, 16], [15, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rempus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Is Sally a wumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a numpus, so Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus."], "answer": "Sally is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "grimpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "rempus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [2, 11], [5, 9], [10, 9], [8, 9], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every felpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Is Sam a chorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gerpus, so Sam is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a shumpus, so Sam is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a chorpus, so Sam is a chorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "scrompus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "rompus", "numpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "felpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [18, 13], [18, 11], [12, 16], [5, 15], [18, 15], [16, 11], [13, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Is Rex a numpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a impus, so Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus."], "answer": "Rex is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "quimpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "impus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [7, 10], [8, 12], [12, 11], [4, 12], [9, 11], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a rompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Is Gabriel a grimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "jompus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "fompus", "boompus", "rorpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [6, 10], [5, 13], [14, 12], [13, 11], [8, 10], [15, 13], [3, 14], [7, 14], [7, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Jack is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Is Jack a tumpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a impus.", "Every impus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus."], "answer": "Jack is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "impus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "fompus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [14, 10], [8, 10], [0, 10], [9, 16], [9, 17], [2, 15], [14, 15], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Wren is a rompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Is Wren a tumpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "lempus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "impus", "terpus", "quimpus", "jompus", "rompus", "jelpus", "gorpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 18], [15, 17], [16, 11], [2, 13], [7, 18], [3, 9], [6, 17], [19, 9], [0, 14], [8, 13], [15, 11], [1, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Is Gabriel a jompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "quimpus", "storpus", "terpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "bompus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [11, 12], [7, 14], [6, 10], [1, 14], [3, 10], [7, 11], [14, 13], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Carol is a boompus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Is Carol a worpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zumpus, so Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a zhorpus, so Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus."], "answer": "Carol is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "numpus", "jompus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "boompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [7, 9], [15, 10], [14, 13], [6, 10], [0, 14], [4, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Polly is a worpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Polly is a gerpus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Is Polly a zumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rorpus, so Polly is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a numpus, so Polly is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "grimpus", "rorpus", "numpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "lempus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "impus", "terpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 9], [10, 16], [2, 15], [6, 9], [16, 11], [2, 14], [0, 12], [3, 14], [0, 14], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Is Sam a grimpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Sam is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a shumpus, so Sam is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a grimpus, so Sam is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "tumpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "terpus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "jompus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 15], [2, 10], [7, 19], [13, 19], [9, 11], [2, 11], [2, 18], [1, 18], [3, 14], [18, 14], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every boompus is a impus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Alex is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Alex is a lempus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Is Alex a hilpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Alex is a hilpus."], "answer": "Alex is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "impus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "storpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [13, 12], [7, 10], [0, 9], [0, 11], [6, 9], [1, 12], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Is Fae a vumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "brimpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "felpus", "kerpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 18], [12, 13], [7, 10], [3, 12], [10, 9], [3, 10], [14, 19], [8, 16], [7, 12], [15, 12], [18, 10], [4, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Is Tom a storpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus."], "answer": "Tom is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "zumpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "terpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [2, 12], [4, 12], [7, 9], [13, 11], [10, 9], [12, 13], [11, 10], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every impus is a felpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Is Eva a sterpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a lorpus, so Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus."], "answer": "Eva is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "impus", "lorpus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [8, 12], [8, 10], [10, 12], [4, 11], [3, 13], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Is Eva a gorpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Eva is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a bompus, so Eva is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Eva is a lorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "gwompus", "fompus", "kerpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 18], [12, 14], [3, 14], [7, 11], [10, 13], [15, 9], [1, 10], [11, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Sam is a quimpus. Is Sam a dumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a dumpus, so Sam is a dumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "hilpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "timpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [0, 12], [2, 9], [6, 12], [12, 10], [7, 9], [7, 12], [11, 13], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every bompus is a rompus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Sam is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Is Sam a storpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a shumpus, so Sam is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus."], "answer": "Sam is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "felpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "numpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "storpus", "timpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [12, 14], [10, 15], [0, 12], [1, 12], [11, 16], [12, 18], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every worpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Is Gabriel a numpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "tumpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "brimpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "numpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [17, 18], [5, 14], [12, 19], [18, 15], [7, 11], [10, 18], [16, 11], [14, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Jack is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Is Jack a storpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gerpus, so Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a storpus, so Jack is a storpus."], "answer": "Jack is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jompus", "gerpus", "fompus", "bompus", "storpus", "chorpus", "brimpus", "numpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 17], [15, 16], [14, 11], [9, 12], [11, 15], [8, 11], [11, 9], [15, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Fae is a jelpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Is Fae a fompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a fompus, so Fae is a fompus."], "answer": "Fae is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "vumpus", "storpus", "yumpus", "terpus", "fompus", "bompus", "chorpus", "boompus", "rorpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 13], [18, 16], [2, 10], [17, 15], [6, 10], [8, 11], [0, 13], [5, 14], [16, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Wren is a dumpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Is Wren a zhorpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "shumpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "felpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [9, 14], [3, 14], [13, 10], [5, 14], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Is Oliver a shumpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "zhorpus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 9], [7, 13], [15, 14], [12, 10], [11, 14], [12, 13], [5, 11], [5, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Is Bob a rorpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus."], "answer": "Bob is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "storpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "bompus", "felpus", "worpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [11, 18], [13, 19], [3, 9], [1, 18], [5, 19], [7, 15], [15, 11], [16, 19], [3, 19], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Is Rex a rorpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a gorpus, so Rex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jelpus, so Rex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Rex is a rorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "brimpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "felpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [2, 11], [8, 10], [10, 11], [3, 10], [6, 10], [3, 11], [4, 11], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Polly is a quimpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Is Polly a scrompus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a grimpus, so Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a bompus, so Polly is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "wumpus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [3, 11], [13, 10], [12, 9], [7, 10], [3, 13], [5, 12], [0, 9], [6, 11], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every boompus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Is Max a lorpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jelpus, so Max is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a lorpus, so Max is a lorpus."], "answer": "Max is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "bompus", "impus", "boompus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "fompus", "kerpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "terpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [17, 14], [8, 10], [14, 15], [17, 15], [3, 17], [9, 14], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Bob is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Is Bob a gerpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "jompus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "gerpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 15], [6, 15], [15, 9], [9, 15], [0, 9], [8, 14], [9, 11], [14, 16], [15, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Is Bob a sterpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a boompus, so Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a sterpus, so Bob is a sterpus."], "answer": "Bob is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rempus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [5, 9], [6, 15], [9, 16], [12, 11], [5, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Is Max a terpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus."], "answer": "Max is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "hilpus", "storpus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [9, 11], [4, 12], [1, 12], [2, 14], [11, 12], [2, 10], [14, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rempus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Fae is a terpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Is Fae a bompus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zumpus, so Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus."], "answer": "Fae is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "fompus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "bompus", "dumpus", "timpus", "rempus", "terpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [3, 14], [15, 11], [1, 16], [8, 12], [2, 12], [5, 16], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Is Rex a vumpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a tumpus, so Rex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a vumpus, so Rex is a vumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "quimpus", "worpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "boompus", "impus", "lorpus", "storpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [3, 15], [11, 17], [6, 10], [4, 17], [12, 17], [14, 13], [3, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Is Carol a storpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a fompus, so Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Carol is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus."], "answer": "Carol is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "hilpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "worpus", "storpus", "impus", "felpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "jompus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 10], [11, 16], [2, 15], [5, 10], [6, 16], [14, 9], [16, 14], [4, 15], [12, 13], [11, 17], [6, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Davis is a rempus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Davis is a wumpus. Is Davis a jompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Davis is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus."], "answer": "Davis is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "storpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "boompus", "gorpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [12, 11], [0, 10], [18, 16], [0, 9], [2, 18], [5, 9], [11, 15], [16, 14], [15, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Is Tom a tumpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a scrompus, so Tom is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "storpus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "yumpus", "terpus", "lempus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "timpus", "fompus", "jelpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 18], [8, 17], [10, 18], [10, 9], [12, 15], [5, 9], [17, 9], [1, 9], [1, 12], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every bompus is a rempus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Is Bob a rempus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rompus", "timpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "rempus", "impus", "bompus", "wumpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [5, 10], [12, 11], [8, 13], [11, 9], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every worpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Is Carol a chorpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a wumpus, so Carol is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "fompus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "storpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [15, 10], [10, 9], [16, 14], [15, 14], [1, 14], [15, 13], [4, 15], [16, 13], [5, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Polly is a storpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Is Polly a sterpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Polly is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a wumpus, so Polly is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "fompus", "timpus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "storpus", "sterpus", "quimpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [5, 14], [4, 9], [4, 14], [0, 11], [2, 12], [14, 10], [10, 14], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rompus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Is Gabriel a brimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "storpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "jompus", "grimpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "terpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [9, 18], [11, 14], [19, 9], [14, 9], [4, 15], [16, 13], [19, 11], [10, 14], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lempus is a rempus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a felpus. Stella is a gorpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Is Stella a boompus or a impus?", "steps": ["Stella is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a impus, so Stella is a impus."], "answer": "Stella is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "lempus", "wumpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "impus", "timpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [5, 13], [18, 15], [15, 18], [7, 17], [7, 14], [12, 17], [0, 9], [15, 17], [11, 16], [8, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Is Rex a zhorpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus."], "answer": "Rex is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "dumpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "zhorpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [5, 10], [5, 15], [1, 19], [2, 13], [15, 10], [17, 13], [8, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Tom is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Is Tom a gorpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus."], "answer": "Tom is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "yimpus", "hilpus", "storpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "bompus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "impus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [6, 12], [8, 13], [11, 14], [2, 9], [11, 12], [11, 10], [0, 14], [9, 13], [2, 11], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a zumpus, so Eva is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "kerpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "bompus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "terpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [18, 13], [7, 18], [13, 18], [5, 10], [4, 12], [7, 9], [7, 14], [3, 17], [8, 12], [18, 10], [17, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Is Davis a yerpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rorpus, so Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus."], "answer": "Davis is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "quimpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "bompus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "numpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 15], [4, 17], [13, 19], [2, 10], [4, 11], [19, 11], [3, 18], [5, 15], [18, 19], [8, 14], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every terpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Fae is a fompus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Is Fae a felpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gorpus, so Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus."], "answer": "Fae is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "brimpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "felpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "fompus", "rompus", "lempus", "gwompus", "jelpus", "boompus", "worpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [9, 11], [1, 18], [11, 18], [0, 11], [6, 9], [10, 16], [7, 10], [13, 14], [15, 14], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Fae is a numpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Is Fae a gwompus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a scrompus, so Fae is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus."], "answer": "Fae is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "kerpus", "brimpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "rempus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "numpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [0, 11], [6, 11], [9, 10], [12, 9], [12, 11], [7, 9], [4, 10], [9, 12], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Stella is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Is Stella a scrompus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a lempus, so Stella is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a dumpus, so Stella is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a sterpus, so Stella is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a scrompus, so Stella is a scrompus."], "answer": "Stella is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "quimpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "boompus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "fompus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [8, 16], [14, 11], [15, 10], [0, 14], [10, 11], [4, 9], [13, 9], [6, 16], [8, 11], [4, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every timpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Is Gabriel a zhorpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "numpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "worpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [9, 15], [5, 12], [9, 10], [17, 16], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Alex is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Alex is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Is Alex a timpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Alex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus."], "answer": "Alex is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "quimpus", "fompus", "rompus", "kerpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "impus", "grimpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [7, 11], [2, 12], [9, 14], [3, 12], [2, 13], [0, 11], [1, 12], [8, 10], [0, 13], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every bompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Is Alex a terpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a tumpus, so Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus."], "answer": "Alex is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "worpus", "scrompus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "felpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "terpus", "fompus", "bompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [4, 12], [9, 14], [19, 10], [7, 9], [12, 11], [19, 9], [18, 12], [13, 18], [3, 17], [5, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Is Sam a storpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus."], "answer": "Sam is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "rorpus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "boompus", "numpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "storpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [13, 10], [9, 12], [9, 13], [4, 11], [3, 10], [1, 13], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a grimpus. Wren is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Is Wren a jompus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yumpus, so Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a chorpus, so Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus."], "answer": "Wren is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yimpus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "jompus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "brimpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 12], [13, 15], [12, 15], [6, 9], [12, 13], [5, 11], [12, 9], [2, 15], [1, 14], [0, 14], [9, 10], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Jack is a worpus. Is Jack a wumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rompus, so Jack is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jelpus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "fompus", "felpus", "wumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 13], [13, 15], [3, 13], [8, 16], [1, 16], [0, 14], [6, 9], [9, 17], [13, 14], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a impus. Fae is a fompus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a chorpus. Is Fae a impus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a chorpus, so Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus."], "answer": "Fae is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "sterpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "jompus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "fompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 16], [6, 9], [11, 10], [13, 11], [14, 16], [6, 13], [0, 15], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Is Alex a chorpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a worpus, so Alex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gwompus, so Alex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Alex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "vumpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "timpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [8, 9], [14, 10], [5, 13], [13, 10], [3, 11], [9, 13], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every fompus is a numpus. Max is a jompus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Is Max a jelpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Max is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a numpus, so Max is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jelpus, so Max is a jelpus."], "answer": "Max is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "felpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "numpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "jompus", "impus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [2, 11], [11, 10], [0, 12], [14, 16], [4, 16], [13, 12], [5, 13], [16, 14], [14, 17], [9, 13], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Is Davis a impus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a fompus, so Davis is a fompus."], "answer": "Davis is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "grimpus", "felpus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [1, 11], [9, 10], [14, 13], [13, 11], [3, 14], [10, 9], [8, 13], [6, 14], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every bompus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "grimpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "rompus", "gorpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [3, 10], [12, 13], [1, 12], [9, 14], [14, 13], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a lorpus. Sally is a gerpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Sally is a fompus. Is Sally a rorpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Sally is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a rorpus, so Sally is a rorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "quimpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "brimpus", "fompus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [2, 10], [0, 10], [0, 11], [9, 11], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Jack is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every boompus is a felpus. Jack is a numpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Is Jack a impus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gerpus, so Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a impus, so Jack is a impus."], "answer": "Jack is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "boompus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "impus", "grimpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [3, 9], [11, 18], [18, 14], [0, 13], [7, 14], [6, 11], [0, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Is Tom a boompus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a scrompus, so Tom is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus."], "answer": "Tom is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "gwompus", "jompus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "boompus", "yumpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "worpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [5, 13], [8, 16], [1, 16], [8, 17], [12, 9], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Bob is a felpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a impus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Is Bob a tumpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a lempus, so Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "numpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "impus", "felpus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [5, 11], [16, 12], [12, 13], [10, 11], [0, 12], [5, 12], [3, 17], [7, 11], [5, 15], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Is Jack a storpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a tumpus, so Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gwompus, so Jack is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a storpus, so Jack is a storpus."], "answer": "Jack is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "kerpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "numpus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [9, 11], [3, 16], [4, 12], [7, 16], [6, 13], [8, 14], [11, 12], [17, 16], [1, 16], [16, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a numpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Is Fae a yumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "vumpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "fompus", "terpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "jompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [7, 15], [7, 13], [10, 11], [15, 14], [5, 9], [6, 13], [15, 10], [11, 13], [4, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Davis is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Is Davis a vumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a impus, so Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus."], "answer": "Davis is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "storpus", "numpus", "impus", "rompus", "worpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [9, 13], [5, 12], [7, 12], [11, 10], [10, 11], [1, 13], [0, 13], [6, 11], [5, 10], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a rompus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every timpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Is Fae a yimpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a timpus, so Fae is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rompus, so Fae is a rompus."], "answer": "Fae is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "quimpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "felpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "shumpus", "terpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [13, 15], [2, 10], [7, 12], [2, 16], [1, 11], [12, 9], [11, 17], [15, 13], [14, 17], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Tom is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every impus is a jompus. Is Tom a sterpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus."], "answer": "Tom is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "yumpus", "vumpus", "impus", "jompus", "storpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [8, 12], [1, 10], [10, 14], [6, 12], [4, 12], [12, 9], [12, 10], [9, 12], [6, 9], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Polly is a impus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Polly is a brimpus. Is Polly a rorpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a numpus, so Polly is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus."], "answer": "Polly is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "zhorpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "impus", "felpus", "rorpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [6, 12], [2, 12], [12, 10], [8, 11], [0, 9], [0, 12], [2, 11], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Is Sally a vumpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus."], "answer": "Sally is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jelpus", "lempus", "rempus", "hilpus", "bompus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "rompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [15, 12], [2, 14], [10, 13], [12, 15], [1, 13], [8, 12], [7, 14], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Is Gabriel a brimpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gwompus, so Gabriel is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "shumpus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "impus", "brimpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "numpus", "wumpus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 19], [14, 9], [7, 11], [13, 16], [7, 16], [10, 14], [18, 19], [17, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Polly is a yumpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Is Polly a rempus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a chorpus, so Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a worpus, so Polly is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rempus, so Polly is a rempus."], "answer": "Polly is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "jompus", "boompus", "chorpus", "worpus", "rempus", "timpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "impus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [5, 11], [4, 15], [0, 9], [8, 14], [7, 14], [10, 12], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Oliver is a lorpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Is Oliver a timpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a kerpus, so Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "rorpus", "kerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "chorpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "hilpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 12], [3, 11], [0, 13], [13, 11], [2, 12], [5, 11], [1, 9], [3, 13], [8, 9], [12, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Is Jack a grimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a kerpus, so Jack is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a storpus, so Jack is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "numpus", "kerpus", "storpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "bompus", "yerpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "rempus", "impus", "felpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "jompus", "sterpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [9, 10], [9, 11], [5, 11], [15, 16], [3, 10], [6, 18], [5, 17], [9, 18], [15, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every impus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every impus is a lempus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Bob is a boompus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Is Bob a rorpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a brimpus, so Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "storpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "impus", "rempus", "worpus", "vumpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "lempus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [13, 12], [7, 13], [4, 10], [12, 10], [14, 9], [0, 11], [14, 11], [7, 11], [12, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every numpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Fae is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Fae is a brimpus. Is Fae a jelpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a chorpus, so Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus."], "answer": "Fae is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "lempus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [3, 11], [12, 10], [0, 9], [9, 11], [4, 9], [8, 10], [0, 11], [9, 10], [11, 12], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Is Sam a timpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a shumpus, so Sam is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "yumpus", "shumpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "timpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [14, 17], [10, 18], [18, 16], [13, 11], [16, 18], [8, 13], [3, 11], [7, 14], [18, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Fae is a worpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Is Fae a worpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a chorpus, so Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rempus, so Fae is a rempus."], "answer": "Fae is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "sterpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "storpus", "rempus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "timpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [18, 10], [7, 11], [15, 10], [15, 12], [3, 15], [10, 13], [0, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a impus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Is Stella a gwompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Stella is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a lempus, so Stella is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Stella is a gwompus."], "answer": "Stella is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "hilpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "jompus", "rempus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "tumpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [15, 10], [12, 9], [8, 11], [14, 11], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Wren is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Is Wren a chorpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus."], "answer": "Wren is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "tumpus", "felpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [7, 11], [7, 12], [12, 10], [9, 10], [4, 9], [9, 11], [10, 11], [1, 13], [12, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Eva is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Is Eva a boompus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Eva is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "zhorpus", "impus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "boompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [0, 10], [3, 11], [4, 15], [14, 15], [14, 13], [15, 11], [7, 13], [12, 14], [6, 14], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Eva is a bompus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Is Eva a vumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Eva is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a sterpus, so Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "scrompus", "boompus", "fompus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "timpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "bompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [9, 10], [12, 10], [6, 12], [4, 12], [3, 9], [3, 12], [6, 11], [4, 9], [0, 11], [8, 12], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Tom is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Is Tom a gerpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gerpus, so Tom is a gerpus."], "answer": "Tom is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "zumpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "bompus", "jompus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [3, 19], [2, 17], [18, 17], [2, 15], [3, 12], [7, 18], [0, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every bompus is a boompus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Is Tom a boompus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus."], "answer": "Tom is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "chorpus", "storpus", "impus", "vumpus", "boompus", "fompus", "quimpus", "bompus", "lempus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [10, 13], [2, 9], [11, 15], [9, 12], [11, 14], [14, 13], [3, 11], [5, 10], [12, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Is Fae a yerpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus."], "answer": "Fae is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "sterpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "yimpus", "worpus", "storpus", "numpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "boompus", "lempus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 17], [11, 16], [6, 9], [3, 12], [19, 11], [13, 10], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a worpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Is Wren a gwompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus."], "answer": "Wren is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "zumpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "rempus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "impus", "timpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "jompus", "brimpus", "terpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [4, 11], [19, 12], [5, 11], [11, 9], [2, 18], [2, 16], [15, 19], [1, 14], [10, 15], [3, 11], [19, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every numpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Jack is a jompus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Is Jack a worpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a vumpus, so Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus."], "answer": "Jack is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "numpus", "worpus", "grimpus", "impus", "gerpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 15], [9, 16], [15, 10], [17, 14], [17, 11], [7, 16], [12, 11], [12, 13], [9, 14], [10, 15], [0, 13], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Is Wren a kerpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jompus, so Wren is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus."], "answer": "Wren is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "brimpus", "lempus", "jompus", "timpus", "gwompus", "numpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [7, 10], [4, 12], [6, 10], [6, 13], [10, 9], [6, 12], [9, 13], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Is Stella a jompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a jelpus, so Stella is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a gerpus, so Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "sterpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "lempus", "jompus", "vumpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [2, 13], [1, 9], [13, 12], [14, 9], [11, 13], [11, 12], [8, 15], [6, 14], [1, 13], [9, 10], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Is Bob a worpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus."], "answer": "Bob is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "vumpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "rompus", "numpus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "worpus", "zumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 15], [8, 14], [2, 14], [15, 9], [11, 9], [4, 15], [10, 13], [8, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Jack is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Jack is a impus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Is Jack a terpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "rempus", "boompus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "terpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [8, 11], [11, 10], [6, 14], [7, 9], [10, 12], [0, 14], [10, 14], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Polly is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a impus. Is Polly a kerpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a impus, so Polly is a impus.", "Every impus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a wumpus, so Polly is a wumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yimpus", "impus", "zumpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "timpus", "scrompus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [8, 9], [8, 10], [5, 11], [2, 11], [12, 9], [0, 11], [5, 12], [12, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every boompus is a bompus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every impus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Alex is a gwompus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Is Alex a zhorpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus."], "answer": "Alex is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "boompus", "jelpus", "impus", "timpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [0, 10], [3, 14], [5, 9], [13, 11], [3, 11], [3, 10], [10, 9], [6, 14], [10, 11], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every storpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Is Fae a jompus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus."], "answer": "Fae is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "quimpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "numpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "storpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "impus", "wumpus", "worpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 11], [12, 16], [17, 14], [14, 12], [11, 9], [5, 18], [18, 9], [9, 14], [10, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Is Davis a worpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rorpus, so Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a brimpus, so Davis is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus."], "answer": "Davis is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "grimpus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "brimpus", "worpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [5, 11], [8, 9], [7, 10], [1, 10], [1, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Is Rex a yerpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Rex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lorpus, so Rex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "grimpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "timpus", "jompus", "fompus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "lempus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "rempus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [17, 14], [2, 12], [2, 16], [4, 12], [2, 14], [16, 11], [13, 16], [9, 15], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every jompus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every impus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Is Gabriel a hilpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a sterpus, so Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "bompus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "terpus", "rempus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "impus", "jompus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [1, 14], [3, 12], [3, 9], [6, 10], [9, 12], [11, 15], [12, 13], [8, 15], [10, 13], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every felpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Tom is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Is Tom a boompus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rompus, so Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus."], "answer": "Tom is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "yumpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "felpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [1, 9], [0, 10], [6, 10], [9, 10], [8, 9], [7, 9], [11, 10], [1, 10], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Eva is a brimpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Is Eva a brimpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Eva is a lorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "vumpus", "rorpus", "fompus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [4, 13], [12, 10], [6, 13], [9, 11], [0, 11], [8, 12], [8, 9], [7, 12], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Wren is a lempus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Is Wren a lempus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a fompus, so Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus."], "answer": "Wren is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "quimpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "yumpus", "felpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [11, 10], [6, 10], [7, 11], [3, 9], [4, 11], [8, 11], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every felpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Max is a rompus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Is Max a grimpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a tumpus, so Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus."], "answer": "Max is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "numpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "bompus", "worpus", "wumpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "timpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 17], [9, 15], [14, 13], [4, 9], [10, 14], [1, 18], [4, 11], [1, 10], [17, 15], [0, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Is Bob a rorpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "fompus", "timpus", "storpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "numpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [3, 9], [1, 12], [12, 9], [2, 11], [11, 10], [12, 10], [11, 9], [7, 10], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Jack is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Is Jack a quimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "terpus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "impus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [4, 11], [1, 9], [2, 9], [7, 11], [6, 10], [1, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a yerpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Alex is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Is Alex a timpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a tumpus, so Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a numpus, so Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Alex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "lorpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "jompus", "impus", "timpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "bompus", "hilpus", "fompus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [14, 13], [6, 11], [14, 12], [9, 13], [5, 13], [6, 10], [7, 16], [2, 15], [0, 16], [9, 10], [12, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Wren is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Is Wren a vumpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "lorpus", "terpus", "numpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "fompus", "quimpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [15, 10], [14, 12], [9, 12], [10, 11], [0, 10], [9, 14], [16, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Fae is a lempus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Is Fae a fompus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a fompus, so Fae is a fompus."], "answer": "Fae is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "rompus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "felpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 14], [12, 9], [4, 14], [5, 14], [0, 10], [1, 9], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every storpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Rex is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Is Rex a timpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a quimpus, so Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus."], "answer": "Rex is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "terpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "shumpus", "impus", "lempus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [5, 12], [0, 14], [5, 14], [5, 13], [4, 12], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every terpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Is Polly a gorpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a storpus, so Polly is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a lorpus, so Polly is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "terpus", "storpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "lempus", "impus", "boompus", "gerpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 17], [13, 16], [7, 9], [14, 11], [11, 17], [14, 15], [6, 19], [1, 18], [14, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every jompus is a impus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every jompus is a terpus. Eva is a yumpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Is Eva a grimpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "bompus", "brimpus", "jompus", "impus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [8, 10], [3, 10], [3, 11], [2, 11], [6, 11], [8, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Is Tom a worpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus."], "answer": "Tom is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "felpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "worpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "numpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [3, 9], [3, 17], [16, 14], [9, 11], [15, 16], [13, 16], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Jack is a jompus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Is Jack a gorpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "quimpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "jompus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "storpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [13, 9], [5, 14], [6, 14], [8, 13], [4, 12], [2, 9], [3, 10], [3, 11], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Alex is a impus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every impus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Is Alex a kerpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a vumpus, so Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a hilpus, so Alex is a hilpus."], "answer": "Alex is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "fompus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "impus", "boompus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [9, 12], [7, 11], [3, 13], [5, 13], [2, 13], [5, 11], [9, 10], [8, 12], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Is Polly a yerpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a hilpus, so Polly is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "jelpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [2, 11], [10, 18], [8, 12], [15, 9], [7, 15], [3, 14], [5, 13], [15, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Is Rex a chorpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus."], "answer": "Rex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rorpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "worpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [11, 12], [6, 13], [17, 9], [15, 17], [3, 14], [9, 14], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every felpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Is Bob a shumpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus."], "answer": "Bob is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "yerpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "timpus", "impus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [8, 10], [1, 9], [5, 9], [3, 11], [2, 10], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Stella is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Is Stella a quimpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a worpus, so Stella is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus."], "answer": "Stella is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "brimpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "numpus", "sterpus", "boompus", "timpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 14], [7, 9], [5, 12], [11, 12], [9, 18], [4, 12], [4, 9], [19, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every rompus is a impus. Every lempus is a impus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Gabriel is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Is Gabriel a lorpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "sterpus", "lempus", "impus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "bompus", "jelpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [5, 10], [1, 10], [10, 9], [3, 11], [1, 9], [8, 10], [0, 10], [11, 10], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Bob is a yerpus. Is Bob a grimpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rempus", "jompus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "boompus", "yerpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "rompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [13, 14], [3, 9], [3, 13], [2, 13], [9, 11], [0, 9], [14, 10], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rompus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Is Alex a rempus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Alex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus."], "answer": "Alex is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "wumpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "timpus", "storpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [6, 9], [10, 9], [4, 9], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a yerpus. Tom is a felpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Is Tom a hilpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a zhorpus, so Tom is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus."], "answer": "Tom is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "sterpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "storpus", "lempus", "terpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [7, 12], [2, 10], [3, 10], [0, 13], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a rempus. Jack is a felpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Is Jack a jompus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a tumpus, so Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "chorpus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "worpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [1, 11], [4, 9], [2, 9], [0, 12], [9, 11], [12, 10], [8, 12], [12, 9], [5, 10], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Is Bob a rorpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a quimpus, so Bob is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Bob is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "scrompus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "kerpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [4, 10], [5, 9], [4, 13], [1, 10], [3, 13], [4, 12], [3, 11], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Fae is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Is Fae a brimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rempus, so Fae is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "rorpus", "rempus", "fompus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [3, 14], [11, 16], [4, 9], [14, 16], [10, 13], [2, 16], [0, 9], [2, 9], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Tom is a lempus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Is Tom a worpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus."], "answer": "Tom is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "gwompus", "rempus", "vumpus", "felpus", "worpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [0, 12], [13, 14], [9, 10], [6, 15], [3, 10], [2, 11], [5, 10], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a impus. Jack is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Is Jack a yimpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a tumpus, so Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a sterpus, so Jack is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "kerpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "felpus", "boompus", "lempus", "lorpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 14], [17, 9], [11, 18], [5, 15], [10, 12], [0, 14], [7, 15], [4, 12], [4, 10], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Sally is a hilpus. Sally is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Is Sally a scrompus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a scrompus, so Sally is a scrompus."], "answer": "Sally is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "bompus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "storpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "brimpus", "terpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 16], [0, 15], [2, 13], [3, 17], [3, 10], [5, 10], [0, 17], [2, 11], [10, 12], [9, 15], [9, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Carol is a felpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Is Carol a chorpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a impus, so Carol is a impus.", "Every impus is a rempus, so Carol is a rempus."], "answer": "Carol is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "scrompus", "terpus", "worpus", "impus", "rempus", "timpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "felpus", "dumpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [5, 11], [6, 11], [12, 10], [4, 9], [10, 11], [1, 12], [2, 10], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Carol is a impus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Is Carol a boompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a kerpus, so Carol is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus."], "answer": "Carol is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "zumpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "chorpus", "boompus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "impus", "fompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [7, 15], [1, 13], [14, 10], [6, 12], [7, 10], [10, 15], [0, 13], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Is Gabriel a shumpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "zumpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "tumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [6, 12], [1, 9], [7, 9], [1, 10], [9, 10], [4, 11], [12, 9], [10, 12], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Gabriel is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Is Gabriel a lorpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lorpus, so Gabriel is a lorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "kerpus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [8, 11], [17, 14], [0, 15], [16, 15], [12, 10], [16, 13], [7, 13], [6, 17], [10, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every rempus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Tom is a brimpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Is Tom a terpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Tom is a terpus."], "answer": "Tom is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "shumpus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "terpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "storpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [2, 14], [3, 12], [12, 10], [1, 11], [8, 15], [9, 11], [0, 12], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Is Tom a yerpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a quimpus, so Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "sterpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "worpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [2, 11], [7, 13], [7, 9], [5, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every bompus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Eva is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Is Eva a rompus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yumpus, so Eva is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a scrompus, so Eva is a scrompus."], "answer": "Eva is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "grimpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "bompus", "timpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "jelpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [19, 12], [16, 19], [2, 18], [19, 11], [8, 11], [17, 9], [0, 12], [6, 14], [11, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every lempus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Is Davis a zumpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "impus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [4, 9], [9, 13], [2, 12], [10, 13], [4, 11], [3, 9], [14, 13], [13, 12], [13, 10], [2, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every bompus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every lempus is a impus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Is Fae a yimpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "lempus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "impus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "terpus", "numpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "fompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 16], [8, 13], [13, 9], [14, 15], [16, 10], [13, 10], [16, 13], [13, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Is Stella a lorpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a impus, so Stella is a impus.", "Every impus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Stella is a kerpus."], "answer": "Stella is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "storpus", "impus", "chorpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [9, 15], [8, 13], [6, 10], [11, 9], [9, 11], [6, 13], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Is Rex a shumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a impus, so Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus."], "answer": "Rex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "boompus", "bompus", "impus", "gwompus", "rompus", "jompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "felpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [12, 9], [11, 13], [8, 12], [4, 13], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a worpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Is Rex a yimpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "impus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [8, 11], [9, 10], [8, 12], [7, 9], [1, 9], [9, 11], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Is Gabriel a jompus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rorpus, so Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "gorpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 12], [2, 9], [13, 12], [13, 15], [9, 14], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a gerpus, so Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Eva is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "yerpus", "gerpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [9, 11], [7, 12], [4, 9], [5, 11], [2, 9], [3, 11], [1, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a impus. Bob is a rompus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Is Bob a grimpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Bob is a impus."], "answer": "Bob is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "sterpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "fompus", "impus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [7, 12], [2, 10], [5, 13], [12, 10], [3, 13], [8, 13], [2, 9], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rompus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a impus. Is Alex a yerpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a numpus, so Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jelpus", "timpus", "rompus", "numpus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "impus", "fompus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [1, 10], [2, 11], [5, 12], [5, 10], [6, 12], [9, 12], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Bob is a jompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Is Bob a vumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "felpus", "fompus", "numpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "impus", "lempus", "vumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 18], [14, 12], [17, 13], [2, 13], [19, 9], [0, 14], [11, 15], [2, 18], [13, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every rempus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Is Max a wumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Max is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus."], "answer": "Max is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "zhorpus", "terpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "rempus", "storpus", "bompus", "fompus", "gorpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [6, 11], [1, 10], [7, 11], [4, 9], [11, 9], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Sally is a bompus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Is Sally a zumpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "chorpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "felpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [8, 13], [11, 12], [1, 12], [0, 10], [5, 12], [6, 11], [7, 9], [2, 9], [8, 12], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Gabriel is a yumpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Is Gabriel a chorpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "vumpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "impus", "rompus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [17, 16], [12, 18], [9, 17], [3, 9], [0, 17], [2, 9], [7, 14], [3, 16], [14, 12], [6, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a boompus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Is Wren a boompus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a boompus, so Wren is a boompus."], "answer": "Wren is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "fompus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "boompus", "lorpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "numpus", "felpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [14, 13], [14, 11], [8, 14], [12, 13], [6, 9], [7, 13], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a timpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Is Oliver a brimpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "impus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "bompus", "timpus", "kerpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 13], [13, 11], [9, 12], [10, 9], [2, 11], [4, 13], [1, 11], [7, 12], [2, 10], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Is Oliver a dumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "brimpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "impus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "jompus", "sterpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [6, 13], [3, 11], [7, 9], [9, 11], [3, 9], [4, 10], [4, 11], [10, 11], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Is Davis a gerpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rorpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "impus", "sterpus", "rompus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 14], [11, 10], [8, 19], [4, 17], [8, 10], [10, 16], [15, 19], [4, 12], [4, 19], [7, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Max is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Is Max a impus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a bompus, so Max is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Max is a impus."], "answer": "Max is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "bompus", "fompus", "impus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "boompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [0, 10], [12, 9], [8, 10], [7, 14], [1, 11], [5, 12], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Is Wren a wumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a jompus, so Wren is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a chorpus, so Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a worpus, so Wren is a worpus."], "answer": "Wren is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "kerpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "chorpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [10, 9], [4, 9], [1, 9], [11, 10], [3, 12], [3, 9], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Is Oliver a kerpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a scrompus, so Oliver is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rorpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "worpus", "lempus", "wumpus", "storpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "impus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 16], [10, 11], [3, 12], [3, 11], [13, 11], [16, 10], [16, 12], [7, 14], [13, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Is Bob a brimpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a boompus, so Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a brimpus, so Bob is a brimpus."], "answer": "Bob is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gorpus", "timpus", "boompus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "jompus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [11, 14], [3, 11], [5, 14], [5, 15], [9, 12], [10, 13], [4, 16], [6, 14], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Is Max a hilpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a hilpus, so Max is a hilpus."], "answer": "Max is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "yimpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "worpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [10, 9], [9, 12], [7, 12], [1, 10], [3, 10], [5, 11], [3, 11], [4, 10], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every impus is a rorpus. Gabriel is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Is Gabriel a rorpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "boompus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "impus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "fompus", "quimpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [5, 13], [10, 12], [15, 13], [1, 12], [15, 9], [5, 11], [3, 9], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Is Jack a yerpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "terpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "bompus", "rompus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 15], [6, 16], [10, 12], [7, 12], [11, 17], [11, 9], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every impus is a worpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a impus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a impus. Is Alex a lorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a lempus, so Alex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Alex is a lorpus."], "answer": "Alex is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "terpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "lorpus", "storpus", "jelpus", "gwompus", "impus", "worpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [6, 14], [5, 10], [11, 12], [9, 10], [11, 10], [14, 9], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every storpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Stella is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Is Stella a storpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a storpus, so Stella is a storpus."], "answer": "Stella is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "rorpus", "bompus", "timpus", "wumpus", "storpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [0, 13], [7, 12], [15, 13], [4, 14], [12, 15], [5, 14], [6, 10], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Is Sally a shumpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus."], "answer": "Sally is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yumpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "lempus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "felpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 13], [14, 16], [9, 18], [1, 15], [2, 15], [10, 12], [8, 15], [4, 13], [18, 16], [2, 9], [12, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every rompus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Jack is a boompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Is Jack a worpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus."], "answer": "Jack is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "rompus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "fompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [3, 13], [5, 12], [1, 9], [0, 11], [12, 11], [13, 10], [12, 9], [2, 11], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jompus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Is Gabriel a quimpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "hilpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "impus", "bompus", "wumpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "fompus", "rempus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [8, 16], [11, 13], [1, 17], [17, 18], [14, 11], [3, 13], [15, 13], [15, 19], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Oliver is a rompus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a rompus. Oliver is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Is Oliver a brimpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "tumpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "boompus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "rompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 15], [8, 10], [5, 12], [2, 15], [10, 11], [8, 12], [14, 13], [13, 10], [0, 9], [8, 13], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every impus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Is Rex a brimpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gorpus, so Rex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a kerpus, so Rex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "storpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "impus", "jompus", "felpus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [4, 12], [8, 15], [6, 13], [3, 14], [8, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Rex is a storpus. Is Rex a zumpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a quimpus, so Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "gerpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "bompus", "zumpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [11, 10], [8, 10], [1, 9], [10, 9], [2, 10], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a terpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "fompus", "tumpus", "terpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "lempus", "felpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [5, 11], [3, 9], [9, 10], [8, 10], [2, 11], [9, 11], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Fae is a storpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Is Fae a timpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "hilpus", "numpus", "felpus", "bompus", "dumpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "storpus", "yerpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [8, 9], [7, 10], [1, 12], [1, 9], [2, 12], [0, 10], [11, 12], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a impus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Rex is a chorpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Rex is a gwompus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Is Rex a scrompus or a impus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a impus, so Rex is a impus."], "answer": "Rex is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rompus", "boompus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "sterpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "lempus", "felpus", "terpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [1, 9], [8, 9], [0, 12], [4, 11], [0, 15], [4, 12], [15, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Eva is a wumpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Is Eva a timpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rompus, so Eva is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yimpus, so Eva is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus."], "answer": "Eva is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lorpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "yimpus", "jompus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "timpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [7, 9], [11, 13], [13, 11], [6, 9], [12, 9], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Is Fae a yumpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a timpus, so Fae is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "zhorpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [2, 10], [9, 12], [8, 9], [5, 9], [6, 9], [8, 11], [8, 12], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Is Oliver a zumpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "brimpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "bompus", "terpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 15], [9, 15], [14, 13], [10, 13], [2, 14], [8, 9], [9, 14], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Is Oliver a zumpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "impus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [6, 11], [14, 10], [2, 10], [12, 16], [11, 12], [1, 13], [7, 9], [16, 14], [15, 11], [2, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Is Oliver a bompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Oliver is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rorpus", "rompus", "numpus", "jompus", "bompus", "storpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [3, 11], [1, 11], [3, 9], [6, 10], [4, 9], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Is Wren a dumpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "hilpus", "lempus", "gwompus", "storpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "rompus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 17], [1, 16], [16, 17], [14, 18], [6, 17], [1, 17], [5, 13], [12, 13], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Davis is a felpus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Is Davis a lorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a impus, so Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus."], "answer": "Davis is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gwompus", "tumpus", "impus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [2, 9], [7, 13], [0, 11], [2, 13], [12, 13], [10, 13], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Alex is a scrompus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Is Alex a bompus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a vumpus, so Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a boompus, so Alex is a boompus."], "answer": "Alex is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "impus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "boompus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "bompus", "felpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [5, 13], [13, 11], [4, 11], [2, 13], [12, 11], [2, 11], [0, 10], [3, 12], [6, 11], [9, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Jack is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Is Jack a lorpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gwompus, so Jack is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a terpus, so Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "vumpus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "terpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [9, 12], [5, 10], [1, 9], [0, 9], [3, 12], [1, 10], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Is Alex a gwompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a chorpus, so Alex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a tumpus, so Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus."], "answer": "Alex is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "gorpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "timpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 14], [2, 12], [3, 9], [10, 12], [5, 9], [6, 9], [7, 14], [6, 12], [10, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Sally is a rempus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Is Sally a rempus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus."], "answer": "Sally is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jelpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "impus", "rempus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "sterpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [15, 13], [7, 13], [2, 12], [13, 9], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Is Fae a boompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a gorpus, so Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yerpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "numpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [7, 13], [14, 15], [7, 9], [8, 10], [4, 12], [7, 14], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Is Rex a grimpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus."], "answer": "Rex is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "impus", "chorpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 15], [2, 10], [1, 17], [11, 14], [7, 9], [13, 12], [14, 9], [7, 11], [11, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Davis is a yimpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Is Davis a zumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gwompus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "worpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [6, 10], [16, 15], [11, 13], [10, 15], [2, 13], [1, 12], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Wren is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Is Wren a terpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus."], "answer": "Wren is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "jompus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [4, 12], [9, 15], [3, 10], [13, 11], [0, 10], [14, 9], [11, 10], [9, 10], [5, 9], [8, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every numpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Is Stella a chorpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a tumpus, so Stella is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gorpus, so Stella is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus."], "answer": "Stella is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "numpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [10, 9], [11, 10], [10, 11], [1, 10], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rempus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Is Wren a zhorpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a chorpus, so Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "terpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [8, 14], [2, 13], [5, 12], [12, 10], [3, 15], [13, 15], [8, 11], [2, 9], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every felpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Carol is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Carol is a impus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Is Carol a vumpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gwompus, so Carol is a gwompus."], "answer": "Carol is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "gerpus", "storpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "timpus", "numpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "impus", "tumpus", "rempus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [0, 11], [4, 9], [7, 12], [12, 13], [13, 9], [4, 10], [0, 10], [2, 11], [11, 10], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Is Gabriel a rempus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rempus, so Gabriel is a rempus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "yerpus", "boompus", "worpus", "rompus", "rempus", "shumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [13, 10], [1, 9], [14, 9], [13, 9], [7, 9], [5, 12], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every impus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Is Sally a gorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "quimpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "worpus", "impus", "hilpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [2, 12], [3, 9], [4, 9], [4, 13], [3, 13], [9, 12], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Eva is a worpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Is Eva a hilpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yimpus, so Eva is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gerpus, so Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus."], "answer": "Eva is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lorpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 15], [3, 12], [14, 10], [4, 10], [5, 10], [0, 9], [13, 10], [15, 13], [10, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a jompus. Max is a rompus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Is Max a quimpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus."], "answer": "Max is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rorpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "felpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [9, 11], [4, 15], [1, 13], [10, 9], [0, 16], [2, 14], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a bompus. Every impus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every impus is a numpus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Is Polly a zhorpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a impus.", "Every impus is a fompus, so Polly is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zhorpus, so Polly is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "impus", "fompus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "numpus", "felpus", "bompus", "timpus", "storpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 18], [5, 12], [14, 18], [18, 13], [16, 9], [3, 10], [5, 13], [2, 14], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Oliver is a storpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Is Oliver a storpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus."], "answer": "Oliver is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gwompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "impus", "shumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [0, 12], [2, 11], [7, 9], [6, 10], [4, 11], [3, 12], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every impus is a bompus. Gabriel is a impus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a impus. Is Gabriel a bompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "rompus", "gerpus", "terpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "impus", "shumpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [9, 11], [0, 9], [11, 13], [3, 9], [7, 12], [8, 11], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Is Polly a boompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Polly is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rompus, so Polly is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "brimpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "rompus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "terpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "fompus", "timpus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 18], [1, 15], [18, 11], [12, 19], [11, 13], [19, 16], [17, 16], [18, 19], [3, 11], [5, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Is Oliver a rorpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "yerpus", "timpus", "felpus", "worpus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "terpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [13, 15], [8, 11], [2, 11], [11, 12], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a shumpus. Eva is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Is Eva a vumpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a wumpus, so Eva is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a shumpus, so Eva is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "lempus", "lorpus", "felpus", "boompus", "worpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 16], [9, 15], [7, 10], [0, 12], [14, 13], [16, 15], [5, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Fae is a zumpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Is Fae a yumpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a chorpus, so Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "fompus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "terpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [5, 9], [4, 10], [3, 10], [6, 12], [10, 11], [11, 12], [8, 9], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Tom is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Is Tom a worpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a scrompus, so Tom is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a wumpus, so Tom is a wumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "quimpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [11, 13], [1, 12], [2, 13], [7, 11], [0, 12], [8, 12], [5, 9], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every numpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Is Fae a numpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus."], "answer": "Fae is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "chorpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "storpus", "lempus", "scrompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 15], [1, 10], [15, 12], [2, 11], [17, 12], [8, 9], [13, 11], [3, 12], [4, 10], [1, 13], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Is Wren a terpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus."], "answer": "Wren is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "numpus", "jelpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "rorpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "impus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [8, 14], [4, 12], [16, 14], [15, 18], [2, 17], [12, 17], [6, 15], [5, 17], [4, 9], [13, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Is Oliver a rempus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus."], "answer": "Oliver is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "jelpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "lempus", "rempus", "shumpus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "numpus", "wumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [3, 9], [5, 12], [1, 9], [2, 10], [3, 11], [2, 9], [11, 9], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a timpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Tom is a kerpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Is Tom a jompus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus."], "answer": "Tom is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "impus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "rempus", "grimpus", "worpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [8, 15], [11, 15], [15, 10], [14, 12], [3, 9], [0, 9], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rempus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every impus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Is Polly a gorpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a impus.", "Every impus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "impus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [10, 12], [3, 10], [5, 12], [10, 9], [12, 9], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Is Wren a zumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a boompus, so Wren is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "storpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "rompus", "felpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [5, 11], [2, 10], [9, 12], [3, 11], [11, 12], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Bob is a impus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Is Bob a worpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus."], "answer": "Bob is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "boompus", "storpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "impus", "jompus", "zumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "worpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [12, 10], [12, 13], [2, 16], [5, 16], [4, 9], [6, 9], [15, 18], [8, 12], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Polly is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Is Polly a scrompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a chorpus, so Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lorpus, so Polly is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a fompus, so Polly is a fompus."], "answer": "Polly is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "vumpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "storpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "terpus", "impus", "gerpus", "felpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 16], [12, 17], [4, 17], [0, 11], [17, 15], [18, 14], [4, 12], [11, 12], [17, 11], [17, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a impus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Is Bob a yimpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus."], "answer": "Bob is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gorpus", "fompus", "rompus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [8, 10], [5, 12], [1, 10], [3, 9], [4, 9], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every bompus is a impus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Is Alex a impus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a tumpus, so Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yimpus, so Alex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a numpus, so Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus."], "answer": "Alex is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "sterpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "numpus", "impus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "terpus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [16, 14], [1, 10], [14, 13], [14, 9], [3, 15], [6, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Is Max a lempus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rompus, so Max is a rompus."], "answer": "Max is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "sterpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "rompus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "lempus", "bompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [8, 11], [2, 10], [3, 12], [6, 12], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Sam is a terpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Is Sam a terpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a impus, so Sam is a impus.", "Every impus is a dumpus, so Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus."], "answer": "Sam is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "gorpus", "impus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "felpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 13], [2, 16], [5, 17], [19, 13], [4, 11], [11, 13], [9, 11], [5, 14], [0, 9], [17, 15], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Fae is a numpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Is Fae a kerpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a grimpus, so Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus."], "answer": "Fae is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yumpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "impus", "yimpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [18, 14], [4, 9], [0, 12], [4, 13], [9, 15], [17, 18], [1, 12], [11, 15], [3, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Sam is a numpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Is Sam a numpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a kerpus, so Sam is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a vumpus, so Sam is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lempus, so Sam is a lempus."], "answer": "Sam is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "felpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "timpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [6, 10], [0, 9], [11, 12], [8, 9], [9, 12], [12, 10], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Is Max a jompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a grimpus, so Max is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "vumpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 18], [11, 15], [7, 19], [11, 10], [15, 9], [12, 9], [3, 15], [17, 14], [19, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every storpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Max is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Is Max a zumpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a grimpus, so Max is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Max is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus."], "answer": "Max is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rorpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "numpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [8, 10], [11, 10], [3, 11], [0, 12], [12, 11], [4, 10], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every storpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Gabriel is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Is Gabriel a yerpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gwompus, so Gabriel is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "hilpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "impus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "jompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [12, 15], [10, 13], [16, 10], [7, 16], [15, 16], [6, 17], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a terpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Is Alex a yumpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a quimpus, so Alex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "boompus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "terpus", "rompus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [4, 10], [8, 10], [9, 12], [7, 9], [10, 9], [5, 12], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every storpus is a wumpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Is Alex a terpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a wumpus, so Alex is a wumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "shumpus", "kerpus", "bompus", "storpus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "felpus", "terpus", "jompus", "fompus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [4, 10], [15, 12], [7, 10], [2, 11], [10, 13], [15, 9], [15, 10], [9, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Alex is a wumpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Alex is a gwompus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Is Alex a jelpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gerpus, so Alex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus."], "answer": "Alex is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jompus", "shumpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "gwompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [0, 10], [10, 9], [0, 9], [5, 9], [4, 11], [5, 10], [3, 9], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a rempus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a chorpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gwompus", "impus", "rempus", "vumpus", "terpus", "lempus", "bompus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [3, 12], [12, 10], [4, 9], [6, 13], [4, 11], [3, 10], [11, 9], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Rex is a bompus. Rex is a brimpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Is Rex a worpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "lempus", "storpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "jompus", "felpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "bompus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [10, 11], [0, 15], [3, 16], [11, 14], [0, 13], [6, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Is Sam a brimpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rompus, so Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a felpus, so Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a hilpus, so Sam is a hilpus."], "answer": "Sam is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "gwompus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 15], [12, 10], [17, 18], [1, 17], [9, 14], [11, 14], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Polly is a terpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Is Polly a kerpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a felpus, so Polly is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "lempus", "shumpus", "jompus", "felpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "rompus", "boompus", "grimpus", "terpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [0, 10], [5, 9], [2, 10], [8, 9], [8, 10], [3, 11], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a terpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Is Stella a boompus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Stella is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a tumpus, so Stella is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Stella is a boompus."], "answer": "Stella is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "rorpus", "bompus", "rempus", "tumpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "terpus", "rompus", "fompus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [3, 12], [11, 9], [14, 13], [2, 10], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every felpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a impus. Max is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Is Max a impus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a tumpus, so Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a impus, so Max is a impus."], "answer": "Max is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rorpus", "yimpus", "lempus", "tumpus", "impus", "numpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [13, 9], [11, 12], [6, 11], [3, 12], [0, 10], [13, 11], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a numpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every impus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Oliver is a jompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Oliver is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a terpus. Is Oliver a jompus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a scrompus, so Oliver is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "impus", "zumpus", "jompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [0, 9], [2, 9], [11, 10], [0, 10], [3, 11], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Is Wren a bompus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus."], "answer": "Wren is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "gorpus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "bompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [9, 11], [11, 10], [1, 9], [6, 11], [6, 9], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Is Bob a worpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a lempus, so Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus."], "answer": "Bob is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "sterpus", "fompus", "lempus", "scrompus", "worpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "bompus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 18], [15, 17], [11, 14], [9, 12], [17, 15], [8, 16], [10, 13], [13, 11], [5, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a storpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Is Max a worpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a jelpus, so Max is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus."], "answer": "Max is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "timpus", "dumpus", "impus", "jelpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "terpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [7, 15], [15, 14], [5, 14], [17, 10], [16, 10], [10, 13], [4, 16], [19, 13], [12, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Is Eva a vumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a felpus, so Eva is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a sterpus, so Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rompus, so Eva is a rompus."], "answer": "Eva is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "yerpus", "jompus", "felpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [3, 9], [10, 11], [10, 12], [1, 11], [5, 13], [12, 9], [5, 9], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every felpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Davis is a rempus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Davis is a lorpus. Davis is a jelpus. Is Davis a lempus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus."], "answer": "Davis is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "grimpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "dumpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 19], [15, 11], [11, 12], [0, 15], [2, 10], [0, 9], [4, 13], [14, 10], [0, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Rex is a worpus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Is Rex a yimpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "scrompus", "rempus", "fompus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [10, 11], [6, 12], [0, 11], [13, 10], [12, 11], [11, 13], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Is Max a rompus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Max is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a shumpus, so Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a numpus, so Max is a numpus."], "answer": "Max is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "lorpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "numpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "impus", "bompus", "rompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [1, 11], [8, 9], [6, 10], [8, 12], [7, 10], [6, 12], [8, 11], [5, 9], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a dumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "jelpus", "brimpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "impus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "felpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [14, 13], [4, 17], [9, 11], [16, 10], [10, 13], [8, 12], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every terpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Is Tom a quimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zhorpus, so Tom is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "kerpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "boompus", "worpus", "quimpus", "impus", "timpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [8, 11], [14, 13], [7, 12], [2, 13], [14, 9], [13, 14], [9, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Oliver is a impus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Oliver is a worpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Is Oliver a dumpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a jelpus, so Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "jelpus", "gorpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "rompus", "impus", "lempus", "worpus", "chorpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 16], [17, 16], [13, 10], [5, 15], [17, 12], [0, 13], [0, 15], [15, 16], [9, 11], [11, 9], [1, 10], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rempus is a worpus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a rempus. Rex is a jompus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Is Rex a worpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Rex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus."], "answer": "Rex is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "shumpus", "timpus", "numpus", "rempus", "worpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "rompus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 12], [6, 15], [6, 16], [9, 13], [8, 11], [3, 12], [0, 15], [11, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Is Polly a lorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a terpus, so Polly is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a wumpus, so Polly is a wumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "grimpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [5, 10], [9, 13], [12, 10], [1, 12], [8, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every fompus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Sam is a gwompus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a fompus. Sam is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Is Sam a worpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Sam is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a lempus, so Sam is a lempus."], "answer": "Sam is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "lempus", "felpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "terpus", "worpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [16, 14], [6, 17], [9, 14], [9, 17], [0, 10], [11, 13], [16, 13], [0, 15], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Fae is a rempus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Is Fae a bompus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rorpus, so Fae is a rorpus."], "answer": "Fae is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "kerpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "timpus", "chorpus", "shumpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [4, 13], [6, 11], [1, 10], [13, 14], [8, 14], [7, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Is Eva a bompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a jelpus, so Eva is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a bompus, so Eva is a bompus."], "answer": "Eva is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "scrompus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "impus", "wumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [10, 12], [1, 17], [12, 17], [14, 11], [6, 15], [4, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every bompus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Oliver is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Is Oliver a tumpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "brimpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "bompus", "boompus", "terpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 15], [8, 13], [3, 11], [12, 16], [9, 10], [1, 10], [6, 11], [6, 17], [14, 9], [6, 13], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Wren is a impus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Wren is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Is Wren a impus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus."], "answer": "Wren is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "worpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "impus", "tumpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [4, 9], [0, 10], [0, 9], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Carol is a yumpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Is Carol a jelpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gorpus, so Carol is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jelpus, so Carol is a jelpus."], "answer": "Carol is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "fompus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "numpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "hilpus", "terpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [0, 12], [17, 9], [11, 10], [5, 19], [3, 15], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every numpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Jack is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Is Jack a fompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gerpus, so Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus."], "answer": "Jack is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "numpus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "fompus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "bompus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [15, 10], [12, 9], [11, 9], [4, 11], [1, 11], [14, 12], [0, 16], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a felpus. Fae is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Is Fae a worpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gorpus, so Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus."], "answer": "Fae is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "storpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "sterpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [9, 11], [3, 11], [0, 13], [4, 9], [8, 10], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every storpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Carol is a lempus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Is Carol a vumpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a numpus, so Carol is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yumpus, so Carol is a yumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "zumpus", "worpus", "numpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "lempus", "felpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [7, 11], [7, 12], [10, 15], [8, 10], [6, 14], [13, 15], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Sally is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Is Sally a quimpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "felpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "worpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "terpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 14], [13, 12], [1, 16], [0, 15], [16, 9], [5, 11], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Wren is a numpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Wren is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Is Wren a shumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a tumpus, so Wren is a tumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yumpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 14], [3, 14], [0, 13], [1, 11], [13, 10], [8, 12], [4, 13], [12, 9], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Sally is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Is Sally a dumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus."], "answer": "Sally is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "zumpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "fompus", "felpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "hilpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [0, 9], [7, 12], [3, 10], [1, 14], [16, 11], [16, 13], [10, 13], [12, 16], [3, 13], [6, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Is Davis a numpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a kerpus, so Davis is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus."], "answer": "Davis is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "impus", "worpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "storpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "yerpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 17], [11, 15], [6, 13], [15, 11], [12, 17], [15, 10], [12, 16], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Fae is a numpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Is Fae a numpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus."], "answer": "Fae is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yimpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "jompus", "numpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [14, 9], [12, 13], [9, 10], [3, 13], [0, 11], [7, 12], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every boompus is a brimpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Is Rex a storpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jelpus, so Rex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus."], "answer": "Rex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "numpus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "worpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "terpus", "impus", "wumpus", "storpus", "rorpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 17], [15, 10], [11, 12], [9, 15], [15, 13], [4, 16], [7, 15], [5, 17], [4, 11], [15, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Max is a impus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Is Max a gerpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a gorpus, so Max is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus."], "answer": "Max is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "fompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "timpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "yumpus", "impus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "storpus", "brimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [2, 11], [16, 9], [0, 11], [8, 18], [12, 16], [17, 10], [16, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a fompus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gorpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "terpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "impus", "fompus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [7, 12], [1, 13], [8, 9], [8, 13], [6, 10], [4, 10], [10, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every fompus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Is Jack a yimpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rempus, so Jack is a rempus."], "answer": "Jack is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "kerpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "timpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 19], [18, 17], [15, 14], [12, 17], [13, 15], [5, 12], [7, 12], [10, 11], [10, 14], [18, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rempus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Sam is a rempus. Is Sam a rempus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gerpus, so Sam is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a scrompus, so Sam is a scrompus."], "answer": "Sam is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "rompus", "bompus", "timpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "kerpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [14, 13], [13, 16], [0, 13], [5, 13], [2, 13], [5, 18], [14, 16], [1, 11], [8, 10], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Oliver is a impus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a gwompus or a impus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "lempus", "terpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "impus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [12, 13], [9, 12], [13, 10], [5, 9], [11, 10], [0, 13], [3, 11], [12, 10], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Is Oliver a zumpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rempus", "hilpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "terpus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "numpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [5, 12], [10, 17], [15, 13], [19, 12], [13, 10], [10, 19], [9, 11], [5, 14], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Sally is a numpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Is Sally a worpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus."], "answer": "Sally is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "tumpus", "lempus", "felpus", "terpus", "worpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 19], [5, 13], [5, 9], [0, 15], [19, 18], [2, 9], [16, 18], [7, 13], [10, 18], [14, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every boompus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Sally is a chorpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Is Sally a kerpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "boompus", "rompus", "fompus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [6, 11], [7, 10], [3, 12], [1, 10], [10, 11], [0, 11], [2, 11], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Is Sally a quimpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Sally is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yimpus, so Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus."], "answer": "Sally is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "zhorpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [3, 10], [8, 12], [6, 10], [1, 11], [6, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a yimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "worpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [3, 18], [5, 10], [6, 14], [18, 11], [3, 17], [11, 12], [9, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every timpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Oliver is a scrompus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a worpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rempus", "bompus", "timpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "felpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "jompus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [6, 17], [2, 16], [16, 14], [14, 17], [11, 9], [3, 14], [2, 13], [0, 11], [13, 9], [4, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every impus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every impus is a hilpus. Is Max a jompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "impus", "timpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 17], [17, 18], [11, 13], [13, 18], [18, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every rompus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Carol is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Carol is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Is Carol a zumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zhorpus, so Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yimpus, so Carol is a yimpus."], "answer": "Carol is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "rompus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "numpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [9, 10], [0, 10], [1, 9], [0, 9], [6, 9], [2, 11], [5, 11], [4, 11], [8, 11], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every impus is a dumpus. Sally is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Is Sally a rempus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus."], "answer": "Sally is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "scrompus", "lempus", "brimpus", "jompus", "rempus", "tumpus", "impus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "yumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 15], [6, 10], [7, 9], [0, 16], [13, 12], [7, 19], [7, 15], [3, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Is Polly a gorpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rorpus, so Polly is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a worpus, so Polly is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "storpus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "impus", "numpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [13, 12], [1, 11], [4, 12], [10, 9], [2, 11], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Is Carol a chorpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yimpus, so Carol is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus."], "answer": "Carol is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "zumpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [2, 10], [10, 11], [4, 11], [8, 10], [7, 10], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every terpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Is Fae a jelpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zhorpus, so Fae is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a wumpus, so Fae is a wumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "felpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "storpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "brimpus", "numpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [18, 11], [16, 13], [5, 14], [11, 10], [11, 14], [11, 15], [5, 11], [7, 18], [10, 11], [14, 11], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Is Fae a gorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lempus, so Fae is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a wumpus, so Fae is a wumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "dumpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "numpus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "worpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [2, 9], [11, 13], [11, 14], [6, 14], [1, 14], [6, 12], [12, 10], [11, 10], [2, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a impus. Every impus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Is Tom a impus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gerpus, so Tom is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus."], "answer": "Tom is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "brimpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "timpus", "impus", "hilpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "storpus", "jelpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 17], [12, 11], [3, 10], [5, 10], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Jack is a gwompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Is Jack a fompus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gerpus, so Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus."], "answer": "Jack is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "vumpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "felpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [7, 12], [5, 9], [3, 10], [4, 9], [5, 12], [11, 9], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a bompus. Eva is a lempus. Eva is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every impus is a jompus. Is Eva a lempus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Eva is a kerpus."], "answer": "Eva is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "impus", "terpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "bompus", "lempus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [1, 11], [0, 11], [0, 10], [4, 9], [8, 10], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every boompus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Is Jack a fompus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus."], "answer": "Jack is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "worpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "numpus", "lempus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "fompus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "boompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [7, 11], [14, 13], [8, 11], [3, 9], [6, 11], [13, 10], [4, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Is Oliver a numpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "shumpus", "sterpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "jompus", "numpus", "fompus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [14, 11], [15, 11], [8, 13], [9, 15], [3, 11], [4, 9], [9, 13], [1, 11], [14, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Sally is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every yerpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Is Sally a rempus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zhorpus, so Sally is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "zumpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "storpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "rempus", "bompus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [2, 13], [2, 10], [9, 13], [9, 12], [3, 13], [2, 11], [9, 11], [6, 10], [0, 13], [11, 12], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every timpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Is Bob a dumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus."], "answer": "Bob is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "sterpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "fompus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [4, 12], [14, 11], [1, 11], [4, 11], [8, 11], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every felpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Is Bob a storpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a lempus, so Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a sterpus, so Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a terpus, so Bob is a terpus."], "answer": "Bob is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "felpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "worpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [16, 9], [11, 10], [3, 16], [9, 14], [2, 12], [5, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rompus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Max is a lorpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Is Max a rorpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a numpus, so Max is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a gorpus, so Max is a gorpus."], "answer": "Max is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "wumpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "numpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "felpus", "boompus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 15], [4, 10], [15, 11], [13, 14], [7, 10], [10, 12], [0, 15], [4, 12], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a impus. Alex is a rompus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Is Alex a impus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus."], "answer": "Alex is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "vumpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "timpus", "impus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [11, 13], [4, 11], [8, 10], [0, 14], [4, 15], [8, 9], [9, 12], [1, 15], [4, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Stella is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Is Stella a zhorpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus."], "answer": "Stella is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "tumpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "timpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [5, 16], [16, 10], [12, 14], [4, 10], [10, 11], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every storpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Is Jack a dumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "brimpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "timpus", "storpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "jompus", "rempus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [10, 13], [15, 16], [6, 12], [6, 9], [9, 16], [16, 11], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Jack is a scrompus. Is Jack a jelpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "bompus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "yumpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [9, 13], [3, 12], [13, 11], [0, 12], [10, 12], [7, 10], [2, 11], [1, 9], [8, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Gabriel is a dumpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Is Gabriel a yerpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rempus, so Gabriel is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a yerpus, so Gabriel is a yerpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "yimpus", "rempus", "storpus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "terpus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [2, 12], [2, 14], [15, 10], [4, 13], [5, 10], [5, 11], [14, 9], [14, 11], [5, 15], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Is Bob a lempus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus."], "answer": "Bob is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "timpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "terpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 12], [9, 15], [2, 9], [11, 9], [1, 10], [7, 12], [9, 16], [11, 14], [17, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Is Wren a bompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus."], "answer": "Wren is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "kerpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [1, 12], [9, 12], [3, 12], [2, 11], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every fompus is a impus. Is Gabriel a zhorpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "grimpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "boompus", "lempus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "impus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "numpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 18], [19, 18], [16, 14], [9, 11], [2, 14], [2, 19], [3, 19], [6, 18], [2, 13], [19, 15], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Stella is a terpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a impus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Is Stella a impus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rompus, so Stella is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a impus, so Stella is a impus."], "answer": "Stella is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "tumpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "rompus", "impus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "numpus", "sterpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [15, 13], [13, 10], [1, 11], [15, 9], [0, 11], [2, 9], [6, 10], [7, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every storpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Max is a timpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Is Max a felpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a hilpus, so Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus."], "answer": "Max is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "brimpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "worpus", "felpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [5, 9], [4, 10], [7, 9], [2, 10], [8, 9], [5, 11], [1, 11], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Is Max a worpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Max is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yumpus, so Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "gwompus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "boompus", "rompus", "bompus", "lorpus", "wumpus", "storpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [10, 16], [16, 14], [7, 15], [16, 11], [4, 12], [2, 11], [11, 9], [3, 13], [8, 10], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gwompus. Fae is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Is Fae a timpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zumpus, so Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus."], "answer": "Fae is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "rorpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [5, 12], [6, 12], [3, 13], [1, 10], [9, 11], [13, 10], [0, 11], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Is Sally a rorpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus."], "answer": "Sally is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "storpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "lempus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [8, 10], [8, 12], [6, 11], [6, 10], [1, 11], [5, 12], [2, 11], [10, 12], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Is Alex a rompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus."], "answer": "Alex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [1, 9], [3, 11], [7, 10], [5, 9], [7, 9], [7, 11], [1, 11], [2, 9], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Sally is a gorpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Is Sally a scrompus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a tumpus, so Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zhorpus, so Sally is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "rempus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 12], [0, 11], [8, 12], [18, 12], [6, 14], [7, 18], [17, 11], [15, 16], [11, 9], [18, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Is Eva a yerpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "yumpus", "fompus", "worpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [11, 14], [12, 9], [2, 11], [1, 11], [7, 12], [6, 10], [1, 14], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Tom is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Is Tom a worpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lorpus, so Tom is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Tom is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a numpus, so Tom is a numpus."], "answer": "Tom is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "rempus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [8, 10], [10, 11], [9, 11], [2, 11], [0, 10], [2, 9], [8, 11], [4, 9], [5, 11], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Sally is a rompus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Sally is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Is Sally a grimpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zhorpus, so Sally is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "rempus", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "felpus", "terpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 17], [13, 10], [16, 11], [1, 15], [8, 13], [0, 12], [11, 14], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every worpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Eva is a dumpus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every impus is a quimpus. Is Eva a timpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a yimpus, so Eva is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus."], "answer": "Eva is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "worpus", "rempus", "impus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "storpus", "lempus", "fompus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [12, 10], [8, 11], [0, 10], [7, 10], [3, 9], [14, 9], [2, 11], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a storpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Is Eva a lempus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a wumpus, so Eva is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a jelpus, so Eva is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus."], "answer": "Eva is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "quimpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "boompus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [2, 14], [6, 14], [6, 9], [13, 9], [1, 14], [15, 12], [4, 9], [9, 15], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Polly is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every impus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Is Polly a lempus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a terpus, so Polly is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus."], "answer": "Polly is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yerpus", "yumpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "impus", "shumpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "bompus", "tumpus", "jompus", "felpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [16, 15], [10, 16], [3, 14], [4, 9], [0, 16], [14, 10], [14, 16], [6, 11], [5, 9], [1, 9], [7, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Is Max a jelpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Max is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jelpus, so Max is a jelpus."], "answer": "Max is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "gorpus", "rempus", "fompus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "impus", "worpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "storpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [18, 14], [3, 11], [19, 11], [19, 16], [8, 12], [4, 17], [8, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Wren is a terpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Is Wren a kerpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a impus, so Wren is a impus.", "Every impus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus."], "answer": "Wren is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "lempus", "gwompus", "impus", "yerpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [5, 11], [19, 18], [10, 19], [8, 15], [0, 13], [8, 11], [3, 14], [2, 19], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Davis is a rempus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a felpus. Is Davis a rempus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a storpus, so Davis is a storpus."], "answer": "Davis is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gerpus", "numpus", "grimpus", "hilpus", "storpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "worpus", "felpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [11, 12], [10, 9], [4, 10], [6, 9], [7, 11], [12, 9], [9, 11], [1, 12], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a impus. Davis is a rorpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Is Davis a grimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rompus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "storpus", "rempus", "yerpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "jelpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [3, 10], [9, 16], [16, 12], [9, 13], [11, 10], [10, 11], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jompus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Rex is a lempus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Is Rex a shumpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus."], "answer": "Rex is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rompus", "hilpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "boompus", "timpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [2, 11], [0, 10], [4, 10], [8, 10], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Bob is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Is Bob a bompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a felpus, so Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a quimpus, so Bob is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus."], "answer": "Bob is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "lorpus", "tumpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "boompus", "rompus", "impus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [7, 10], [11, 9], [10, 9], [8, 10], [8, 9], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Sam is a chorpus. Is Sam a yumpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zumpus, so Sam is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lorpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "storpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [0, 13], [4, 12], [3, 12], [4, 11], [5, 13], [7, 13], [6, 10], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a boompus. Carol is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Is Carol a zumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Carol is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a hilpus, so Carol is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rempus, so Carol is a rempus."], "answer": "Carol is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "yimpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "rempus", "boompus", "terpus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "storpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [14, 13], [9, 14], [6, 9], [1, 13], [4, 11], [7, 9], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Sally is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Sally is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Is Sally a lempus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rorpus, so Sally is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "timpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "storpus", "grimpus", "impus", "yerpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "terpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "jelpus", "fompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [13, 16], [1, 10], [1, 11], [2, 12], [17, 19], [2, 9], [5, 14], [0, 13], [0, 11], [4, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Is Stella a kerpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a zumpus, so Stella is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus."], "answer": "Stella is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "worpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "bompus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [2, 13], [5, 12], [12, 10], [4, 11], [1, 9], [2, 9], [1, 11], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Is Jack a vumpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a wumpus, so Jack is a wumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "lempus", "jelpus", "fompus", "numpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [10, 12], [3, 9], [9, 10], [8, 10], [4, 11], [12, 10], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Sam is a gerpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Sam is a worpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every jompus is a boompus. Is Sam a worpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a hilpus, so Sam is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a storpus, so Sam is a storpus."], "answer": "Sam is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "timpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "storpus", "jompus", "felpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [0, 10], [6, 11], [8, 9], [12, 15], [14, 10], [0, 12], [6, 12], [9, 13], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Is Gabriel a hilpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a bompus, so Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Gabriel is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yerpus, so Gabriel is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a numpus, so Gabriel is a numpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "quimpus", "bompus", "rempus", "yerpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "boompus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 14], [4, 11], [13, 18], [1, 18], [18, 17], [9, 10], [5, 11], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a worpus. Bob is a jompus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Is Bob a chorpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a lempus, so Bob is a lempus."], "answer": "Bob is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "bompus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "worpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "jompus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 17], [1, 10], [9, 17], [13, 16], [14, 9], [11, 14], [17, 16], [2, 16], [0, 13], [13, 17], [13, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every worpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a fompus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Is Sam a scrompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Sam is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a dumpus, so Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus."], "answer": "Sam is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "worpus", "gerpus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "rempus", "impus", "quimpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [6, 10], [11, 10], [11, 12], [1, 12], [5, 12], [8, 9], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every felpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Is Stella a hilpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a jelpus, so Stella is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a kerpus, so Stella is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a scrompus, so Stella is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Stella is a rorpus."], "answer": "Stella is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "quimpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "rompus", "brimpus", "fompus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [8, 9], [11, 14], [11, 12], [10, 12], [1, 9], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every numpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Rex is a numpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Is Rex a rorpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a wumpus, so Rex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rorpus, so Rex is a rorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "grimpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "numpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [0, 10], [7, 10], [1, 10], [11, 9], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rempus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Is Polly a gwompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a grimpus, so Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "rempus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "lempus", "bompus", "scrompus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 13], [1, 11], [2, 9], [1, 10], [10, 9], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every storpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Oliver is a zumpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a kerpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "storpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [7, 10], [0, 12], [5, 12], [2, 9], [7, 9], [4, 12], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Is Davis a rempus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yerpus, so Davis is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus."], "answer": "Davis is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "shumpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "felpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "bompus", "rempus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [6, 12], [11, 12], [11, 10], [4, 12], [6, 10], [5, 10], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every storpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Is Polly a storpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a felpus, so Polly is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rompus, so Polly is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a storpus, so Polly is a storpus."], "answer": "Polly is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "numpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "rompus", "storpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [1, 9], [2, 12], [6, 11], [3, 12], [13, 12], [2, 11], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Is Fae a yimpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus."], "answer": "Fae is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "rompus", "dumpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [4, 9], [8, 12], [10, 9], [1, 11], [7, 10], [1, 9], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a impus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every bompus is a rompus. Is Carol a jompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a dumpus, so Carol is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zhorpus, so Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus."], "answer": "Carol is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "bompus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "jompus", "rompus", "lempus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "impus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [7, 16], [6, 11], [1, 10], [8, 13], [8, 12], [8, 15], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Is Eva a worpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a felpus, so Eva is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a jelpus, so Eva is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus."], "answer": "Eva is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "yumpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "worpus", "lorpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [12, 10], [9, 12], [3, 11], [13, 11], [10, 14], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a fompus. Max is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a numpus. Is Max a lorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lorpus, so Max is a lorpus."], "answer": "Max is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "boompus", "impus", "fompus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [3, 9], [6, 10], [0, 12], [6, 11], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Sally is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Is Sally a brimpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "shumpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "gorpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [11, 12], [5, 11], [10, 9], [0, 10], [11, 9], [12, 9], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Sam is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Is Sam a jompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a grimpus, so Sam is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a timpus, so Sam is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus."], "answer": "Sam is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "sterpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "timpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "boompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 17], [0, 14], [18, 16], [7, 10], [3, 14], [16, 19], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Wren is a chorpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Is Wren a rempus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "bompus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [0, 14], [3, 16], [5, 10], [17, 15], [1, 15], [8, 17], [1, 16], [10, 11], [9, 17], [1, 9], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Oliver is a impus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Is Oliver a felpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gorpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "impus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [10, 13], [2, 13], [11, 10], [1, 11], [10, 15], [6, 16], [12, 13], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Tom is a bompus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Is Tom a jompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus."], "answer": "Tom is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "kerpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "rompus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [5, 11], [5, 12], [1, 11], [1, 10], [9, 13], [11, 10], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a worpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Stella is a yumpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Is Stella a wumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zhorpus, so Stella is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Stella is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a impus, so Stella is a impus.", "Every impus is a worpus, so Stella is a worpus."], "answer": "Stella is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "rempus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "impus", "worpus", "timpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [1, 9], [5, 11], [10, 9], [4, 11], [3, 12], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rempus is a bompus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a rempus. Gabriel is a yerpus. Gabriel is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Is Gabriel a jelpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rempus, so Gabriel is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a bompus, so Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "boompus", "rempus", "bompus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [15, 11], [1, 11], [4, 10], [10, 11], [0, 9], [15, 10], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a impus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Is Oliver a grimpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "impus", "yumpus", "boompus", "rompus", "jompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [10, 11], [4, 11], [9, 10], [2, 11], [6, 11], [1, 11], [2, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Is Polly a jompus or a impus?", "steps": ["Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rompus, so Polly is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a worpus, so Polly is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus."], "answer": "Polly is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "gwompus", "brimpus", "rompus", "worpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "impus", "numpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [4, 9], [6, 9], [5, 10], [3, 11], [4, 11], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jompus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Is Rex a lorpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus."], "answer": "Rex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rompus", "boompus", "jompus", "fompus", "terpus", "quimpus", "storpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [8, 11], [1, 14], [11, 9], [12, 14], [3, 14], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Is Tom a sterpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus."], "answer": "Tom is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "hilpus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "felpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "storpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [11, 9], [5, 9], [5, 11], [7, 11], [8, 9], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a terpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Bob is a brimpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Bob is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Is Bob a brimpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a terpus, so Bob is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "lempus", "shumpus", "scrompus", "terpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "felpus", "brimpus", "sterpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [0, 11], [2, 13], [0, 13], [10, 13], [6, 10], [7, 9], [1, 9], [2, 11], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Is Alex a shumpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gwompus, so Alex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus."], "answer": "Alex is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "felpus", "terpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "fompus", "rempus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "jompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [7, 9], [11, 13], [9, 11], [7, 12], [14, 10], [4, 13], [4, 14], [5, 10], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every terpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Max is a felpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Is Max a felpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a bompus, so Max is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a vumpus, so Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus."], "answer": "Max is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "scrompus", "bompus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "impus", "numpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [3, 14], [11, 15], [9, 12], [6, 14], [7, 9], [0, 13], [15, 11], [8, 13], [8, 12], [13, 9], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every terpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Wren is a scrompus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Wren is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Is Wren a scrompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus."], "answer": "Wren is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "fompus", "rempus", "zumpus", "terpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [0, 11], [8, 9], [0, 10], [11, 9], [3, 10], [12, 10], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Carol is a shumpus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Is Carol a tumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gwompus, so Carol is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "zhorpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "timpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [13, 12], [0, 12], [3, 13], [8, 14], [1, 10], [12, 13], [1, 9], [10, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a gerpus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Is Sam a tumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a impus, so Sam is a impus.", "Every impus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "dumpus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "impus", "tumpus", "bompus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [2, 12], [8, 9], [1, 12], [4, 10], [13, 12], [1, 11], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every boompus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Is Eva a tumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gerpus, so Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "boompus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "numpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 15], [1, 13], [9, 16], [7, 10], [14, 9], [14, 11], [1, 14], [9, 13], [3, 14], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Carol is a jompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Is Carol a bompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a dumpus, so Carol is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a bompus, so Carol is a bompus."], "answer": "Carol is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "jelpus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "yerpus", "rompus", "jompus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [3, 9], [12, 10], [12, 9], [12, 11], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Gabriel is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Is Gabriel a worpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a wumpus, so Gabriel is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "grimpus", "felpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "impus", "dumpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [9, 13], [6, 10], [11, 12], [7, 10], [2, 11], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Oliver is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every worpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Is Oliver a gwompus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "jompus", "terpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "impus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "bompus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [7, 14], [10, 12], [11, 14], [0, 14], [13, 14], [14, 12], [6, 12], [10, 14], [9, 12], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Is Alex a quimpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a wumpus, so Alex is a wumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "yerpus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [12, 11], [3, 12], [2, 10], [12, 10], [11, 10], [6, 10], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Is Oliver a yumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a fompus, so Oliver is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "fompus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "impus", "boompus", "kerpus", "rempus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "worpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [1, 11], [6, 11], [6, 13], [9, 12], [11, 10], [11, 15], [9, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a felpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Is Oliver a zhorpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "fompus", "hilpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "impus", "felpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [13, 17], [14, 15], [5, 14], [14, 12], [1, 9], [5, 10], [15, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a lorpus. Davis is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Is Davis a jelpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a storpus, so Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus."], "answer": "Davis is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "bompus", "grimpus", "storpus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "terpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [3, 11], [17, 14], [4, 9], [8, 14], [13, 16], [0, 11], [2, 12], [8, 10], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a jompus. Carol is a fompus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Carol is a rompus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Carol is a scrompus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Carol is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a timpus. Is Carol a kerpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a bompus, so Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus."], "answer": "Carol is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "yumpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "timpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "impus", "kerpus", "rompus", "fompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [4, 14], [7, 15], [9, 10], [0, 12], [4, 12], [9, 13], [0, 14], [10, 9], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Rex is a lempus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Is Rex a quimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a vumpus, so Rex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a kerpus, so Rex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus."], "answer": "Rex is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "timpus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "hilpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [10, 13], [7, 11], [0, 9], [7, 9], [11, 10], [8, 11], [3, 9], [9, 10], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Is Alex a rempus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rempus, so Alex is a rempus."], "answer": "Alex is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "zumpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [4, 10], [8, 9], [13, 9], [1, 11], [4, 9], [6, 12], [3, 11], [5, 11], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Jack is a scrompus. Is Jack a yerpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "dumpus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "felpus", "terpus", "lempus", "rompus", "worpus", "wumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [10, 13], [3, 11], [4, 9], [10, 14], [7, 10], [14, 16], [7, 17], [1, 15], [18, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every fompus is a terpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Is Fae a vumpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zumpus, so Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a fompus, so Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus."], "answer": "Fae is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "rompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "fompus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "felpus", "jelpus", "terpus", "lempus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [4, 9], [2, 10], [11, 10], [6, 11], [10, 9], [2, 9], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Is Wren a jompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gerpus, so Wren is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Wren is a jompus."], "answer": "Wren is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "lorpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "timpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 14], [15, 10], [3, 15], [1, 10], [5, 13], [1, 12], [13, 14], [12, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Is Sam a scrompus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a jelpus, so Sam is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "dumpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "jompus", "timpus", "impus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "storpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 13], [6, 10], [2, 10], [7, 11], [5, 13], [10, 12], [11, 10], [1, 11], [10, 13], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Is Polly a jompus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Polly is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus."], "answer": "Polly is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "grimpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "jompus", "rempus", "bompus", "rompus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "impus", "terpus", "lempus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 12], [6, 17], [9, 16], [15, 12], [2, 12], [2, 16], [15, 10], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every timpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Is Alex a boompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jompus, so Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus."], "answer": "Alex is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "wumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "timpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [5, 11], [2, 10], [1, 10], [4, 9], [4, 12], [6, 13], [4, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Is Rex a shumpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "yimpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "vumpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "felpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [6, 17], [7, 9], [10, 15], [4, 11], [13, 12], [2, 15], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Is Oliver a sterpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a fompus, so Oliver is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "bompus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [7, 12], [9, 11], [1, 13], [7, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lempus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Is Polly a yumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "lempus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "rompus", "grimpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [1, 15], [12, 11], [13, 15], [1, 13], [11, 15], [5, 13], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Eva is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Is Eva a gorpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a sterpus, so Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus."], "answer": "Eva is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "terpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "timpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [1, 12], [5, 9], [14, 13], [4, 13], [0, 14], [6, 12], [12, 9], [8, 13], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Sam is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Is Sam a yimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a jelpus, so Sam is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "terpus", "jelpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [2, 12], [5, 12], [1, 11], [7, 9], [5, 9], [1, 9], [6, 10], [2, 10], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Sally is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Is Sally a vumpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "storpus", "terpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [3, 12], [0, 10], [2, 10], [3, 11], [11, 12], [4, 10], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Is Jack a zhorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "timpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "impus", "zumpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [1, 15], [14, 10], [11, 17], [10, 14], [2, 17], [4, 11], [1, 16], [15, 9], [15, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Is Rex a brimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "boompus", "yimpus", "storpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "numpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [9, 11], [11, 9], [17, 15], [16, 12], [8, 11], [8, 15], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Fae is a rompus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Is Fae a yimpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yerpus, so Fae is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "fompus", "tumpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "impus", "quimpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "worpus", "rompus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [5, 13], [7, 9], [9, 11], [8, 9], [11, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Is Wren a impus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rorpus, so Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "worpus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "numpus", "hilpus", "impus", "scrompus", "rompus", "gerpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [12, 9], [6, 9], [12, 10], [8, 11], [11, 13], [4, 12], [11, 12], [1, 12], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Is Gabriel a yumpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "numpus", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "terpus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [8, 9], [12, 10], [3, 11], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every timpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Carol is a impus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Is Carol a scrompus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a zumpus, so Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus."], "answer": "Carol is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "felpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "boompus", "timpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "lempus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 10], [6, 15], [10, 13], [0, 15], [9, 13], [1, 13], [17, 13], [6, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every felpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Gabriel is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Is Gabriel a lorpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "felpus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "terpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [6, 13], [0, 11], [5, 11], [14, 11], [4, 10], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Eva is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Is Eva a gorpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a sterpus, so Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "chorpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [9, 12], [11, 10], [2, 11], [11, 9], [7, 10], [7, 11], [0, 10], [3, 11], [2, 9], [4, 11], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Is Carol a zumpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Carol is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus."], "answer": "Carol is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "quimpus", "storpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "tumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [12, 15], [5, 14], [11, 13], [11, 12], [1, 15], [2, 15], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Wren is a wumpus. Is Wren a dumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jompus, so Wren is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus."], "answer": "Wren is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "hilpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "rempus", "rompus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "felpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 19], [13, 14], [7, 16], [0, 11], [18, 19], [12, 13], [14, 13], [5, 18], [17, 11], [17, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a impus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every impus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Is Alex a rorpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Alex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a rempus, so Alex is a rempus."], "answer": "Alex is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "wumpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "terpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "impus", "fompus", "felpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [11, 15], [5, 15], [12, 10], [15, 10], [12, 11], [11, 13], [3, 15], [12, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a brimpus. Bob is a jelpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Bob is a bompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Is Bob a gorpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a sterpus, so Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "boompus", "rompus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [8, 10], [0, 13], [1, 12], [12, 9], [10, 9], [6, 13], [5, 11], [8, 9], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Sally is a yumpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Is Sally a gorpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a boompus, so Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gorpus, so Sally is a gorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gwompus", "boompus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [0, 10], [2, 11], [4, 11], [10, 11], [8, 11], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Sally is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Is Sally a storpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "tumpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [1, 10], [9, 10], [2, 9], [5, 9], [1, 9], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Is Alex a timpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a chorpus, so Alex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a sterpus, so Alex is a sterpus."], "answer": "Alex is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "grimpus", "terpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "timpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [1, 15], [14, 12], [8, 12], [14, 9], [6, 9], [3, 14], [5, 10], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Fae is a kerpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Is Fae a sterpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "terpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "felpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [1, 9], [7, 9], [2, 12], [4, 12], [7, 10], [12, 9], [5, 11], [8, 12], [6, 11], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every storpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Gabriel is a tumpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Is Gabriel a gerpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "felpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "boompus", "timpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [3, 12], [5, 10], [11, 12], [0, 10], [9, 13], [7, 13], [10, 12], [8, 9], [9, 10], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every numpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every impus is a numpus. Is Eva a sterpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "bompus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "impus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "terpus", "jompus", "felpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 15], [15, 14], [4, 10], [5, 12], [13, 11], [15, 10], [12, 10], [7, 15], [3, 9], [12, 13], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jompus is a bompus. Every rompus is a impus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Is Alex a storpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a boompus, so Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jompus", "fompus", "impus", "boompus", "yumpus", "rompus", "timpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "storpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [3, 14], [3, 11], [4, 11], [9, 10], [6, 14], [1, 14], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Is Oliver a grimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "terpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "worpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [15, 14], [12, 14], [10, 15], [9, 12], [10, 14], [12, 15], [9, 14], [13, 14], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Is Alex a yerpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "numpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "rempus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [3, 13], [5, 10], [11, 12], [1, 13], [8, 12], [5, 9], [11, 10], [9, 14], [2, 11], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a impus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Jack is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Is Jack a brimpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a sterpus, so Jack is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a hilpus, so Jack is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a scrompus, so Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a wumpus, so Jack is a wumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "tumpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "fompus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [4, 9], [11, 9], [0, 11], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a jompus. Oliver is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Is Oliver a gwompus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus."], "answer": "Oliver is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "dumpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [8, 9], [2, 10], [11, 10], [0, 11], [4, 11], [7, 9], [5, 9], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Is Alex a timpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a hilpus, so Alex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus."], "answer": "Alex is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "vumpus", "yerpus", "impus", "hilpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [1, 11], [5, 9], [10, 11], [3, 11], [2, 10], [11, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Is Davis a gerpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus."], "answer": "Davis is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "yumpus", "lempus", "rompus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "rempus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [8, 12], [2, 9], [10, 11], [3, 9], [11, 10], [9, 10], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every impus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Is Eva a storpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Eva is a kerpus."], "answer": "Eva is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "gwompus", "worpus", "rempus", "fompus", "kerpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "storpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [1, 12], [15, 9], [12, 13], [15, 11], [10, 16], [15, 16], [7, 9], [15, 17], [16, 14], [13, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Is Rex a gwompus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rorpus, so Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus."], "answer": "Rex is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "felpus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "terpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 9], [15, 13], [2, 16], [10, 15], [15, 12], [4, 11], [8, 10], [16, 12], [10, 13], [4, 12], [3, 13], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Is Rex a lorpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a tumpus, so Rex is a tumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "impus", "jompus", "brimpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "terpus", "rompus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [7, 11], [3, 9], [5, 10], [8, 11], [7, 12], [6, 11], [4, 9], [1, 10], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Is Polly a kerpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lorpus, so Polly is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a terpus, so Polly is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a quimpus, so Polly is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yerpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 13], [4, 12], [5, 11], [2, 12], [15, 12], [10, 9], [4, 10], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Polly is a bompus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Is Polly a boompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Polly is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a timpus, so Polly is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a wumpus, so Polly is a wumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "gerpus", "lempus", "terpus", "timpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "worpus", "hilpus", "rempus", "boompus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "impus", "scrompus", "bompus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [1, 11], [3, 14], [13, 14], [6, 14], [7, 9], [2, 9], [0, 15], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Wren is a rempus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Is Wren a chorpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a brimpus, so Wren is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a worpus, so Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a scrompus, so Wren is a scrompus."], "answer": "Wren is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "tumpus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "impus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "rempus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [0, 11], [14, 12], [5, 9], [13, 9], [15, 14], [14, 16], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Carol is a gerpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Carol is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Carol is a sterpus. Is Carol a sterpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a quimpus, so Carol is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a felpus, so Carol is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus."], "answer": "Carol is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "zhorpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [4, 11], [10, 11], [1, 12], [0, 10], [1, 9], [7, 10], [8, 9], [0, 13], [8, 11], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Is Oliver a yerpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "dumpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "felpus", "fompus", "gwompus", "boompus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "worpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 12], [8, 15], [11, 13], [4, 11], [2, 12], [9, 10], [7, 9], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Is Sam a lempus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a grimpus, so Sam is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a sterpus, so Sam is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sam is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "chorpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "felpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [11, 9], [6, 10], [9, 12], [2, 10], [1, 12], [4, 12], [1, 10], [12, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every lempus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Wren is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Is Wren a yimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a worpus, so Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus."], "answer": "Wren is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "bompus", "lempus", "worpus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "storpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "rorpus", "fompus", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "impus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 15], [0, 14], [10, 17], [14, 13], [3, 17], [18, 12], [1, 16], [3, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every bompus is a lempus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Is Bob a jompus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a felpus, so Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus."], "answer": "Bob is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gorpus", "bompus", "felpus", "gerpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "numpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "boompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [5, 11], [1, 11], [16, 15], [2, 9], [16, 9], [13, 11], [2, 16], [15, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Oliver is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Oliver is a gerpus. Is Oliver a timpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a scrompus, so Oliver is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a grimpus, so Oliver is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "bompus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "sterpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [14, 10], [0, 11], [0, 9], [4, 10], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Is Tom a terpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a sterpus, so Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus."], "answer": "Tom is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "quimpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "rempus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "impus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [16, 15], [3, 17], [2, 15], [5, 15], [7, 15], [3, 12], [4, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Sam is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Is Sam a impus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a fompus, so Sam is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Sam is a impus."], "answer": "Sam is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "kerpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "fompus", "impus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 15], [7, 15], [0, 10], [4, 15], [12, 15], [11, 12], [14, 11], [8, 11], [9, 13], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a impus. Is Carol a scrompus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a lempus, so Carol is a lempus."], "answer": "Carol is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "shumpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "timpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "numpus", "felpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "yerpus", "impus", "scrompus", "storpus", "jelpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [17, 15], [6, 12], [7, 16], [2, 13], [2, 12], [17, 14], [7, 15], [9, 14], [5, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Is Max a timpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "quimpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "lempus", "numpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "rempus", "hilpus", "timpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [4, 14], [4, 9], [2, 12], [3, 11], [13, 11], [7, 9], [3, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Max is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Is Max a wumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a shumpus, so Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus."], "answer": "Max is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "chorpus", "brimpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "impus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [6, 10], [0, 9], [2, 11], [11, 9], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every felpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Is Tom a yimpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a zhorpus, so Tom is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus."], "answer": "Tom is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "impus", "worpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "felpus", "timpus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 13], [8, 12], [3, 9], [15, 13], [5, 16], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Alex is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Is Alex a yerpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "rompus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "worpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [2, 10], [5, 10], [7, 9], [2, 9], [10, 11], [1, 9], [0, 9], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Jack is a impus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Is Jack a tumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Jack is a rempus."], "answer": "Jack is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "brimpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "numpus", "rempus", "sterpus", "jompus", "timpus", "impus", "tumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [1, 9], [4, 10], [7, 11], [1, 10], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Is Sally a boompus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yimpus, so Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus."], "answer": "Sally is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "kerpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "grimpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [3, 11], [9, 11], [5, 9], [4, 9], [8, 11], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Wren is a rorpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Is Wren a felpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gerpus, so Wren is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus."], "answer": "Wren is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "chorpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "felpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "sterpus", "rempus", "numpus", "jelpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 15], [2, 11], [2, 10], [4, 12], [4, 15], [3, 13], [3, 9], [4, 13], [0, 9], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Is Carol a worpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus."], "answer": "Carol is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "brimpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "terpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "storpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 17], [12, 15], [11, 16], [11, 15], [6, 15], [15, 16], [1, 9], [4, 13], [18, 10], [15, 11], [14, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Davis is a worpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Is Davis a tumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "grimpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "lempus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "fompus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 14], [1, 14], [11, 14], [12, 11], [10, 14], [0, 14], [7, 10], [3, 14], [4, 9], [11, 12], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a terpus. Is Davis a zumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a terpus, so Davis is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "brimpus", "timpus", "terpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [4, 15], [16, 11], [1, 10], [15, 9], [11, 9], [8, 9], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every impus is a storpus. Fae is a storpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Is Fae a impus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a rorpus, so Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus."], "answer": "Fae is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "zumpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "impus", "yumpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [8, 11], [12, 9], [9, 15], [12, 15], [5, 13], [3, 9], [16, 12], [6, 10], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every boompus is a fompus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Is Sally a fompus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gorpus, so Sally is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "lempus", "gorpus", "rompus", "timpus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [1, 10], [4, 11], [8, 10], [7, 11], [11, 10], [3, 11], [7, 10], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rompus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Is Max a chorpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yumpus, so Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a shumpus, so Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus."], "answer": "Max is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rompus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [14, 10], [5, 9], [8, 15], [9, 15], [17, 15], [13, 9], [15, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every bompus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Eva is a storpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Eva is a boompus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Eva is a grimpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "vumpus", "timpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "bompus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "boompus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "storpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 14], [3, 16], [1, 13], [0, 13], [7, 16], [1, 14], [2, 12], [12, 9], [0, 11], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Is Alex a terpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus."], "answer": "Alex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "gerpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "numpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "gorpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 10], [13, 15], [7, 15], [15, 14], [6, 13], [5, 13], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every boompus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Davis is a numpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Davis is a brimpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Is Davis a chorpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus."], "answer": "Davis is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "bompus", "lempus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "boompus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [0, 11], [2, 9], [9, 12], [4, 10], [5, 11], [8, 9], [7, 10], [10, 11], [0, 12], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every timpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Is Gabriel a zumpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "timpus", "impus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "fompus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "boompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 16], [3, 11], [13, 11], [10, 18], [10, 9], [13, 17], [16, 17], [1, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Fae is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Is Fae a lempus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a numpus, so Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a lempus, so Fae is a lempus."], "answer": "Fae is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yimpus", "felpus", "numpus", "storpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "boompus", "bompus", "zumpus", "wumpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [3, 9], [5, 10], [14, 13], [10, 11], [10, 12], [0, 12], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Is Stella a lorpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a dumpus, so Stella is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gwompus, so Stella is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lorpus, so Stella is a lorpus."], "answer": "Stella is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "vumpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [3, 12], [11, 13], [3, 13], [12, 14], [4, 10], [8, 9], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Is Stella a wumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a storpus, so Stella is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a jompus, so Stella is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "boompus", "storpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 15], [3, 11], [14, 10], [9, 10], [4, 12], [11, 9], [15, 9], [15, 12], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every storpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Oliver is a numpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Is Oliver a tumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "shumpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "wumpus", "impus", "chorpus", "jompus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "numpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [11, 13], [4, 11], [1, 14], [5, 9], [11, 10], [0, 13], [8, 13], [6, 10], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Is Jack a yumpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a vumpus, so Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "numpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "rompus", "boompus", "felpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [9, 15], [6, 13], [14, 15], [11, 10], [13, 9], [13, 12], [16, 9], [7, 14], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Rex is a vumpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Rex is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Is Rex a vumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "quimpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "numpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [12, 11], [7, 10], [4, 9], [0, 10], [3, 10], [2, 9], [0, 9], [8, 9], [4, 11], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Is Wren a worpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a rompus, so Wren is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus."], "answer": "Wren is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "rorpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "bompus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 15], [2, 12], [12, 13], [9, 13], [14, 12], [6, 13], [9, 11], [9, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every fompus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a numpus. Rex is a numpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Is Rex a gorpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gorpus, so Rex is a gorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "fompus", "boompus", "lempus", "storpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "rompus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [6, 10], [10, 13], [2, 14], [1, 9], [0, 14], [2, 12], [8, 11], [10, 12], [3, 12], [7, 12], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Oliver is a rompus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Is Oliver a scrompus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a scrompus, so Oliver is a scrompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "yumpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "rempus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "rompus", "lorpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [3, 9], [0, 12], [5, 12], [1, 9], [6, 14], [8, 13], [3, 10], [2, 14], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Polly is a numpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Is Polly a rompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a felpus, so Polly is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "zumpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "numpus", "rompus", "boompus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [3, 16], [5, 15], [12, 10], [2, 16], [16, 9], [14, 11], [0, 11], [14, 10], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every fompus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Carol is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every timpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Is Carol a kerpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a felpus, so Carol is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a fompus, so Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus."], "answer": "Carol is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "rorpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "fompus", "boompus", "worpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "impus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 16], [0, 17], [8, 9], [17, 16], [2, 10], [7, 9], [1, 15], [16, 17], [18, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Is Stella a shumpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a brimpus, so Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "storpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 12], [8, 14], [16, 11], [5, 14], [19, 16], [15, 11], [19, 15], [15, 13], [4, 17], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Carol is a zhorpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a impus. Is Carol a timpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a wumpus, so Carol is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yumpus, so Carol is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus."], "answer": "Carol is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "bompus", "wumpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "impus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [6, 12], [1, 13], [0, 14], [12, 10], [13, 9], [7, 10], [2, 13], [2, 9], [11, 9], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every terpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Is Fae a fompus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Fae is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "quimpus", "terpus", "bompus", "rempus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "fompus", "gerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [11, 9], [3, 12], [10, 12], [4, 10], [11, 12], [6, 9], [6, 10], [11, 10], [10, 11], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a impus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Sam is a boompus. Is Sam a zumpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a terpus, so Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Sam is a kerpus."], "answer": "Sam is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "dumpus", "terpus", "bompus", "yumpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "impus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [10, 11], [6, 10], [2, 10], [7, 9], [5, 9], [8, 9], [0, 9], [8, 10], [4, 11], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Is Davis a rempus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a bompus, so Davis is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus."], "answer": "Davis is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gorpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "fompus", "rempus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [15, 11], [1, 11], [4, 11], [13, 10], [12, 10], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Alex is a lempus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Is Alex a numpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lorpus, so Alex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a numpus, so Alex is a numpus."], "answer": "Alex is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "tumpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "timpus", "numpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "grimpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "jompus", "lempus", "terpus", "gorpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 17], [8, 17], [9, 15], [14, 11], [8, 16], [0, 14], [3, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Is Bob a timpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus."], "answer": "Bob is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "brimpus", "jelpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "impus", "rempus", "rorpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "boompus", "worpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [17, 15], [7, 14], [6, 11], [8, 11], [9, 11], [10, 12], [15, 16], [11, 17], [16, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Is Jack a dumpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a jompus, so Jack is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "worpus", "jompus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "impus", "jelpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 14], [7, 11], [1, 10], [3, 11], [8, 9], [5, 13], [14, 11], [4, 14], [3, 13], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every impus is a worpus. Is Alex a brimpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gerpus, so Alex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a worpus, so Alex is a worpus."], "answer": "Alex is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "gwompus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "impus", "rompus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "timpus", "jelpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [3, 11], [4, 11], [4, 10], [5, 11], [4, 12], [13, 14], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every fompus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Davis is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every impus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Is Davis a sterpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a boompus, so Davis is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus."], "answer": "Davis is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rorpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "boompus", "sterpus", "storpus", "worpus", "impus", "tumpus", "fompus", "chorpus", "bompus", "shumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [8, 11], [1, 14], [10, 14], [9, 13], [3, 12], [0, 14], [10, 11], [9, 14], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every storpus is a kerpus. Davis is a storpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Davis is a impus. Davis is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Is Davis a vumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a wumpus, so Davis is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gwompus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "impus", "jompus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [5, 15], [4, 15], [0, 15], [15, 11], [0, 12], [10, 12], [2, 12], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Alex is a timpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Is Alex a lempus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lempus, so Alex is a lempus."], "answer": "Alex is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "dumpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "tumpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "rempus", "terpus", "timpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [0, 12], [3, 11], [3, 13], [8, 13], [4, 12], [7, 12], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rompus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Is Bob a tumpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a kerpus, so Bob is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "bompus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [8, 9], [3, 9], [3, 10], [7, 11], [4, 9], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a impus. Is Sam a tumpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a wumpus, so Sam is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a impus, so Sam is a impus.", "Every impus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "dumpus", "wumpus", "impus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "boompus", "bompus", "numpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "terpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 19], [18, 9], [6, 12], [4, 12], [3, 15], [1, 11], [2, 19], [7, 17], [19, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Carol is a storpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Is Carol a grimpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a impus.", "Every impus is a lorpus, so Carol is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a brimpus, so Carol is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus."], "answer": "Carol is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "impus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "grimpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "storpus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "kerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [4, 11], [0, 10], [6, 13], [1, 17], [7, 13], [8, 15], [14, 11], [15, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Is Gabriel a yumpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "worpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "chorpus", "bompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [3, 17], [16, 9], [5, 9], [9, 14], [4, 9], [14, 10], [11, 17], [14, 17], [3, 14], [10, 12], [10, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every boompus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Wren is a felpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Is Wren a timpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a tumpus, so Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus."], "answer": "Wren is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "gorpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "gerpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [0, 9], [3, 12], [4, 15], [3, 13], [14, 13], [10, 9], [10, 12], [5, 14], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Oliver is a impus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a hilpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gorpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "impus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [4, 10], [5, 14], [6, 15], [2, 10], [10, 15], [0, 14], [7, 9], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every jompus is a impus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Tom is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Is Tom a terpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus."], "answer": "Tom is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "gorpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "impus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [4, 12], [15, 9], [7, 10], [1, 13], [14, 13], [0, 15], [2, 12], [8, 14], [14, 11], [6, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Carol is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Carol is a felpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Is Carol a dumpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lempus, so Carol is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus."], "answer": "Carol is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "worpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "storpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "rempus", "dumpus", "felpus", "rompus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 14], [0, 15], [10, 9], [0, 13], [11, 16], [16, 15], [5, 10], [16, 12], [4, 12], [8, 16], [1, 9], [3, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rompus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Max is a chorpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Is Max a timpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rompus, so Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a bompus, so Max is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus."], "answer": "Max is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "sterpus", "rompus", "bompus", "rorpus", "timpus", "fompus", "jompus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "yimpus", "impus", "chorpus", "lempus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [2, 11], [16, 9], [13, 11], [12, 16], [1, 14], [0, 15], [16, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every timpus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Oliver is a rempus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Oliver is a impus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Is Oliver a numpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a jelpus, so Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "terpus", "jelpus", "jompus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "impus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [12, 10], [12, 14], [0, 10], [15, 14], [0, 13], [1, 13], [5, 10], [15, 12], [2, 13], [1, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Is Alex a yumpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Alex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "numpus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "impus", "bompus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [7, 9], [7, 10], [3, 9], [5, 11], [9, 10], [2, 9], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every lempus is a terpus. Alex is a rempus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Is Alex a rempus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a lempus, so Alex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus."], "answer": "Alex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "rompus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "terpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "hilpus", "bompus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [2, 13], [10, 11], [12, 9], [2, 11], [5, 10], [0, 11], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Is Alex a timpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a worpus, so Alex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gorpus, so Alex is a gorpus."], "answer": "Alex is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "dumpus", "impus", "worpus", "jelpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "gwompus", "felpus", "numpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [16, 11], [5, 13], [3, 10], [15, 9], [13, 14], [6, 14], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Is Eva a felpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a bompus, so Eva is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lempus, so Eva is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Eva is a chorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "tumpus", "bompus", "lempus", "numpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "rompus", "fompus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "rempus", "felpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [14, 11], [15, 12], [10, 13], [5, 10], [1, 12], [9, 11], [10, 15], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every numpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Is Rex a jompus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus."], "answer": "Rex is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "felpus", "rempus", "storpus", "fompus", "jompus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "numpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 16], [11, 9], [16, 11], [14, 11], [7, 11], [12, 11], [10, 11], [16, 14], [17, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a storpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a impus. Polly is a impus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Is Polly a vumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yumpus", "lempus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "bompus", "boompus", "impus", "gorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [8, 11], [4, 12], [5, 11], [3, 12], [9, 10], [12, 9], [8, 9], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Is Stella a numpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rompus, so Stella is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus."], "answer": "Stella is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "brimpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "worpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "rempus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "zhorpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [2, 10], [4, 14], [10, 12], [12, 10], [3, 13], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Alex is a vumpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Is Alex a rorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a tumpus, so Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a jompus, so Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "bompus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [4, 10], [8, 10], [7, 10], [9, 11], [7, 11], [0, 9], [11, 10], [4, 11], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Wren is a rompus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a impus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Is Wren a hilpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus."], "answer": "Wren is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "boompus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "impus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [5, 11], [11, 10], [9, 11], [4, 11], [0, 10], [10, 9], [4, 10], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Is Stella a yumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a brimpus, so Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "gorpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "numpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [9, 11], [4, 10], [4, 9], [3, 11], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Bob is a gorpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Is Bob a lorpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "jelpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "terpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [4, 11], [9, 10], [8, 11], [0, 9], [9, 11], [5, 10], [2, 9], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rempus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Is Davis a shumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rempus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [3, 12], [9, 12], [4, 12], [11, 10], [5, 11], [2, 9], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Is Jack a zumpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "bompus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "rompus", "yerpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [8, 13], [5, 14], [14, 13], [6, 12], [5, 12], [7, 11], [5, 9], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Bob is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Is Bob a grimpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a brimpus, so Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a quimpus, so Bob is a quimpus."], "answer": "Bob is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "timpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "storpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [8, 13], [11, 14], [16, 9], [10, 17], [0, 14], [7, 13], [18, 10], [3, 18], [3, 15], [1, 11], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Max is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Max is a impus. Every lorpus is a impus. Is Max a scrompus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rompus, so Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gorpus, so Max is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus."], "answer": "Max is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "tumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "bompus", "felpus", "fompus", "lempus", "yimpus", "worpus", "terpus", "impus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [0, 16], [11, 9], [7, 15], [6, 16], [13, 9], [11, 15], [17, 12], [12, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Is Fae a dumpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "vumpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "rempus", "impus", "felpus", "boompus", "fompus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [5, 11], [4, 11], [6, 12], [2, 12], [2, 9], [4, 9], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Tom is a felpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Is Tom a brimpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a scrompus, so Tom is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gerpus, so Tom is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "tumpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "storpus", "boompus", "rompus", "felpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [1, 13], [13, 11], [14, 12], [13, 9], [9, 11], [8, 11], [2, 10], [5, 12], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Stella is a jompus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Stella is a timpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Is Stella a boompus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zhorpus, so Stella is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Stella is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rempus, so Stella is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus."], "answer": "Stella is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "rempus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "jompus", "fompus", "timpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 16], [4, 11], [11, 12], [11, 10], [11, 17], [9, 17], [11, 16], [0, 14], [6, 11], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every terpus is a jompus. Is Carol a zumpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Carol is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a brimpus, so Carol is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a impus, so Carol is a impus."], "answer": "Carol is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "wumpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "impus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "lempus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [2, 9], [14, 13], [8, 13], [1, 14], [9, 11], [13, 14], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Is Jack a terpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a tumpus, so Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a storpus, so Jack is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a terpus, so Jack is a terpus."], "answer": "Jack is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jelpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "yumpus", "terpus", "gwompus", "timpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "numpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 17], [18, 14], [6, 16], [8, 14], [11, 16], [5, 17], [9, 10], [10, 11], [1, 17], [7, 16], [11, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every fompus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Wren is a fompus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Is Wren a yerpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "rorpus", "zumpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [7, 11], [8, 13], [7, 13], [1, 9], [4, 9], [12, 13], [0, 12], [13, 9], [6, 11], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every fompus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Is Eva a zumpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "rorpus", "fompus", "terpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "impus", "bompus", "zumpus", "jompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 15], [5, 15], [6, 14], [3, 15], [1, 10], [1, 16], [14, 16], [12, 13], [8, 16], [4, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every worpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Oliver is a bompus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Is Oliver a hilpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "worpus", "numpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "jompus", "felpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "rorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 15], [1, 16], [9, 15], [18, 12], [7, 13], [15, 9], [12, 14], [5, 17], [0, 17], [10, 14], [14, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Fae is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Fae is a boompus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Fae is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Is Fae a tumpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rempus, so Fae is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yumpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "impus", "lempus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "boompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 16], [18, 9], [9, 15], [18, 17], [0, 13], [8, 14], [0, 15], [16, 10], [5, 14], [0, 10], [17, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Is Gabriel a chorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a wumpus, so Gabriel is a wumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "impus", "gerpus", "jompus", "lempus", "wumpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [9, 11], [2, 11], [5, 9], [7, 11], [4, 14], [13, 12], [13, 10], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a impus. Sally is a storpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Is Sally a yerpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a yimpus, so Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus."], "answer": "Sally is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jelpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [8, 11], [0, 9], [11, 12], [9, 12], [6, 12], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every impus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Stella is a dumpus. Every fompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Is Stella a dumpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Stella is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Stella is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Stella is a impus."], "answer": "Stella is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "zumpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "impus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [0, 13], [1, 13], [5, 10], [11, 13], [12, 11], [5, 9], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every bompus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Wren is a yerpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Is Wren a yerpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus."], "answer": "Wren is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "dumpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "storpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "impus", "boompus", "rompus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [12, 15], [15, 17], [6, 15], [16, 13], [0, 14], [4, 9], [8, 11], [9, 14], [5, 17], [1, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every storpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every storpus is a impus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Is Sam a yimpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a impus, so Sam is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "storpus", "impus", "jompus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "worpus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [3, 15], [8, 11], [2, 10], [9, 10], [7, 15], [4, 15], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Rex is a worpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Rex is a sterpus. Is Rex a vumpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a vumpus, so Rex is a vumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "dumpus", "shumpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "numpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [1, 13], [6, 12], [2, 10], [5, 11], [0, 10], [9, 11], [0, 9], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every worpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Gabriel is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Gabriel is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Is Gabriel a storpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "gwompus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "felpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [6, 13], [11, 10], [0, 9], [0, 11], [1, 9], [8, 12], [12, 14], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Alex is a fompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Is Alex a zumpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rorpus, so Alex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "lempus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [4, 12], [2, 10], [0, 12], [11, 12], [8, 12], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Is Sally a vumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a tumpus, so Sally is a tumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "worpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [7, 11], [12, 10], [5, 13], [9, 10], [10, 11], [7, 10], [4, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rempus is a worpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a boompus. Is Max a worpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus."], "answer": "Max is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "hilpus", "zumpus", "impus", "kerpus", "rempus", "numpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "worpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "lempus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [1, 15], [3, 14], [5, 12], [5, 9], [9, 11], [4, 12], [8, 10], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Wren is a brimpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Is Wren a boompus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yumpus, so Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus."], "answer": "Wren is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "rompus", "hilpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 18], [14, 11], [3, 10], [9, 13], [18, 16], [15, 9], [10, 14], [0, 15], [9, 10], [16, 11], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Max is a yumpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Is Max a rorpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rompus, so Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gorpus, so Max is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus."], "answer": "Max is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "quimpus", "rompus", "boompus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "fompus", "storpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [9, 12], [4, 10], [2, 11], [1, 12], [1, 11], [2, 9], [10, 12], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Is Max a felpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus."], "answer": "Max is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "yumpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "felpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "numpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [1, 9], [7, 18], [14, 17], [8, 12], [11, 10], [18, 11], [1, 14], [13, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Is Stella a terpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a scrompus, so Stella is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a storpus, so Stella is a storpus."], "answer": "Stella is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "scrompus", "storpus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "rompus", "fompus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [11, 12], [12, 14], [5, 11], [11, 13], [13, 11], [6, 14], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Is Wren a quimpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a worpus, so Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus."], "answer": "Wren is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "vumpus", "timpus", "worpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "impus", "brimpus", "lempus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [12, 13], [4, 12], [7, 11], [5, 9], [6, 13], [3, 14], [14, 11], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Is Alex a rorpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a worpus, so Alex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "felpus", "rompus", "worpus", "impus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "bompus", "fompus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 13], [5, 12], [9, 12], [2, 12], [10, 9], [8, 9], [4, 10], [4, 13], [11, 10], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lempus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Is Max a felpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rompus, so Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus."], "answer": "Max is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "lempus", "yimpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [2, 12], [11, 12], [14, 12], [11, 10], [3, 9], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a numpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Is Rex a kerpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a timpus, so Rex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "bompus", "terpus", "timpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [4, 10], [11, 13], [9, 13], [12, 9], [1, 13], [8, 12], [7, 11], [2, 9], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Is Davis a rompus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a scrompus, so Davis is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a impus, so Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus."], "answer": "Davis is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "chorpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "impus", "rompus", "felpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "rempus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [15, 9], [8, 13], [7, 13], [14, 9], [13, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Is Stella a vumpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Stella is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a sterpus, so Stella is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "wumpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "terpus", "numpus", "bompus", "yerpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 16], [5, 9], [7, 11], [9, 17], [2, 14], [11, 14], [15, 17], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Is Max a grimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yumpus, so Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a grimpus, so Max is a grimpus."], "answer": "Max is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "dumpus", "rempus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "terpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [18, 15], [8, 15], [5, 18], [6, 17], [17, 11], [7, 17], [14, 9], [5, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Is Davis a numpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "terpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "fompus", "bompus", "vumpus", "numpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [7, 11], [9, 11], [7, 10], [5, 10], [5, 9], [4, 10], [7, 9], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every bompus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Wren is a rompus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Is Wren a rompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "bompus", "sterpus", "numpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "boompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [7, 12], [10, 11], [9, 10], [11, 12], [11, 10], [2, 10], [1, 9], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Is Rex a kerpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus."], "answer": "Rex is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "fompus", "wumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 13], [10, 14], [16, 11], [1, 14], [1, 13], [1, 16], [14, 18], [8, 10], [19, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rempus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Is Tom a brimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus."], "answer": "Tom is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rempus", "grimpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "impus", "wumpus", "boompus", "gorpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [16, 13], [9, 16], [11, 17], [6, 16], [16, 12], [2, 15], [2, 9], [4, 12], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rempus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Is Carol a quimpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a bompus, so Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zhorpus, so Carol is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a quimpus, so Carol is a quimpus."], "answer": "Carol is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "rompus", "sterpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "timpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [4, 9], [11, 9], [1, 11], [8, 11], [7, 11], [3, 11], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every impus is a worpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Sally is a bompus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Is Sally a gwompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rorpus, so Sally is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus."], "answer": "Sally is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jompus", "zumpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "terpus", "felpus", "worpus", "impus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 14], [11, 9], [4, 10], [15, 12], [1, 12], [11, 15], [10, 9], [15, 14], [13, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every numpus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Is Max a kerpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Max is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lorpus, so Max is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus."], "answer": "Max is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 11], [1, 16], [2, 16], [10, 16], [10, 14], [3, 14], [2, 10], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Sam is a scrompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Sam is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Is Sam a yimpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a numpus, so Sam is a numpus."], "answer": "Sam is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "rempus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [12, 13], [1, 11], [0, 13], [2, 12], [5, 13], [5, 10], [5, 12], [0, 11], [5, 9], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Is Bob a numpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "yerpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "terpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "jelpus", "impus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 18], [19, 11], [8, 11], [7, 12], [17, 9], [1, 14], [16, 11], [1, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rempus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Is Wren a tumpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a worpus, so Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "dumpus", "grimpus", "numpus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "felpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [1, 15], [12, 13], [8, 9], [4, 12], [9, 10], [8, 12], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Gabriel is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every worpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Is Gabriel a brimpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a sterpus, so Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "lorpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [1, 11], [7, 11], [2, 9], [7, 13], [2, 10], [11, 9], [7, 10], [0, 12], [2, 13], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Jack is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Is Jack a zhorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "gorpus", "boompus", "numpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "worpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [16, 14], [2, 16], [3, 11], [12, 16], [2, 13], [0, 12], [16, 9], [16, 15], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every felpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Sally is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Is Sally a dumpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yimpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "impus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [3, 9], [7, 10], [7, 9], [5, 9], [6, 10], [0, 11], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a sterpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Is Rex a kerpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a tumpus, so Rex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a quimpus, so Rex is a quimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "impus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "lempus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [9, 13], [7, 14], [2, 12], [7, 10], [8, 13], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every storpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Is Bob a bompus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus.", "Every impus is a boompus, so Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus."], "answer": "Bob is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "zhorpus", "impus", "boompus", "numpus", "bompus", "storpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [7, 11], [4, 10], [11, 9], [8, 11], [8, 10], [3, 9], [8, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Gabriel is a numpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Is Gabriel a impus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rorpus, so Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "wumpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "impus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "fompus", "timpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [8, 9], [10, 11], [11, 10], [7, 11], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Is Polly a storpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a quimpus, so Polly is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a felpus, so Polly is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yumpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "felpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "storpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [4, 10], [13, 9], [11, 12], [7, 12], [10, 11], [12, 13], [2, 10], [7, 10], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Sally is a lempus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Is Sally a jompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Sally is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a boompus, so Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus."], "answer": "Sally is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yumpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "boompus", "jompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "fompus", "numpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [19, 17], [1, 11], [13, 11], [7, 14], [6, 10], [9, 12], [3, 19], [7, 15], [0, 19], [9, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every timpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Polly is a timpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Is Polly a hilpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a worpus, so Polly is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a jelpus, so Polly is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a hilpus, so Polly is a hilpus."], "answer": "Polly is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "lempus", "worpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "terpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [11, 9], [12, 13], [15, 14], [14, 12], [10, 16], [4, 16], [0, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Max is a timpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Max is a shumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Is Max a worpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Max is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a terpus, so Max is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus."], "answer": "Max is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "lempus", "lorpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "kerpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [4, 10], [1, 10], [0, 11], [0, 9], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Stella is a terpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Is Stella a boompus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a boompus, so Stella is a boompus."], "answer": "Stella is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "fompus", "bompus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "scrompus", "rompus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "numpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [15, 17], [13, 17], [3, 9], [4, 10], [15, 9], [14, 15], [8, 15], [18, 11], [14, 11], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Carol is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Carol is a worpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Is Carol a kerpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gerpus, so Carol is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a quimpus, so Carol is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus."], "answer": "Carol is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "terpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "tumpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [5, 11], [1, 14], [16, 13], [1, 13], [8, 10], [0, 16], [0, 10], [16, 12], [5, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every impus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Is Bob a yerpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "shumpus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "impus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [5, 11], [9, 11], [4, 11], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Is Davis a terpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gwompus, so Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a fompus, so Davis is a fompus."], "answer": "Davis is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "chorpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "timpus", "fompus", "boompus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [9, 12], [11, 15], [1, 11], [10, 11], [14, 17], [7, 9], [5, 12], [9, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every bompus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Is Sam a gerpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rompus, so Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus."], "answer": "Sam is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "bompus", "gorpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "fompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 9], [10, 11], [13, 10], [11, 13], [12, 14], [1, 13], [2, 9], [8, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rempus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Sam is a yimpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Is Sam a yimpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a wumpus, so Sam is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a hilpus, so Sam is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "jelpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "lempus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "impus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [7, 18], [18, 9], [1, 17], [4, 15], [0, 17], [16, 15], [6, 12], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every terpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Is Tom a quimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gwompus, so Tom is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a quimpus, so Tom is a quimpus."], "answer": "Tom is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "terpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "storpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "timpus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "impus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [6, 19], [6, 11], [16, 10], [11, 9], [9, 13], [17, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a rompus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Is Alex a brimpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gwompus, so Alex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus."], "answer": "Alex is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "vumpus", "zumpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "rempus", "fompus", "lempus", "kerpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [12, 9], [1, 12], [6, 9], [3, 11], [6, 11], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jompus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a worpus. Rex is a terpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Is Rex a yimpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rempus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "jompus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [5, 9], [1, 12], [4, 14], [2, 10], [8, 12], [0, 14], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Is Polly a worpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Polly is a hilpus."], "answer": "Polly is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "dumpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "numpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "rompus", "terpus", "worpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 15], [9, 14], [6, 15], [2, 16], [13, 16], [13, 12], [8, 14], [3, 13], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every felpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Carol is a lempus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Is Carol a jelpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a numpus, so Carol is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus."], "answer": "Carol is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "chorpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "worpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "felpus", "gerpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [1, 11], [7, 9], [6, 11], [5, 10], [11, 10], [6, 9], [10, 9], [9, 11], [6, 10], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Eva is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Is Eva a tumpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a bompus, so Eva is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus."], "answer": "Eva is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "rompus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "storpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "tumpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [4, 9], [6, 13], [3, 9], [8, 11], [13, 12], [0, 13], [13, 11], [9, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Is Sally a storpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gorpus, so Sally is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus."], "answer": "Sally is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "terpus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "storpus", "rorpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "impus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "fompus", "felpus", "numpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 14], [13, 12], [6, 17], [15, 14], [7, 9], [13, 16], [6, 11], [8, 17], [8, 12], [2, 15], [18, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Fae is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Is Fae a impus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a scrompus, so Fae is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gorpus, so Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus."], "answer": "Fae is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "dumpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "impus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [15, 17], [4, 14], [17, 13], [7, 16], [15, 16], [14, 12], [0, 15], [5, 17], [12, 10], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Sam is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Sam is a worpus. Is Sam a jelpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gerpus, so Sam is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a scrompus, so Sam is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus."], "answer": "Sam is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "worpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [4, 10], [5, 10], [6, 10], [3, 11], [4, 9], [0, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a quimpus. Alex is a brimpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Alex is a quimpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Is Alex a bompus or a impus?", "steps": ["Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a jelpus, so Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus."], "answer": "Alex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "rompus", "fompus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "impus", "brimpus", "worpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 16], [0, 14], [9, 14], [15, 14], [6, 15], [9, 12], [6, 12], [0, 12], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Is Fae a vumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yerpus, so Fae is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gorpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "boompus", "rompus", "timpus", "zumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 16], [6, 17], [12, 9], [8, 12], [6, 19], [8, 14], [9, 11], [13, 18], [18, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rompus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Is Max a brimpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a vumpus, so Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus."], "answer": "Max is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "jompus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "quimpus", "rompus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [9, 10], [9, 11], [1, 11], [13, 11], [7, 10], [2, 12], [2, 10], [8, 9], [5, 12], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Bob is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Is Bob a gerpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "lorpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [0, 12], [7, 12], [6, 9], [8, 10], [2, 9], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every numpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Gabriel is a lempus. Is Gabriel a scrompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "numpus", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "impus", "zumpus", "boompus", "storpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [5, 9], [3, 9], [7, 12], [12, 9], [0, 12], [3, 10], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Jack is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a rompus. Is Jack a terpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a terpus, so Jack is a terpus."], "answer": "Jack is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "quimpus", "lempus", "felpus", "jelpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "hilpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [7, 9], [11, 16], [10, 17], [8, 16], [15, 17], [14, 12], [16, 10], [2, 10], [0, 16], [8, 14], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every terpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Max is a hilpus. Is Max a hilpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Max is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a bompus, so Max is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a vumpus, so Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a tumpus, so Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus."], "answer": "Max is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "terpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [10, 11], [2, 12], [2, 11], [11, 12], [0, 9], [5, 12], [3, 12], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Is Gabriel a quimpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "dumpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "storpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 14], [10, 9], [17, 14], [10, 13], [10, 17], [1, 15], [11, 14], [3, 11], [14, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Eva is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Is Eva a lempus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus."], "answer": "Eva is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "gerpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [2, 10], [12, 11], [7, 10], [0, 13], [8, 13], [6, 11], [12, 10], [4, 12], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every jelpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Is Rex a grimpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a quimpus, so Rex is a quimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rompus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [14, 12], [5, 17], [7, 17], [6, 12], [10, 17], [16, 13], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Tom is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Is Tom a yimpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a quimpus, so Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a sterpus, so Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "bompus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [5, 9], [0, 11], [7, 10], [11, 12], [13, 9], [9, 13], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every bompus is a felpus. Stella is a yerpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Stella is a lempus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Is Stella a grimpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a felpus, so Stella is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus."], "answer": "Stella is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "jompus", "timpus", "wumpus", "felpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 16], [19, 18], [14, 12], [11, 14], [0, 13], [0, 10], [8, 15], [11, 18], [18, 19], [17, 19], [14, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Fae is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Is Fae a worpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus."], "answer": "Fae is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gerpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "numpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 18], [12, 15], [12, 14], [16, 13], [0, 18], [4, 15], [12, 16], [6, 10], [5, 18], [15, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Stella is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Stella is a gerpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Stella is a timpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Is Stella a felpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a hilpus, so Stella is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jompus, so Stella is a jompus."], "answer": "Stella is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "dumpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "timpus", "brimpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [15, 13], [17, 13], [15, 9], [14, 11], [0, 16], [10, 13], [12, 15], [0, 11], [8, 16], [3, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every jompus is a terpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Oliver is a rempus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Is Oliver a storpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rompus, so Oliver is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "jompus", "rompus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "numpus", "terpus", "boompus", "yumpus", "storpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [11, 17], [7, 13], [2, 11], [11, 13], [6, 15], [6, 9], [0, 10], [16, 13], [1, 12], [7, 12], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every impus is a boompus. Rex is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Is Rex a hilpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a wumpus, so Rex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus."], "answer": "Rex is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "worpus", "fompus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "rompus", "tumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [14, 9], [5, 10], [4, 10], [5, 12], [14, 11], [0, 10], [14, 10], [4, 12], [8, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a fompus. Is Sally a kerpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "bompus", "gerpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "jompus", "timpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [4, 12], [8, 15], [16, 17], [6, 11], [12, 18], [9, 10], [5, 14], [8, 11], [16, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Is Fae a dumpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Fae is a grimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "felpus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "rompus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "dumpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "storpus", "jelpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [7, 18], [9, 16], [16, 15], [6, 16], [16, 11], [5, 13], [5, 14], [2, 16], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Alex is a vumpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Is Alex a chorpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gwompus, so Alex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a chorpus, so Alex is a chorpus."], "answer": "Alex is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jelpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "terpus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "worpus", "fompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [10, 11], [5, 13], [12, 13], [8, 11], [13, 12], [8, 10], [3, 11], [5, 9], [1, 10], [0, 13], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Is Rex a terpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a tumpus, so Rex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus."], "answer": "Rex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "timpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "jelpus", "impus", "yimpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [6, 9], [7, 9], [13, 10], [2, 11], [6, 13], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every impus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Is Tom a wumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a dumpus, so Tom is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus."], "answer": "Tom is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "vumpus", "impus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [7, 13], [10, 14], [4, 13], [2, 11], [1, 11], [1, 14], [11, 14], [7, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every timpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Wren is a timpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Is Wren a timpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rompus, so Wren is a rompus."], "answer": "Wren is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "lorpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "storpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "impus", "boompus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [6, 16], [0, 11], [16, 13], [6, 11], [5, 10], [2, 12], [15, 10], [11, 14], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Sally is a timpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Is Sally a rorpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a dumpus, so Sally is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gerpus", "felpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "storpus", "tumpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [0, 9], [2, 14], [10, 13], [8, 11], [3, 10], [11, 13], [7, 13], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Davis is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Is Davis a chorpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a fompus, so Davis is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus."], "answer": "Davis is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "yerpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "chorpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "terpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 14], [3, 10], [4, 11], [5, 16], [9, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Gabriel is a storpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Is Gabriel a worpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "lempus", "boompus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "worpus", "impus", "storpus", "numpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [11, 14], [9, 11], [15, 10], [8, 13], [9, 14], [12, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Eva is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Is Eva a sterpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a lempus, so Eva is a lempus."], "answer": "Eva is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "vumpus", "rempus", "rorpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "gerpus", "felpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 10], [9, 16], [1, 15], [9, 12], [2, 11], [1, 12], [8, 11], [0, 10], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Bob is a gerpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Bob is a brimpus. Bob is a timpus. Is Bob a rorpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a quimpus, so Bob is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus."], "answer": "Bob is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "jompus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 13], [13, 10], [3, 13], [11, 9], [0, 10], [4, 9], [0, 11], [5, 12], [0, 12], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rompus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Stella is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Stella is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Is Stella a gwompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a rompus, so Stella is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a boompus, so Stella is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zhorpus, so Stella is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Stella is a yerpus."], "answer": "Stella is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "grimpus", "rompus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "felpus", "kerpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "terpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [19, 12], [0, 19], [14, 11], [19, 14], [0, 11], [15, 16], [4, 14], [14, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a fompus. Polly is a rompus. Every felpus is a impus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Is Polly a fompus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a timpus, so Polly is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a fompus, so Polly is a fompus."], "answer": "Polly is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "chorpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "timpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "lempus", "felpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "worpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "impus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [0, 11], [3, 9], [3, 18], [8, 14], [9, 17], [2, 14], [6, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Is Bob a kerpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a terpus, so Bob is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "lempus", "hilpus", "numpus", "terpus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 14], [3, 11], [13, 15], [7, 14], [7, 13], [1, 14], [15, 9], [6, 15], [9, 11], [1, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every impus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Polly is a timpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Is Polly a chorpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a impus.", "Every impus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a tumpus, so Polly is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a grimpus, so Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a chorpus, so Polly is a chorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "impus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "worpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "jelpus", "lempus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [12, 10], [14, 17], [1, 12], [2, 9], [3, 14], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Is Tom a zhorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a zhorpus, so Tom is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "tumpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "zumpus", "impus", "rorpus", "worpus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 14], [6, 14], [5, 14], [10, 14], [14, 12], [14, 15], [15, 12], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every felpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Sam is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Is Sam a tumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a felpus, so Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "grimpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [0, 10], [9, 12], [9, 10], [11, 12], [10, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Is Bob a boompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a dumpus, so Bob is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "terpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "boompus", "bompus", "jompus", "kerpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [5, 10], [12, 10], [13, 10], [6, 9], [3, 10], [10, 12], [2, 13], [7, 13], [5, 12], [8, 10], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Is Wren a impus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a impus, so Wren is a impus."], "answer": "Wren is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "storpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "impus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "rempus", "jompus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [17, 9], [9, 10], [12, 18], [11, 16], [1, 14], [10, 13], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every impus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Carol is a yumpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Is Carol a shumpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a brimpus, so Carol is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a impus, so Carol is a impus.", "Every impus is a rorpus, so Carol is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "felpus", "brimpus", "impus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [6, 13], [3, 13], [8, 9], [7, 11], [2, 11], [4, 14], [5, 12], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Wren is a boompus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Is Wren a storpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yumpus, so Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "grimpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "jompus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "storpus", "boompus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [14, 17], [0, 16], [13, 10], [4, 16], [16, 11], [16, 10], [4, 15], [1, 17], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a lorpus. Gabriel is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Is Gabriel a bompus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lorpus, so Gabriel is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "vumpus", "felpus", "terpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "fompus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "storpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [6, 15], [0, 14], [11, 9], [14, 12], [1, 9], [12, 15], [10, 11], [6, 14], [14, 11], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Is Davis a jelpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus."], "answer": "Davis is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "bompus", "impus", "shumpus", "jompus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [11, 9], [13, 10], [4, 11], [10, 12], [8, 12], [16, 14], [9, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Is Sam a brimpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a vumpus, so Sam is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Sam is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "rempus", "vumpus", "storpus", "gorpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "felpus", "impus", "kerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 15], [13, 11], [3, 9], [12, 14], [3, 11], [5, 12], [9, 12], [10, 12], [5, 9], [11, 12], [2, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Sam is a rempus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Is Sam a gwompus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a sterpus, so Sam is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus."], "answer": "Sam is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "rompus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "boompus", "bompus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "terpus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [11, 13], [14, 16], [7, 11], [0, 11], [4, 9], [8, 11], [15, 12], [15, 9], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Oliver is a worpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a lempus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "vumpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [7, 12], [4, 12], [8, 13], [1, 11], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Sally is a sterpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Is Sally a scrompus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a tumpus, so Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "felpus", "timpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [5, 9], [10, 12], [6, 13], [3, 9], [0, 12], [6, 11], [2, 9], [2, 12], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Tom is a jompus. Every rempus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Is Tom a zumpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a wumpus, so Tom is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "zhorpus", "wumpus", "rempus", "impus", "zumpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "numpus", "jompus", "terpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 13], [14, 16], [6, 14], [19, 12], [8, 13], [14, 17], [13, 17], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every terpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Sally is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Is Sally a yerpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a scrompus, so Sally is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "numpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 15], [2, 9], [12, 11], [0, 12], [10, 12], [9, 15], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a impus. Alex is a bompus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Is Alex a kerpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus."], "answer": "Alex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "numpus", "brimpus", "impus", "yumpus", "rompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "timpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 15], [5, 14], [1, 10], [2, 10], [0, 14], [16, 13], [15, 13], [7, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every felpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Is Jack a impus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "hilpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "impus", "bompus", "wumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [14, 13], [8, 9], [7, 10], [8, 10], [7, 12], [1, 12], [11, 9], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Davis is a boompus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Is Davis a gwompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "shumpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [5, 12], [1, 9], [6, 9], [3, 12], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a wumpus. Sally is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Sally is a lempus. Is Sally a gerpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus."], "answer": "Sally is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "boompus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "wumpus", "fompus", "chorpus", "timpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "lempus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 14], [5, 10], [6, 9], [10, 9], [0, 10], [11, 12], [6, 12], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Is Rex a impus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a impus, so Rex is a impus."], "answer": "Rex is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "terpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "sterpus", "impus", "kerpus", "bompus", "storpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 15], [1, 10], [10, 9], [5, 10], [5, 12], [7, 12], [4, 15], [1, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every fompus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Bob is a terpus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Bob is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Is Bob a brimpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a brimpus, so Bob is a brimpus."], "answer": "Bob is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "fompus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "dumpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [0, 11], [10, 12], [2, 10], [9, 12], [11, 9], [13, 11], [12, 13], [7, 13], [1, 13], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Is Oliver a quimpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "jompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "impus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [3, 15], [9, 11], [8, 16], [15, 12], [11, 9], [12, 19], [7, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a rempus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Rex is a worpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every impus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Is Rex a chorpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rorpus", "rempus", "storpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "impus", "rompus", "brimpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [2, 13], [12, 10], [6, 10], [0, 10], [4, 10], [8, 13], [1, 13], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Is Davis a yimpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a vumpus, so Davis is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a kerpus, so Davis is a kerpus."], "answer": "Davis is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "impus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [2, 10], [4, 11], [6, 10], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Is Fae a rompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus."], "answer": "Fae is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "scrompus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "felpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "rompus", "bompus", "impus", "zumpus", "wumpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 15], [6, 16], [17, 11], [11, 19], [15, 18], [7, 18], [1, 18], [1, 9], [12, 16], [17, 18], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a terpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Is Bob a grimpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus."], "answer": "Bob is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rorpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "quimpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "yimpus", "worpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [4, 10], [7, 16], [18, 11], [1, 16], [3, 15], [2, 17], [12, 15], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every fompus is a impus. Every kerpus is a impus. Jack is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Jack is a lempus. Is Jack a storpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Jack is a impus.", "Every impus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a storpus, so Jack is a storpus."], "answer": "Jack is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "gerpus", "fompus", "impus", "numpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "lempus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [2, 12], [8, 9], [5, 10], [10, 18], [0, 13], [3, 9], [12, 15], [15, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a rompus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a rempus. Bob is a gwompus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Is Bob a worpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus."], "answer": "Bob is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "storpus", "rempus", "rompus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "worpus", "jompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 16], [11, 17], [0, 17], [16, 9], [14, 10], [10, 12], [9, 16], [3, 12], [15, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every jompus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Is Gabriel a scrompus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a tumpus, so Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rempus, so Gabriel is a rempus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "felpus", "worpus", "tumpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "fompus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "jompus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 18], [10, 9], [17, 12], [9, 16], [9, 10], [2, 15], [15, 11], [3, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every rompus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every impus is a hilpus. Max is a zumpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every impus is a worpus. Max is a zhorpus. Is Max a fompus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a hilpus, so Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus."], "answer": "Max is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rompus", "jompus", "impus", "hilpus", "fompus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 15], [0, 14], [10, 13], [7, 13], [12, 18], [5, 10], [13, 10], [16, 13], [1, 11], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Is Wren a kerpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus."], "answer": "Wren is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "tumpus", "grimpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "timpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 17], [7, 16], [15, 13], [12, 17], [4, 10], [4, 11], [12, 10], [16, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Rex is a impus. Every impus is a gorpus. Is Rex a lorpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a wumpus, so Rex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a kerpus, so Rex is a kerpus."], "answer": "Rex is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rempus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "impus", "fompus", "lorpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [5, 12], [4, 9], [6, 9], [9, 12], [2, 12], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Is Rex a chorpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "wumpus", "zhorpus", "rompus", "lempus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "bompus", "jompus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [3, 12], [2, 10], [12, 11], [13, 10], [10, 13], [10, 12], [4, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a gerpus. Oliver is a yimpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Oliver is a boompus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Is Oliver a tumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "numpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "storpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [0, 9], [1, 9], [6, 11], [6, 10], [0, 11], [3, 11], [1, 10], [1, 11], [8, 11], [4, 10], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a felpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Is Alex a rorpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a sterpus, so Alex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rorpus, so Alex is a rorpus."], "answer": "Alex is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "dumpus", "terpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "felpus", "bompus", "yumpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "lorpus", "lempus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 17], [17, 16], [8, 14], [1, 9], [13, 12], [5, 10], [10, 9], [16, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Is Sally a storpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus."], "answer": "Sally is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yumpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "fompus", "tumpus", "bompus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [5, 10], [10, 9], [5, 11], [7, 10], [3, 11], [6, 10], [8, 11], [1, 11], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a impus. Is Bob a numpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus.", "Every impus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus."], "answer": "Bob is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "chorpus", "lorpus", "impus", "rompus", "numpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 9], [14, 13], [17, 11], [17, 13], [1, 10], [15, 17], [10, 13], [9, 16], [18, 17], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Oliver is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Is Oliver a jompus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "hilpus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "rompus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "lempus", "terpus", "jompus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 15], [17, 9], [11, 9], [2, 14], [13, 12], [6, 16], [0, 13], [10, 11], [12, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Oliver is a storpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a yumpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a kerpus, so Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rompus", "numpus", "kerpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [7, 11], [3, 9], [5, 9], [5, 11], [0, 11], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Oliver is a storpus. Is Oliver a hilpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "quimpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "jompus", "boompus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [4, 9], [8, 12], [0, 12], [12, 10], [9, 10], [1, 10], [8, 11], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Is Tom a bompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a felpus, so Tom is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus."], "answer": "Tom is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "numpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "gwompus", "terpus", "gerpus", "bompus", "worpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [1, 11], [8, 10], [10, 9], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rempus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Is Oliver a quimpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "vumpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "boompus", "quimpus", "storpus", "rempus", "lorpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "worpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 17], [8, 13], [12, 10], [16, 12], [2, 15], [3, 15], [6, 9], [12, 16], [7, 15], [7, 10], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every storpus is a impus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Stella is a zumpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Is Stella a hilpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a felpus, so Stella is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a hilpus, so Stella is a hilpus."], "answer": "Stella is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "chorpus", "quimpus", "felpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "impus", "gerpus", "storpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [7, 10], [3, 10], [2, 11], [0, 12], [11, 9], [10, 12], [6, 10], [3, 9], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every bompus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Is Bob a kerpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rompus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [5, 14], [11, 13], [8, 9], [12, 9], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Is Sally a rompus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a fompus, so Sally is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus."], "answer": "Sally is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gwompus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "fompus", "jompus", "brimpus", "storpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [1, 14], [2, 12], [5, 10], [3, 10], [10, 12], [3, 14], [12, 15], [3, 15], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Jack is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Is Jack a zhorpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "rorpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [6, 14], [0, 12], [5, 11], [14, 9], [5, 16], [16, 12], [13, 11], [14, 17], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Bob is a brimpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Is Bob a bompus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a kerpus, so Bob is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus."], "answer": "Bob is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "felpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "bompus", "yerpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 14], [7, 11], [8, 10], [4, 14], [14, 9], [1, 12], [6, 9], [3, 12], [4, 13], [11, 16], [0, 12], [12, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Is Eva a gerpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a felpus, so Eva is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus."], "answer": "Eva is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "sterpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "felpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [15, 16], [14, 16], [6, 12], [3, 14], [4, 15], [7, 9], [2, 14], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Is Eva a worpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a zumpus, so Eva is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus."], "answer": "Eva is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "dumpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "timpus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "kerpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "shumpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 18], [11, 10], [3, 15], [4, 13], [3, 10], [17, 12], [10, 14], [3, 11], [18, 13], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Is Stella a timpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a fompus, so Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a rorpus, so Stella is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Stella is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a hilpus, so Stella is a hilpus."], "answer": "Stella is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "wumpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "brimpus", "felpus", "timpus", "impus", "sterpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [4, 9], [1, 9], [8, 12], [10, 11], [1, 11], [3, 9], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a jompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Stella is a tumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Is Stella a rompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a gerpus, so Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "fompus", "timpus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "quimpus", "lempus", "tumpus", "terpus", "worpus", "rompus", "rempus", "bompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [5, 13], [6, 10], [4, 9], [7, 10], [1, 13], [1, 14], [2, 11], [10, 15], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jompus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Is Fae a worpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a grimpus, so Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus."], "answer": "Fae is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "bompus", "jompus", "grimpus", "boompus", "worpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [3, 10], [4, 12], [9, 11], [5, 10], [3, 12], [5, 12], [9, 12], [1, 10], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a hilpus. Gabriel is a numpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Is Gabriel a zhorpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a sterpus, so Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "chorpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "terpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "worpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [0, 13], [10, 12], [1, 13], [6, 10], [9, 13], [3, 11], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Is Eva a jompus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Eva is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a kerpus, so Eva is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Eva is a felpus."], "answer": "Eva is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "wumpus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "jompus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "impus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "lempus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 18], [11, 12], [3, 12], [19, 12], [1, 19], [9, 15], [9, 16], [1, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every worpus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Is Eva a chorpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gerpus, so Eva is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus."], "answer": "Eva is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "worpus", "impus", "jompus", "gerpus", "numpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [1, 11], [7, 15], [7, 12], [6, 11], [4, 12], [12, 15], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every bompus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Is Gabriel a kerpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a bompus, so Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "lorpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "jompus", "impus", "lempus", "storpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [7, 12], [2, 11], [12, 9], [5, 10], [8, 9], [3, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every impus is a rempus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a impus. Is Tom a zumpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a sterpus, so Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus."], "answer": "Tom is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rompus", "sterpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "boompus", "bompus", "impus", "rempus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 15], [8, 9], [6, 12], [3, 14], [11, 14], [12, 9], [16, 9], [6, 16], [1, 13], [16, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Is Jack a rempus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Jack is a rempus."], "answer": "Jack is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "shumpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "bompus", "rempus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "numpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 9], [18, 16], [12, 15], [5, 13], [1, 18], [17, 9], [8, 18], [4, 9], [17, 14], [18, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Is Sally a terpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus."], "answer": "Sally is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "vumpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "lempus", "terpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "jompus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [5, 12], [9, 13], [15, 10], [15, 11], [3, 15], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every storpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Max is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Is Max a felpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a timpus, so Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus."], "answer": "Max is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "sterpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "storpus", "felpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [3, 13], [12, 9], [6, 10], [5, 11], [6, 13], [5, 13], [7, 13], [8, 11], [0, 13], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Wren is a quimpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a rompus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Is Wren a timpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yerpus, so Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lempus, so Wren is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus."], "answer": "Wren is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "bompus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "rempus", "rompus", "terpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [10, 12], [7, 9], [1, 9], [0, 11], [2, 10], [8, 11], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a felpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a felpus, so Oliver is a felpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "boompus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "felpus", "fompus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "impus", "storpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [7, 17], [3, 13], [1, 12], [3, 12], [14, 18], [8, 12], [11, 10], [8, 10], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Stella is a gerpus. Is Stella a rorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a brimpus, so Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gwompus, so Stella is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "numpus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "vumpus", "bompus", "timpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 16], [15, 12], [11, 10], [15, 14], [3, 11], [6, 15], [0, 11], [5, 13], [8, 13], [3, 15], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Sam is a lempus. Is Sam a gorpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a timpus, so Sam is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gorpus, so Sam is a gorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lorpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [0, 16], [2, 10], [16, 14], [9, 10], [6, 10], [15, 11], [2, 16], [16, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Alex is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Is Alex a bompus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus."], "answer": "Alex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "grimpus", "felpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "worpus", "boompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 15], [9, 15], [12, 10], [8, 13], [5, 9], [3, 12], [2, 13], [13, 14], [1, 11], [0, 11], [10, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Bob is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Is Bob a scrompus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a vumpus, so Bob is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus."], "answer": "Bob is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "bompus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "impus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "fompus", "quimpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 16], [0, 11], [6, 16], [1, 12], [17, 9], [6, 9], [10, 13], [12, 13], [2, 14], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Is Bob a shumpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a kerpus, so Bob is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gwompus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "storpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "jompus", "jelpus", "timpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [13, 11], [3, 16], [11, 14], [5, 12], [15, 14], [4, 12], [7, 12], [9, 13], [10, 12], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Is Davis a shumpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gwompus", "numpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [3, 11], [2, 12], [1, 10], [5, 11], [3, 10], [9, 10], [7, 11], [12, 10], [5, 10], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every terpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Sally is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Is Sally a yumpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "tumpus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [13, 10], [13, 14], [9, 13], [15, 13], [2, 11], [0, 10], [7, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Jack is a storpus. Is Jack a sterpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a hilpus, so Jack is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "rempus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "numpus", "lempus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [0, 9], [2, 13], [3, 9], [11, 10], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Is Davis a chorpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rempus, so Davis is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus."], "answer": "Davis is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "zhorpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "fompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [6, 12], [12, 11], [3, 9], [5, 11], [7, 10], [3, 10], [8, 10], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a grimpus. Davis is a bompus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Davis is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Is Davis a yumpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zhorpus, so Davis is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lempus", "zhorpus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "bompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [0, 9], [7, 12], [2, 12], [3, 11], [0, 12], [3, 10], [10, 11], [10, 9], [2, 11], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lempus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Is Jack a lempus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a wumpus, so Jack is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus."], "answer": "Jack is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "tumpus", "lorpus", "zhorpus", "wumpus", "lempus", "numpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "felpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [11, 9], [4, 9], [5, 12], [2, 12], [5, 9], [2, 9], [10, 9], [5, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Is Sally a yerpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a numpus, so Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yimpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "rempus", "bompus", "gorpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [18, 13], [13, 15], [17, 18], [11, 18], [9, 17], [2, 18], [7, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a lorpus. Sally is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Is Sally a quimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a dumpus, so Sally is a dumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "shumpus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "dumpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "worpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [5, 12], [5, 9], [3, 10], [10, 11], [4, 10], [0, 9], [2, 10], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rempus is a worpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Is Oliver a numpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "grimpus", "bompus", "worpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "felpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "numpus", "terpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [6, 12], [13, 12], [10, 13], [12, 11], [1, 9], [12, 10], [1, 11], [8, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Eva is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Is Eva a kerpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus."], "answer": "Eva is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "jelpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "timpus", "kerpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [5, 11], [2, 12], [0, 12], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Max is a rompus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Max is a vumpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Is Max a rompus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus."], "answer": "Max is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "timpus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "rompus", "rempus", "numpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [6, 9], [12, 10], [14, 9], [9, 13], [0, 9], [14, 11], [0, 12], [1, 14], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a timpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Is Stella a rempus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a timpus, so Stella is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rempus, so Stella is a rempus."], "answer": "Stella is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "yumpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "rempus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "impus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "jompus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "numpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 18], [15, 11], [12, 18], [2, 18], [17, 10], [1, 13], [13, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Is Sam a sterpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a timpus, so Sam is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a worpus, so Sam is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus."], "answer": "Sam is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "scrompus", "timpus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "terpus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "dumpus", "impus", "felpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 17], [12, 11], [11, 9], [12, 13], [17, 12], [3, 12], [8, 13], [17, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Is Jack a gerpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gwompus, so Jack is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a scrompus, so Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "wumpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "zumpus", "timpus", "impus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "worpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "rompus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 18], [17, 15], [14, 17], [8, 10], [8, 14], [15, 17], [4, 18], [7, 19], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Is Polly a lempus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a storpus, so Polly is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zhorpus, so Polly is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus."], "answer": "Polly is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yimpus", "kerpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "fompus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [12, 11], [2, 10], [10, 9], [7, 14], [1, 12], [3, 11], [8, 11], [10, 14], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Gabriel is a numpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Gabriel is a wumpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Is Gabriel a lempus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "vumpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "boompus", "dumpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "grimpus", "wumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [6, 11], [0, 15], [0, 14], [5, 15], [13, 9], [11, 13], [2, 13], [8, 12], [15, 14], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Is Oliver a shumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rorpus", "timpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [1, 16], [14, 15], [1, 14], [3, 11], [12, 15], [8, 14], [14, 12], [7, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Gabriel is a dumpus. Is Gabriel a rorpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "storpus", "boompus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "worpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 16], [19, 11], [2, 11], [2, 19], [16, 15], [2, 18], [19, 14], [4, 16], [3, 17], [0, 12], [15, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Bob is a lorpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Is Bob a lorpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a kerpus, so Bob is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a felpus, so Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus."], "answer": "Bob is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "storpus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "felpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [10, 11], [4, 12], [0, 9], [2, 9], [1, 11], [2, 10], [10, 9], [1, 12], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Is Sam a yerpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a worpus, so Sam is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a sterpus, so Sam is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Sam is a lempus."], "answer": "Sam is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "tumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "sterpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "gorpus", "felpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [11, 12], [8, 16], [15, 17], [16, 15], [12, 14], [16, 12], [9, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Tom is a lempus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Tom is a rempus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Is Tom a lorpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rompus, so Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a hilpus, so Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "vumpus", "kerpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [9, 13], [13, 10], [0, 12], [3, 9], [7, 13], [3, 13], [5, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a vumpus. Jack is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Jack is a worpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every impus is a numpus. Jack is a bompus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Is Jack a grimpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a impus, so Jack is a impus.", "Every impus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus."], "answer": "Jack is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "gwompus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "impus", "numpus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [11, 9], [3, 11], [7, 11], [8, 11], [0, 11], [0, 9], [6, 11], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every fompus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Fae is a brimpus. Fae is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Fae is a yimpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Is Fae a quimpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "jompus", "vumpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "terpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 15], [15, 10], [14, 12], [2, 10], [17, 9], [0, 16], [7, 9], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Is Davis a lorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Davis is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Davis is a lorpus."], "answer": "Davis is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "brimpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [4, 12], [3, 12], [12, 10], [8, 9], [9, 12], [6, 9], [3, 10], [11, 9], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a boompus. Jack is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Is Jack a lempus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "gorpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "boompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "impus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "rompus", "jompus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [4, 12], [7, 10], [10, 12], [7, 13], [1, 12], [1, 10], [6, 14], [0, 14], [3, 14], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Is Stella a kerpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a terpus, so Stella is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a kerpus, so Stella is a kerpus."], "answer": "Stella is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "rorpus", "chorpus", "terpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [7, 11], [9, 10], [7, 10], [7, 9], [8, 9], [3, 9], [4, 9], [6, 9], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Is Sam a lorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a wumpus, so Sam is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a scrompus, so Sam is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "yumpus", "wumpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "timpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [10, 9], [5, 10], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every storpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Fae is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Fae is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Is Fae a storpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus."], "answer": "Fae is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "kerpus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "terpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "lempus", "impus", "quimpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "storpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 15], [0, 10], [6, 11], [6, 16], [2, 14], [10, 14], [7, 14], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Stella is a scrompus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Stella is a gwompus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Is Stella a wumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a chorpus, so Stella is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Stella is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "yumpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "rempus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "terpus", "impus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 14], [10, 14], [3, 16], [7, 13], [17, 11], [0, 19], [15, 11], [16, 11], [0, 15], [5, 17], [6, 16], [19, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a rempus. Is Rex a sterpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a impus, so Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus."], "answer": "Rex is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "terpus", "yumpus", "impus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "numpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 16], [12, 15], [12, 14], [15, 13], [7, 13], [4, 9], [11, 12], [9, 14], [6, 16], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every numpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Is Carol a chorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a lempus, so Carol is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yumpus, so Carol is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Carol is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus."], "answer": "Carol is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "storpus", "lempus", "yumpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "timpus", "tumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [14, 17], [12, 14], [5, 16], [3, 16], [8, 17], [17, 14], [18, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every sterpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Is Alex a gorpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lorpus, so Alex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a terpus, so Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus."], "answer": "Alex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "sterpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 13], [3, 9], [5, 13], [11, 13], [1, 12], [15, 12], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Is Polly a timpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a impus.", "Every impus is a gwompus, so Polly is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a tumpus, so Polly is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus."], "answer": "Polly is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "impus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "timpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [14, 12], [10, 12], [11, 10], [12, 14], [6, 14], [12, 13], [12, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Is Tom a zumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jelpus, so Tom is a jelpus."], "answer": "Tom is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "timpus", "chorpus", "brimpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [1, 10], [8, 10], [3, 10], [2, 9], [10, 9], [6, 11], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every terpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Is Carol a lorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a impus, so Carol is a impus.", "Every impus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lorpus, so Carol is a lorpus."], "answer": "Carol is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "fompus", "terpus", "impus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "rempus", "dumpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "felpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 18], [15, 10], [7, 18], [14, 16], [8, 18], [1, 19], [17, 16], [14, 13], [2, 12], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every sterpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Is Carol a worpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gerpus, so Carol is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a fompus, so Carol is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus."], "answer": "Carol is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "sterpus", "gerpus", "terpus", "fompus", "rompus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "numpus", "storpus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 15], [14, 10], [7, 9], [6, 15], [4, 14], [12, 15], [15, 14], [14, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Bob is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Is Bob a rorpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "boompus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "numpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "impus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [14, 15], [4, 10], [12, 16], [11, 15], [11, 10], [0, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every timpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Eva is a yimpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Eva is a sterpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Is Eva a lorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yumpus, so Eva is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus."], "answer": "Eva is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "timpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "terpus", "lorpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [0, 9], [1, 10], [4, 10], [10, 14], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Carol is a impus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Is Carol a tumpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Carol is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Carol is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Carol is a kerpus."], "answer": "Carol is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "yimpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "gorpus", "rempus", "lempus", "vumpus", "boompus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 16], [11, 13], [13, 10], [2, 15], [14, 15], [8, 11], [3, 14], [1, 13], [9, 14], [0, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every bompus is a felpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Is Davis a quimpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "boompus", "gerpus", "lempus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "rompus", "yumpus", "storpus", "timpus", "fompus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [11, 9], [3, 16], [14, 16], [6, 13], [6, 17], [3, 14], [11, 10], [1, 10], [17, 13], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Is Wren a zumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a tumpus, so Wren is a tumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yumpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "rompus", "jelpus", "boompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 19], [17, 18], [17, 9], [18, 11], [19, 16], [17, 10], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Polly is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Polly is a felpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Is Polly a vumpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a rempus, so Polly is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yimpus, so Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "hilpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "jelpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [8, 12], [0, 13], [4, 12], [1, 13], [5, 11], [0, 10], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Tom is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Is Tom a sterpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "vumpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "worpus", "terpus", "felpus", "storpus", "dumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [11, 9], [6, 9], [0, 11], [4, 11], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Is Gabriel a jelpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "terpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "jelpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 13], [16, 13], [2, 12], [11, 9], [1, 17], [4, 9], [15, 10], [15, 18], [1, 10], [11, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Is Sally a dumpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a dumpus, so Sally is a dumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "numpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [7, 9], [12, 9], [4, 12], [12, 10], [5, 10], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Jack is a numpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Jack is a rompus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Is Jack a numpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus."], "answer": "Jack is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jelpus", "timpus", "worpus", "fompus", "boompus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "numpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "lempus", "dumpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 19], [9, 19], [14, 10], [15, 10], [0, 14], [4, 9], [15, 11], [6, 12], [0, 15], [10, 14], [9, 11], [11, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Rex is a timpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Is Rex a gorpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lorpus, so Rex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gorpus, so Rex is a gorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "numpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "bompus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "timpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [7, 11], [0, 10], [4, 10], [5, 14], [6, 11], [4, 11], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every fompus is a rempus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a bompus. Every impus is a rempus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a impus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Is Alex a bompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a quimpus, so Alex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Alex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus."], "answer": "Alex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "rompus", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "bompus", "terpus", "worpus", "impus", "fompus", "rempus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [4, 11], [9, 10], [3, 9], [1, 11], [11, 9], [8, 10], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Is Polly a vumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a scrompus, so Polly is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a quimpus, so Polly is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a bompus, so Polly is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "grimpus", "scrompus", "quimpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "terpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "hilpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [3, 12], [12, 11], [10, 9], [2, 12], [6, 11], [11, 9], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lempus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Is Eva a quimpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a numpus, so Eva is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Eva is a bompus."], "answer": "Eva is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lempus", "dumpus", "jompus", "numpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "impus", "fompus", "felpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 15], [15, 14], [2, 17], [15, 10], [9, 10], [8, 16], [16, 15], [8, 13], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every impus is a boompus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Alex is a yimpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Is Alex a bompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a boompus, so Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rorpus, so Alex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus."], "answer": "Alex is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "terpus", "impus", "boompus", "rorpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [11, 13], [11, 14], [14, 13], [15, 10], [2, 10], [3, 10], [0, 10], [11, 9], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a numpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Is Jack a gerpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a impus, so Jack is a impus.", "Every impus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus."], "answer": "Jack is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jelpus", "bompus", "impus", "shumpus", "numpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "fompus", "boompus", "timpus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 17], [17, 12], [1, 18], [14, 17], [10, 15], [3, 17], [12, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Is Bob a zumpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a boompus, so Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rorpus", "boompus", "fompus", "chorpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [2, 11], [8, 10], [7, 11], [4, 9], [6, 10], [7, 10], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every timpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every numpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Is Wren a terpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus."], "answer": "Wren is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yerpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "numpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "impus", "timpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [8, 14], [14, 10], [11, 14], [9, 12], [15, 16], [16, 9], [12, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a lorpus. Carol is a rompus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Carol is a storpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Is Carol a impus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lorpus, so Carol is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a felpus, so Carol is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a impus, so Carol is a impus."], "answer": "Carol is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "grimpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "impus", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "wumpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "storpus", "quimpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 16], [0, 10], [0, 17], [13, 16], [3, 19], [13, 15], [13, 10], [19, 18], [19, 15], [6, 10], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Is Bob a rempus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus."], "answer": "Bob is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gorpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "bompus", "felpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "jompus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 13], [14, 16], [14, 11], [15, 16], [14, 15], [11, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Jack is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Is Jack a grimpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Jack is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rempus, so Jack is a rempus."], "answer": "Jack is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "numpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "jelpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [11, 9], [3, 12], [4, 12], [7, 9], [0, 11], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every lempus is a impus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Is Bob a sterpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a felpus, so Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "scrompus", "felpus", "timpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "jompus", "lempus", "quimpus", "terpus", "impus", "gorpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [7, 10], [7, 11], [8, 10], [1, 10], [12, 9], [8, 9], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every bompus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Is Jack a chorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a sterpus, so Jack is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "scrompus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "timpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "jompus", "impus", "yimpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 15], [16, 11], [12, 9], [12, 15], [13, 12], [9, 10], [3, 11], [16, 9], [6, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Tom is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a chorpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a impus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Is Tom a yerpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rompus, so Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "jompus", "rompus", "storpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "impus", "quimpus", "boompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 13], [6, 10], [6, 9], [5, 12], [0, 10], [5, 10], [7, 9], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Is Oliver a rompus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "yerpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "impus", "felpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "boompus", "rompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 14], [7, 13], [8, 9], [8, 14], [11, 9], [7, 10], [7, 14], [5, 14], [9, 11], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every impus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a impus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every rempus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Is Carol a yerpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Carol is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a impus, so Carol is a impus.", "Every impus is a rompus, so Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a numpus, so Carol is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Carol is a rempus."], "answer": "Carol is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "lempus", "impus", "rompus", "numpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [3, 13], [5, 11], [3, 9], [11, 12], [10, 12], [5, 13], [5, 10], [7, 12], [6, 11], [4, 9], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rempus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Sally is a tumpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Is Sally a gwompus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a scrompus, so Sally is a scrompus."], "answer": "Sally is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yimpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "felpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "numpus", "bompus", "lempus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "boompus", "gwompus", "rempus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 14], [7, 9], [6, 12], [17, 12], [14, 15], [0, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every boompus is a rempus. Wren is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Is Wren a kerpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus."], "answer": "Wren is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "boompus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "fompus", "gorpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "gerpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 13], [12, 10], [4, 13], [15, 16], [13, 12], [13, 10], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a fompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Is Davis a felpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rorpus, so Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a wumpus, so Davis is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "impus", "yerpus", "jompus", "storpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 17], [13, 10], [8, 10], [16, 15], [10, 11], [14, 17], [15, 10], [1, 13], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Is Sam a terpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a wumpus, so Sam is a wumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "felpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "zhorpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [16, 9], [18, 11], [17, 15], [6, 15], [13, 17], [17, 19], [3, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Is Alex a zumpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a wumpus, so Alex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a boompus, so Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a numpus, so Alex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "grimpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "numpus", "dumpus", "rompus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "rorpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [8, 9], [12, 10], [16, 9], [17, 12], [6, 12], [11, 9], [9, 16], [18, 10], [2, 11], [9, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Is Rex a lempus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus."], "answer": "Rex is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "brimpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "storpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [9, 11], [8, 10], [1, 13], [7, 13], [6, 11], [2, 12], [13, 9], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Is Jack a tumpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Jack is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rompus, so Jack is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Jack is a lempus."], "answer": "Jack is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "sterpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "chorpus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "bompus", "fompus", "rorpus", "terpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [8, 11], [7, 11], [1, 9], [6, 11], [2, 9], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Davis is a yumpus. Davis is a terpus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Is Davis a timpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus."], "answer": "Davis is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gorpus", "jelpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "terpus", "kerpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [12, 11], [8, 10], [0, 10], [3, 11], [0, 9], [4, 11], [1, 9], [11, 9], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every felpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every wumpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Is Wren a hilpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a scrompus, so Wren is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a sterpus, so Wren is a sterpus."], "answer": "Wren is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yumpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "lorpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [13, 12], [10, 9], [16, 9], [19, 16], [2, 14], [2, 9], [9, 15], [4, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Fae is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Is Fae a shumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a jompus, so Fae is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus."], "answer": "Fae is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "yerpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "worpus", "zumpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [7, 9], [9, 10], [3, 10], [0, 11], [5, 9], [4, 11], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every fompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Polly is a impus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Is Polly a rompus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a hilpus, so Polly is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gerpus, so Polly is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a quimpus, so Polly is a quimpus."], "answer": "Polly is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "fompus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "bompus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "jelpus", "impus", "zumpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [2, 17], [7, 9], [5, 9], [19, 16], [0, 12], [6, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Is Davis a dumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a bompus, so Davis is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a kerpus, so Davis is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "scrompus", "quimpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "brimpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "jompus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [10, 18], [15, 9], [11, 19], [10, 9], [7, 18], [1, 15], [13, 9], [5, 10], [5, 16], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every storpus is a terpus. Every impus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Rex is a lempus. Every kerpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every impus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Is Rex a timpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jelpus, so Rex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a timpus, so Rex is a timpus."], "answer": "Rex is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "impus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "numpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [8, 12], [9, 11], [0, 10], [3, 10], [11, 9], [1, 11], [10, 12], [6, 10], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Jack is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Is Jack a tumpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "jompus", "boompus", "fompus", "timpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 14], [14, 9], [4, 11], [4, 9], [6, 14], [13, 9], [9, 11], [0, 14], [15, 10], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Wren is a lempus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Wren is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Is Wren a timpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a kerpus, so Wren is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a fompus, so Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus."], "answer": "Wren is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "shumpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "fompus", "hilpus", "numpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "timpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "storpus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [14, 9], [17, 19], [9, 11], [9, 19], [5, 12], [17, 18], [0, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a brimpus. Max is a jompus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Is Max a hilpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a vumpus, so Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a hilpus, so Max is a hilpus."], "answer": "Max is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "yimpus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "boompus", "jelpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [0, 11], [16, 15], [14, 13], [11, 12], [10, 13], [12, 9], [18, 14], [8, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jompus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a grimpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "wumpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "sterpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "terpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [10, 11], [10, 13], [13, 9], [6, 9], [2, 15], [3, 13], [15, 11], [5, 14], [4, 9], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Is Polly a zhorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rempus, so Polly is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "wumpus", "rempus", "brimpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "rompus", "bompus", "yumpus", "worpus", "lempus", "scrompus", "terpus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "zhorpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 15], [18, 11], [17, 14], [9, 13], [10, 17], [16, 17], [13, 12], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Gabriel is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Is Gabriel a gwompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "dumpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "fompus", "rompus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [9, 12], [10, 16], [13, 11], [4, 11], [8, 11], [2, 9], [16, 9], [16, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every boompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Is Rex a sterpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "lempus", "rompus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "storpus", "timpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [5, 10], [5, 13], [13, 16], [13, 14], [6, 10], [2, 15], [15, 14], [15, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every numpus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Fae is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every impus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Is Fae a boompus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a kerpus, so Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus.", "Every impus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus."], "answer": "Fae is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gerpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "impus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [1, 9], [4, 11], [12, 9], [5, 13], [3, 13], [0, 10], [3, 9], [7, 9], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Oliver is a storpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Oliver is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Is Oliver a wumpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "lempus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "grimpus", "hilpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [3, 10], [12, 13], [1, 14], [11, 10], [14, 13], [6, 14], [7, 14], [0, 12], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every numpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Is Eva a dumpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a scrompus, so Eva is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a dumpus, so Eva is a dumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lorpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "bompus", "quimpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 17], [7, 16], [8, 13], [12, 13], [11, 12], [6, 11], [8, 17], [16, 14], [1, 9], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every worpus is a impus. Davis is a bompus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every impus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a impus. Is Davis a numpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a kerpus, so Davis is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus."], "answer": "Davis is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "rompus", "lempus", "kerpus", "numpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "impus", "terpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [2, 9], [8, 9], [9, 11], [1, 11], [0, 11], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Is Gabriel a numpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a numpus, so Gabriel is a numpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "sterpus", "gerpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "numpus", "jompus", "worpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "yumpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [10, 11], [7, 10], [4, 13], [14, 12], [2, 12], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a sterpus. Sally is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Is Sally a fompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Sally is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "terpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "felpus", "grimpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 14], [6, 11], [4, 13], [1, 14], [0, 12], [11, 14], [2, 13], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every worpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Polly is a rompus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Polly is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Is Polly a kerpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a wumpus, so Polly is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a timpus, so Polly is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "worpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [1, 10], [7, 13], [10, 9], [12, 11], [11, 9], [9, 11], [5, 13], [6, 10], [0, 13], [13, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Is Tom a lempus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a terpus, so Tom is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus."], "answer": "Tom is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "scrompus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "lempus", "bompus", "shumpus", "rompus", "storpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [18, 13], [1, 12], [18, 10], [18, 17], [2, 13], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every fompus is a rompus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a impus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Is Sally a storpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a impus, so Sally is a impus.", "Every impus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus."], "answer": "Sally is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "bompus", "worpus", "impus", "yumpus", "felpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "storpus", "jompus", "zumpus", "rompus", "numpus", "rorpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 18], [11, 15], [8, 10], [2, 12], [14, 12], [3, 13], [7, 18], [10, 12], [8, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Is Tom a yumpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "lorpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "boompus", "yumpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "felpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [2, 10], [6, 10], [1, 9], [4, 11], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a impus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Davis is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Is Davis a yimpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "jelpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 14], [12, 15], [15, 14], [11, 9], [14, 9], [5, 12], [8, 9], [12, 9], [13, 12], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every chorpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Sally is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Is Sally a wumpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a chorpus, so Sally is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jompus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "shumpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [12, 9], [8, 12], [9, 13], [11, 9], [2, 13], [10, 12], [12, 13], [1, 9], [0, 13], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Alex is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Alex is a chorpus. Is Alex a lempus or a impus?", "steps": ["Alex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gorpus, so Alex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yerpus, so Alex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a impus, so Alex is a impus."], "answer": "Alex is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "tumpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "vumpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [5, 11], [7, 9], [4, 10], [0, 10], [5, 9], [0, 9], [6, 10], [10, 11], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every terpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a numpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Jack is a lempus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a impus. Is Jack a impus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gwompus, so Jack is a gwompus."], "answer": "Jack is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "tumpus", "worpus", "numpus", "boompus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [7, 12], [0, 10], [2, 9], [1, 9], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Is Max a fompus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Max is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus."], "answer": "Max is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "lorpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "rompus", "felpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 14], [12, 11], [6, 14], [16, 14], [5, 10], [1, 10], [3, 14], [15, 9], [3, 9], [5, 13], [5, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every storpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a terpus. Every yumpus is a wumpus. Davis is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Is Davis a boompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a timpus, so Davis is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a boompus, so Davis is a boompus."], "answer": "Davis is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "yumpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "timpus", "boompus", "storpus", "kerpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "terpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [1, 13], [9, 13], [6, 11], [0, 11], [9, 15], [4, 12], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a boompus. Is Sally a lorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a tumpus, so Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "lempus", "rompus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [5, 11], [8, 9], [7, 9], [6, 13], [3, 9], [7, 11], [4, 13], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Carol is a felpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Is Carol a wumpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a hilpus, so Carol is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gorpus, so Carol is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus."], "answer": "Carol is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "kerpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "gwompus", "timpus", "sterpus", "rempus", "terpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 11], [6, 11], [13, 12], [0, 12], [3, 15], [12, 16], [10, 16], [13, 16], [12, 11], [15, 16], [10, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every worpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Max is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Is Max a kerpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a zhorpus, so Max is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Max is a gerpus."], "answer": "Max is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "wumpus", "quimpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "storpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [8, 12], [19, 16], [9, 13], [10, 18], [0, 16], [5, 14], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Is Sally a wumpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gerpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "zumpus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "terpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [7, 10], [3, 11], [4, 11], [10, 11], [5, 9], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Is Rex a yumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Rex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "scrompus", "sterpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "timpus", "zhorpus", "rompus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 15], [4, 13], [9, 11], [10, 9], [12, 9], [7, 9], [3, 15], [15, 14], [14, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a impus. Every impus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a impus. Every felpus is a impus. Is Carol a lempus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a chorpus, so Carol is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus."], "answer": "Carol is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "kerpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "rempus", "bompus", "felpus", "fompus", "rompus", "lempus", "yerpus", "terpus", "timpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 13], [16, 10], [16, 11], [8, 17], [6, 17], [13, 9], [11, 17], [17, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Is Sally a yumpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a impus, so Sally is a impus.", "Every impus is a yimpus, so Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus."], "answer": "Sally is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gerpus", "impus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "lempus", "jompus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [14, 12], [16, 10], [11, 18], [13, 16], [4, 9], [8, 15], [18, 11], [1, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Is Rex a terpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a worpus, so Rex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus."], "answer": "Rex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rorpus", "rompus", "worpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "bompus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "numpus", "yimpus", "boompus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [9, 11], [8, 13], [4, 12], [9, 13], [9, 12], [6, 14], [1, 12], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Oliver is a rompus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Is Oliver a storpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a dumpus, so Oliver is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "sterpus", "gorpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "jompus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "storpus", "fompus", "gerpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 16], [9, 18], [5, 16], [0, 11], [7, 13], [4, 9], [4, 10], [18, 10], [3, 18], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every numpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Alex is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Is Alex a zhorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a worpus, so Alex is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Alex is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "sterpus", "rompus", "storpus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "numpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "wumpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [10, 13], [9, 12], [3, 10], [9, 13], [0, 12], [5, 9], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a storpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Is Davis a scrompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a brimpus, so Davis is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus."], "answer": "Davis is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "lorpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "storpus", "worpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "scrompus", "impus", "wumpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 15], [11, 10], [9, 14], [14, 10], [8, 10], [4, 10], [3, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every worpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Is Sam a gwompus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a kerpus, so Sam is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a shumpus, so Sam is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a numpus, so Sam is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a hilpus, so Sam is a hilpus."], "answer": "Sam is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "worpus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "terpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 15], [9, 13], [6, 12], [14, 10], [5, 15], [12, 15], [12, 10], [3, 11], [3, 13], [7, 16], [14, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Tom is a gorpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Is Tom a gorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a sterpus, so Tom is a sterpus."], "answer": "Tom is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "lempus", "tumpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "timpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [4, 10], [0, 11], [8, 10], [4, 9], [9, 11], [3, 11], [10, 11], [2, 10], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Is Sam a rempus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zumpus, so Sam is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus."], "answer": "Sam is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "terpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [3, 11], [4, 9], [1, 9], [4, 11], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every lempus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Gabriel is a jompus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Is Gabriel a jompus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a bompus, so Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a lorpus, so Gabriel is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "felpus", "fompus", "bompus", "lorpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "lempus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [1, 9], [0, 9], [2, 9], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Is Davis a kerpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a chorpus, so Davis is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Davis is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a kerpus, so Davis is a kerpus."], "answer": "Davis is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rorpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "terpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "fompus", "worpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "jompus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [12, 11], [12, 10], [2, 13], [4, 11], [11, 12], [9, 13], [3, 9], [8, 9], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every numpus is a rorpus. Oliver is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Is Oliver a hilpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "yumpus", "rempus", "numpus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "terpus", "jompus", "felpus", "impus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [4, 9], [0, 13], [2, 9], [3, 10], [2, 15], [9, 12], [9, 15], [4, 14], [3, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a impus. Is Eva a terpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a sterpus, so Eva is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "zumpus", "sterpus", "impus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "rempus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [7, 15], [5, 10], [9, 14], [8, 14], [5, 14], [9, 12], [4, 10], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every jompus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a rompus. Sally is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Is Sally a vumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a jompus, so Sally is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rorpus, so Sally is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gerpus", "jompus", "rorpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "sterpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "rempus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [5, 15], [6, 11], [0, 11], [6, 13], [4, 15], [2, 10], [9, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Is Polly a hilpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a vumpus, so Polly is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yimpus, so Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a numpus, so Polly is a numpus."], "answer": "Polly is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "chorpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "numpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "lempus", "jompus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "boompus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 13], [14, 9], [9, 15], [8, 10], [10, 15], [12, 13], [13, 9], [13, 14], [11, 13], [5, 9], [4, 15], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a impus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Is Alex a kerpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a vumpus, so Alex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rempus, so Alex is a rempus."], "answer": "Alex is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jelpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "rompus", "wumpus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "storpus", "impus", "kerpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [4, 9], [8, 13], [13, 14], [3, 14], [4, 10], [5, 12], [8, 9], [14, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every felpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a zhorpus. Eva is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Is Eva a jompus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus."], "answer": "Eva is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "chorpus", "zhorpus", "rorpus", "gorpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "felpus", "numpus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [1, 11], [8, 12], [3, 9], [0, 10], [3, 11], [5, 9], [1, 10], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a gerpus. Gabriel is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Gabriel is a boompus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Is Gabriel a rompus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "hilpus", "storpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "bompus", "kerpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [7, 10], [16, 12], [11, 9], [6, 11], [4, 11], [0, 14], [4, 9], [0, 9], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every bompus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Is Eva a vumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a scrompus, so Eva is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lorpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "jompus", "tumpus", "bompus", "brimpus", "felpus", "numpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "grimpus", "boompus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 18], [18, 15], [6, 16], [13, 18], [11, 17], [5, 17], [6, 17], [4, 13], [9, 18], [4, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every boompus is a jompus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Is Sam a yimpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Sam is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Sam is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a brimpus, so Sam is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "terpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [2, 13], [3, 10], [1, 12], [7, 12], [10, 11], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a lempus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Is Carol a bompus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yimpus, so Carol is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a terpus, so Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "lorpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "lempus", "numpus", "yumpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "jompus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [12, 11], [11, 12], [10, 14], [11, 9], [10, 13], [5, 9], [12, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every bompus is a rempus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Is Jack a brimpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a bompus, so Jack is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Jack is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "terpus", "jelpus", "bompus", "rempus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [16, 13], [7, 11], [4, 15], [13, 14], [4, 13], [13, 16], [4, 12], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every gerpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Is Max a rempus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a numpus, so Max is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus."], "answer": "Max is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "gerpus", "impus", "scrompus", "numpus", "rempus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [15, 9], [7, 10], [2, 17], [1, 17], [13, 10], [9, 15], [14, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Stella is a terpus. Every kerpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Is Stella a jompus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a felpus, so Stella is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a lorpus, so Stella is a lorpus."], "answer": "Stella is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "kerpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "zumpus", "terpus", "bompus", "lempus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [9, 19], [7, 12], [2, 9], [19, 15], [16, 15], [7, 13], [0, 14], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a impus. Is Tom a storpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus."], "answer": "Tom is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rorpus", "yerpus", "impus", "jompus", "storpus", "terpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [2, 12], [11, 12], [4, 9], [3, 10], [11, 10], [2, 10], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every jompus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Tom is a storpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Is Tom a tumpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a worpus, so Tom is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a rompus, so Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "grimpus", "worpus", "rompus", "bompus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "jompus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [2, 10], [3, 9], [4, 12], [9, 12], [1, 10], [0, 10], [1, 12], [8, 12], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every worpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a tumpus. Is Gabriel a felpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "chorpus", "worpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "rompus", "storpus", "gwompus", "numpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "fompus", "tumpus", "bompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [15, 9], [1, 11], [9, 16], [7, 15], [2, 10], [17, 14], [2, 13], [8, 10], [4, 13], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every impus is a rompus. Every storpus is a fompus. Davis is a rompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Is Davis a rompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a gwompus, so Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a scrompus, so Davis is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "storpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "fompus", "rompus", "impus", "worpus", "bompus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [3, 13], [3, 12], [0, 9], [6, 11], [10, 9], [7, 10], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every jompus is a boompus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Is Davis a gerpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Davis is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus."], "answer": "Davis is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "jompus", "rompus", "fompus", "worpus", "gerpus", "boompus", "shumpus", "bompus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 17], [10, 15], [16, 11], [2, 10], [14, 13], [18, 12], [3, 9], [17, 15], [15, 13], [18, 10], [16, 12], [18, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Is Wren a rorpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a yumpus, so Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rempus, so Wren is a rempus."], "answer": "Wren is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "storpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [10, 12], [10, 11], [10, 9], [2, 13], [2, 10], [9, 12], [7, 11], [8, 9], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a zhorpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a tumpus. Sally is a yimpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Is Sally a sterpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a zhorpus, so Sally is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a numpus, so Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a sterpus, so Sally is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sally is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "boompus", "chorpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 17], [7, 9], [16, 13], [6, 17], [0, 17], [6, 13], [6, 16], [17, 13], [1, 10], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Carol is a numpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every impus is a terpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Is Carol a hilpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Carol is a hilpus."], "answer": "Carol is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "grimpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "impus", "storpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "numpus", "rorpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [12, 13], [0, 14], [3, 10], [6, 15], [6, 11], [16, 14], [14, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Sally is a lorpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Is Sally a impus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lempus, so Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a kerpus, so Sally is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a impus, so Sally is a impus."], "answer": "Sally is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "numpus", "yumpus", "lempus", "kerpus", "impus", "rempus", "bompus", "terpus", "gorpus", "storpus", "lorpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [3, 12], [6, 10], [8, 10], [12, 11], [6, 12], [8, 9], [0, 11], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Is Rex a felpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a felpus, so Rex is a felpus."], "answer": "Rex is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "gwompus", "jompus", "dumpus", "fompus", "felpus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [4, 13], [4, 9], [6, 9], [7, 11], [5, 11], [12, 13], [7, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every impus is a gwompus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Is Tom a lorpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a impus, so Tom is a impus.", "Every impus is a gwompus, so Tom is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a fompus, so Tom is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a lorpus, so Tom is a lorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "zhorpus", "impus", "gwompus", "fompus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [5, 11], [9, 11], [9, 12], [11, 9], [8, 9], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Is Alex a gorpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a kerpus, so Alex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Alex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "storpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [4, 10], [10, 9], [3, 10], [2, 9], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every lempus is a fompus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Gabriel is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Gabriel is a rempus. Is Gabriel a rompus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "tumpus", "quimpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "bompus", "shumpus", "boompus", "fompus", "lempus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [8, 11], [0, 14], [10, 9], [9, 10], [0, 13], [4, 9], [13, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a worpus. Is Oliver a vumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "rorpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "boompus", "timpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 9], [3, 11], [9, 10], [1, 10], [6, 11], [5, 10], [12, 11], [4, 12], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every storpus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Eva is a rempus. Is Eva a quimpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yerpus, so Eva is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a brimpus, so Eva is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "terpus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "jompus", "rempus", "impus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [2, 15], [9, 11], [4, 14], [0, 9], [15, 11], [4, 16], [3, 10], [11, 10], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Max is a rompus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Max is a bompus. Is Max a bompus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Max is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a sterpus, so Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a grimpus, so Max is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a tumpus, so Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus."], "answer": "Max is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rempus", "sterpus", "grimpus", "tumpus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "felpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 17], [11, 17], [10, 12], [2, 10], [15, 12], [10, 14], [0, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Is Sally a timpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jelpus, so Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a timpus, so Sally is a timpus."], "answer": "Sally is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "lempus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 15], [5, 12], [2, 10], [10, 15], [16, 10], [14, 11], [3, 13], [14, 9], [13, 10], [5, 9], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rempus is a jompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Is Gabriel a hilpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a hilpus, so Gabriel is a hilpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "brimpus", "scrompus", "jompus", "yumpus", "hilpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "felpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 12], [6, 11], [13, 16], [8, 14], [14, 16], [6, 14], [14, 15], [10, 14], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Bob is a quimpus. Every rompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Is Bob a quimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a timpus, so Bob is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "sterpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "timpus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "jelpus", "felpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [0, 14], [3, 12], [11, 15], [12, 10], [9, 15], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every boompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Bob is a boompus. Every rorpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a jompus. Is Bob a dumpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a dumpus, so Bob is a dumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rorpus", "jelpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "bompus", "lempus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "rompus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 15], [5, 14], [9, 14], [13, 11], [9, 13], [11, 9], [12, 14], [0, 11], [9, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Wren is a storpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Is Wren a zhorpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a fompus, so Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yumpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "vumpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [5, 13], [12, 13], [10, 12], [2, 15], [3, 14], [7, 14], [12, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a jompus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Is Davis a gwompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a shumpus, so Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gwompus, so Davis is a gwompus."], "answer": "Davis is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "scrompus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "gwompus", "fompus", "jompus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [5, 9], [3, 11], [13, 9], [1, 9], [1, 12], [11, 12], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every impus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Jack is a jelpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a rompus. Is Jack a numpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a impus, so Jack is a impus.", "Every impus is a kerpus, so Jack is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gwompus, so Jack is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a chorpus, so Jack is a chorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "shumpus", "impus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "dumpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "bompus", "numpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "terpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [10, 15], [1, 10], [10, 12], [13, 9], [11, 10], [2, 12], [9, 10], [0, 11], [5, 15], [15, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every impus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Jack is a lempus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Jack is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every impus is a numpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Is Jack a impus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a shumpus, so Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a impus, so Jack is a impus."], "answer": "Jack is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "rompus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "impus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "brimpus", "terpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "numpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [0, 12], [10, 14], [13, 14], [3, 15], [7, 12], [0, 11], [5, 14], [15, 10], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every fompus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Polly is a timpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Polly is a terpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Is Polly a gorpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a fompus, so Polly is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "wumpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "storpus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "terpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [0, 12], [2, 17], [19, 9], [2, 16], [2, 11], [10, 9], [0, 10], [14, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Tom is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Is Tom a shumpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a wumpus, so Tom is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Tom is a shumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "sterpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [11, 9], [15, 11], [14, 12], [13, 11], [0, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Stella is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Stella is a chorpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Is Stella a numpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a kerpus, so Stella is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a boompus, so Stella is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a dumpus, so Stella is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus."], "answer": "Stella is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "brimpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "numpus", "wumpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "storpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [10, 11], [5, 12], [10, 15], [0, 12], [1, 11], [5, 9], [3, 11], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Bob is a jelpus. Every rempus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Is Bob a yumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus."], "answer": "Bob is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rempus", "jompus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "yumpus", "impus", "sterpus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "worpus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [0, 15], [15, 14], [15, 12], [13, 15], [9, 11], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Carol is a felpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every tumpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Is Carol a felpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a worpus, so Carol is a worpus."], "answer": "Carol is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "tumpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "sterpus", "worpus", "lempus", "storpus", "numpus", "impus", "felpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [4, 10], [10, 9], [0, 10], [7, 10], [6, 11], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Davis is a yumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Davis is a yerpus. Is Davis a brimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zhorpus, so Davis is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a gwompus, so Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus."], "answer": "Davis is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [0, 9], [17, 14], [8, 16], [9, 10], [0, 16], [8, 9], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Tom is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a hilpus. Is Tom a shumpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a jompus, so Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gorpus, so Tom is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "quimpus", "jompus", "boompus", "gorpus", "chorpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 10], [5, 11], [0, 9], [8, 10], [9, 10], [2, 10], [1, 11], [8, 9], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Is Carol a storpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Carol is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a lempus, so Carol is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a sterpus, so Carol is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a storpus, so Carol is a storpus."], "answer": "Carol is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "rompus", "lempus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "storpus", "bompus", "yerpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "wumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 14], [18, 15], [11, 9], [10, 14], [2, 15], [15, 17], [16, 14], [5, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Oliver is a jompus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a brimpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Is Oliver a kerpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "wumpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "rempus", "impus", "kerpus", "timpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [6, 10], [1, 13], [3, 16], [1, 17], [15, 16], [10, 16], [0, 17], [2, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every storpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Is Max a hilpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yumpus, so Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Max is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "storpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "jompus", "quimpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "dumpus", "hilpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [8, 9], [7, 10], [11, 10], [11, 9], [5, 11], [4, 9], [2, 10], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a brimpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a rempus. Davis is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Is Davis a wumpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yumpus, so Davis is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gwompus, so Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a scrompus, so Davis is a scrompus."], "answer": "Davis is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "impus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "brimpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [14, 9], [4, 13], [4, 9], [5, 13], [14, 12], [14, 10], [12, 9], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every storpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Sam is a sterpus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Is Sam a fompus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a grimpus, so Sam is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a kerpus, so Sam is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Sam is a felpus."], "answer": "Sam is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "rorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "storpus", "rompus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "brimpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 12], [13, 9], [7, 9], [1, 12], [5, 11], [0, 11], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every fompus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a terpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every rompus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Davis is a worpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every zhorpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Is Davis a hilpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rompus, so Davis is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Davis is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a bompus, so Davis is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus."], "answer": "Davis is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "gwompus", "rompus", "fompus", "bompus", "hilpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "numpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "sterpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 16], [0, 18], [9, 15], [3, 15], [18, 10], [7, 15], [1, 15], [7, 10], [5, 12], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a yerpus. Every brimpus is a impus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Oliver is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Is Oliver a worpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "kerpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "storpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "gerpus", "numpus", "rorpus", "bompus", "impus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 18], [4, 13], [18, 13], [1, 10], [16, 9], [18, 14], [15, 9], [6, 17], [15, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Is Oliver a lempus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus."], "answer": "Oliver is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "tumpus", "lempus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 12], [7, 15], [3, 14], [14, 9], [2, 13], [11, 13], [3, 11], [5, 9], [4, 12], [16, 13], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every terpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Sally is a vumpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Sally is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Is Sally a vumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a boompus, so Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Sally is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rompus, so Sally is a rompus."], "answer": "Sally is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "wumpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "terpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [8, 12], [0, 9], [2, 9], [0, 12], [10, 9], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Is Eva a impus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jompus, so Eva is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus."], "answer": "Eva is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "yimpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "worpus", "lorpus", "sterpus", "zumpus", "impus", "rompus", "terpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "brimpus", "jelpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [1, 10], [13, 14], [14, 13], [16, 10], [11, 16], [9, 12], [1, 11], [6, 10], [16, 12], [11, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Is Tom a yumpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gerpus, so Tom is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yumpus, so Tom is a yumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "jompus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "dumpus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [8, 10], [13, 11], [8, 14], [4, 15], [2, 10], [11, 10], [9, 12], [15, 11], [15, 9], [3, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rempus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a impus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Oliver is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a timpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus."], "answer": "Oliver is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "bompus", "yumpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "rempus", "fompus", "yerpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "tumpus", "impus", "terpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 16], [5, 14], [2, 13], [1, 15], [11, 15], [12, 10], [9, 12], [10, 16], [6, 11], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every impus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Davis is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Davis is a scrompus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Is Davis a yerpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a storpus, so Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a dumpus, so Davis is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "impus", "storpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [8, 10], [9, 11], [8, 11], [0, 11], [5, 11], [0, 9], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Max is a boompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Is Max a wumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a rempus, so Max is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus."], "answer": "Max is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "zumpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "wumpus", "hilpus", "impus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "gorpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [7, 12], [10, 12], [5, 11], [1, 12], [3, 13], [1, 11], [4, 10], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Is Jack a felpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus."], "answer": "Jack is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "shumpus", "grimpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "chorpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "dumpus", "scrompus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 11], [4, 14], [1, 13], [2, 9], [6, 13], [8, 10], [8, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every bompus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a impus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Is Max a rorpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gwompus, so Max is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a rorpus, so Max is a rorpus."], "answer": "Max is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "grimpus", "jompus", "lempus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "impus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 18], [8, 11], [16, 18], [1, 15], [18, 9], [9, 18], [5, 14], [17, 18], [15, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Alex is a vumpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Is Alex a yimpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a felpus, so Alex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zumpus, so Alex is a zumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jompus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "lempus", "gerpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 19], [19, 16], [18, 14], [7, 18], [11, 14], [7, 11], [11, 19], [14, 10], [9, 13], [2, 14], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Is Gabriel a jompus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a yumpus, so Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a gerpus, so Gabriel is a gerpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "storpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "gerpus", "grimpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "jompus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 12], [13, 16], [10, 17], [7, 14], [2, 9], [8, 13], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Every bompus is a jompus. Alex is a jompus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Is Alex a rempus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a bompus, so Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus."], "answer": "Alex is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "hilpus", "yumpus", "dumpus", "bompus", "fompus", "kerpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "gwompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [7, 12], [4, 9], [4, 12], [5, 12], [9, 12], [11, 10], [12, 10], [1, 9], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every impus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a felpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Is Sam a gwompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a impus.", "Every impus is a gerpus, so Sam is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a lempus, so Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zumpus, so Sam is a zumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "impus", "gerpus", "lempus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "terpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [5, 11], [14, 11], [11, 9], [2, 9], [16, 14], [1, 13], [16, 13], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a gwompus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Is Tom a quimpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lorpus, so Tom is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a wumpus, so Tom is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "lempus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "fompus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "impus", "gerpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [6, 9], [8, 11], [1, 9], [1, 12], [8, 9], [6, 11], [5, 9], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every timpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Is Wren a gerpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gerpus, so Wren is a gerpus."], "answer": "Wren is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "storpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "bompus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "impus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [9, 16], [11, 10], [13, 9], [1, 9], [2, 13], [7, 12], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a numpus. Every terpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a yimpus. Is Sam a yumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Sam is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rompus, so Sam is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus."], "answer": "Sam is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "sterpus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "rempus", "gerpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "tumpus", "yumpus", "vumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [7, 12], [2, 11], [1, 12], [3, 10], [9, 10], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Is Fae a jelpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rorpus, so Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus.", "Every impus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus."], "answer": "Fae is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "brimpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "impus", "jelpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "dumpus", "rempus", "numpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "lempus", "felpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 15], [7, 10], [8, 18], [14, 16], [6, 10], [10, 19], [3, 17], [18, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a felpus. Every timpus is a terpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a lempus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every brimpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Jack is a kerpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Jack is a rempus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Jack is a terpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Is Jack a terpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a fompus, so Jack is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a scrompus, so Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a wumpus, so Jack is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus."], "answer": "Jack is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "zumpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "lempus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "timpus", "yumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [2, 16], [0, 13], [1, 16], [0, 9], [8, 14], [14, 13], [14, 16], [1, 10], [16, 14], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every timpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a zumpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Carol is a chorpus. Is Carol a worpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a bompus, so Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a gorpus, so Carol is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "timpus", "bompus", "gorpus", "scrompus", "vumpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "rompus", "terpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [0, 15], [16, 14], [16, 12], [10, 15], [16, 15], [7, 14], [17, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every felpus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every gorpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a impus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Is Gabriel a chorpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lorpus, so Gabriel is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a grimpus, so Gabriel is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a chorpus, so Gabriel is a chorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "yumpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "felpus", "gwompus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "impus", "lempus", "tumpus", "jompus", "storpus", "fompus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 13], [3, 14], [3, 15], [15, 13], [9, 14], [2, 18], [19, 17], [5, 17], [14, 17], [16, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every lempus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every numpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Is Fae a storpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a lorpus, so Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus."], "answer": "Fae is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "quimpus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "storpus", "numpus", "lempus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [7, 15], [8, 14], [3, 11], [7, 9], [2, 15], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every felpus is a bompus. Every impus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a wumpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a impus. Is Max a numpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus."], "answer": "Max is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "kerpus", "felpus", "impus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "numpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [5, 11], [3, 9], [6, 10], [2, 9], [9, 11], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Sam is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a jompus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Sam is a numpus. Is Sam a worpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a jompus, so Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a worpus, so Sam is a worpus."], "answer": "Sam is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "lempus", "quimpus", "jompus", "tumpus", "worpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "gwompus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 15], [5, 16], [13, 12], [18, 9], [0, 19], [0, 17], [5, 10], [18, 11], [5, 17], [12, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every rompus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Gabriel is a rompus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Is Gabriel a jompus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a gwompus, so Gabriel is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a lempus, so Gabriel is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jompus, so Gabriel is a jompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "bompus", "kerpus", "gwompus", "lempus", "jompus", "yimpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "dumpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "impus", "terpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 17], [12, 17], [6, 12], [11, 10], [8, 16], [11, 14], [3, 15], [0, 11], [4, 13], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every storpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a bompus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a rempus. Tom is a storpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Is Tom a bompus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rorpus, so Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a quimpus, so Tom is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "bompus", "storpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [0, 11], [8, 12], [7, 10], [7, 9], [1, 10], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every worpus is a gwompus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a felpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Is Sally a jelpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a worpus, so Sally is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jelpus, so Sally is a jelpus."], "answer": "Sally is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "lempus", "zumpus", "worpus", "gwompus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "terpus", "felpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [8, 12], [5, 12], [1, 9], [13, 14], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a impus. Max is a zumpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Is Max a felpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a zhorpus, so Max is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a boompus, so Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a impus, so Max is a impus."], "answer": "Max is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "timpus", "zhorpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "impus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "zumpus", "lempus", "rompus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 16], [0, 11], [18, 11], [5, 11], [7, 11], [17, 16], [6, 19], [3, 13], [18, 17], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every lorpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Is Tom a rempus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a brimpus, so Tom is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a lorpus, so Tom is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus."], "answer": "Tom is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rorpus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "hilpus", "worpus", "felpus", "impus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "yerpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "yumpus", "timpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 16], [17, 11], [11, 9], [8, 15], [18, 17], [19, 13], [3, 18], [14, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a storpus. Is Wren a grimpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a hilpus, so Wren is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a grimpus, so Wren is a grimpus."], "answer": "Wren is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "worpus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "storpus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "kerpus", "impus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [6, 9], [15, 18], [10, 18], [5, 12], [10, 13], [11, 10], [18, 10], [15, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Wren is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every impus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Wren is a hilpus. Every numpus is a impus. Is Wren a rorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a numpus, so Wren is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a impus, so Wren is a impus.", "Every impus is a rorpus, so Wren is a rorpus."], "answer": "Wren is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "grimpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "impus", "rorpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "hilpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "dumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [9, 10], [0, 10], [2, 13], [8, 13], [1, 13], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every terpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Eva is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a terpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Is Eva a rempus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a impus, so Eva is a impus.", "Every impus is a shumpus, so Eva is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus."], "answer": "Eva is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "gwompus", "impus", "shumpus", "terpus", "rempus", "zhorpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "jompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [9, 11], [1, 11], [10, 9], [0, 9], [4, 10], [8, 10], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every storpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Jack is a yerpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Jack is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Is Jack a brimpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a scrompus, so Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rorpus, so Jack is a rorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "storpus", "worpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [11, 9], [9, 13], [8, 9], [12, 11], [7, 11], [0, 9], [1, 10], [0, 10], [12, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Is Tom a gwompus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a sterpus, so Tom is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gwompus, so Tom is a gwompus."], "answer": "Tom is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "tumpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "worpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "rompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 15], [4, 12], [8, 14], [9, 11], [5, 15], [13, 9], [3, 9], [8, 12], [12, 11], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every boompus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Fae is a kerpus. Every yerpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a impus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Is Fae a impus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a lempus, so Fae is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a impus, so Fae is a impus."], "answer": "Fae is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "dumpus", "shumpus", "boompus", "lempus", "impus", "terpus", "hilpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "chorpus", "timpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 15], [0, 9], [3, 17], [1, 9], [2, 16], [11, 18], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every rompus is a chorpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every impus is a numpus. Fae is a numpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a yimpus. Is Fae a impus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yimpus, so Fae is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a timpus, so Fae is a timpus."], "answer": "Fae is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "kerpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "storpus", "lorpus", "scrompus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "impus", "boompus", "rempus", "yumpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 10], [4, 9], [15, 18], [5, 17], [7, 10], [14, 10], [14, 17], [12, 11], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every impus is a rompus. Every rompus is a storpus. Fae is a gorpus. Every numpus is a terpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every impus is a numpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every impus is a fompus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Is Fae a terpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a impus.", "Every impus is a timpus, so Fae is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus."], "answer": "Fae is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "impus", "timpus", "dumpus", "storpus", "terpus", "fompus", "rompus", "numpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 16], [2, 14], [7, 19], [7, 11], [6, 19], [13, 16], [10, 19], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Bob is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Bob is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Bob is a brimpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Is Bob a worpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a dumpus, so Bob is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus."], "answer": "Bob is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "zhorpus", "rempus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "impus", "rompus", "yimpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 16], [16, 9], [17, 10], [0, 9], [16, 17], [13, 17], [10, 15], [0, 15], [15, 16], [1, 18], [12, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rempus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every bompus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a vumpus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Every vumpus is a yumpus. Is Eva a sterpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gwompus, so Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yimpus, so Eva is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Eva is a grimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "rempus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "terpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [16, 14], [13, 15], [13, 11], [6, 14], [6, 13], [1, 13], [8, 11], [6, 12], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Jack is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Is Jack a felpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a jelpus, so Jack is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a hilpus, so Jack is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a timpus, so Jack is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus."], "answer": "Jack is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "chorpus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "rompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [6, 14], [6, 12], [11, 9], [15, 9], [3, 15], [1, 12], [13, 15], [0, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rompus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a shumpus. Every impus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a jompus. Every rompus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Is Bob a felpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Bob is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus."], "answer": "Bob is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "hilpus", "impus", "jompus", "shumpus", "rempus", "jelpus", "rompus", "grimpus", "worpus", "felpus", "lempus", "chorpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 14], [7, 12], [13, 9], [3, 14], [7, 9], [12, 14], [13, 15], [4, 10], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Polly is a worpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every bompus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a bompus. Is Polly a rompus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a sterpus, so Polly is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rompus, so Polly is a rompus."], "answer": "Polly is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "fompus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "rompus", "lorpus", "lempus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "impus", "kerpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 13], [8, 10], [13, 12], [4, 13], [5, 9], [7, 9], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Is Bob a storpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a dumpus, so Bob is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gorpus, so Bob is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus."], "answer": "Bob is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "gwompus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "impus", "timpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 11], [2, 9], [5, 10], [10, 11], [7, 11], [8, 10], [1, 9], [9, 11], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a yumpus. Stella is a jompus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Stella is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Is Stella a worpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a scrompus, so Stella is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gerpus, so Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a worpus, so Stella is a worpus."], "answer": "Stella is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "rorpus", "scrompus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [0, 11], [4, 9], [3, 10], [10, 9], [1, 9], [0, 9], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every impus is a numpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a tumpus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a impus. Is Stella a bompus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a wumpus, so Stella is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a kerpus, so Stella is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a shumpus, so Stella is a shumpus."], "answer": "Stella is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "gerpus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "impus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "timpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "brimpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 15], [8, 10], [6, 10], [5, 14], [16, 15], [9, 17], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every rempus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a boompus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every numpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a tumpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Is Bob a fompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a chorpus, so Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a terpus, so Bob is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yerpus, so Bob is a yerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "numpus", "chorpus", "tumpus", "terpus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "boompus", "rempus", "bompus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "worpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 11], [2, 9], [1, 10], [3, 13], [5, 12], [6, 15], [3, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every felpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a storpus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a impus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a fompus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Is Bob a worpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a boompus, so Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus."], "answer": "Bob is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "felpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "worpus", "timpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "rempus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "impus", "gerpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 15], [14, 12], [5, 12], [14, 9], [16, 13], [15, 10], [6, 14], [1, 10], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every timpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Davis is a bompus. Davis is a gorpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every impus is a timpus. Is Davis a rempus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a worpus, so Davis is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rempus, so Davis is a rempus."], "answer": "Davis is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "grimpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "numpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "timpus", "terpus", "impus", "scrompus", "bompus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 11], [6, 9], [12, 10], [15, 13], [11, 15], [10, 9], [0, 9], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a kerpus. Is Wren a tumpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a zumpus, so Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a tumpus, so Wren is a tumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "fompus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "wumpus", "tumpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "boompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [5, 9], [1, 11], [3, 11], [5, 12], [10, 12], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every jompus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Gabriel is a jompus. Every gerpus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Is Gabriel a terpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rorpus, so Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "tumpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "impus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "bompus", "worpus", "zhorpus", "rempus", "terpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "lempus", "rompus", "quimpus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [0, 15], [1, 15], [8, 10], [18, 11], [15, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every numpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Eva is a hilpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every fompus is a rempus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a impus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every yerpus is a kerpus. Is Eva a yimpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a worpus, so Eva is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a quimpus, so Eva is a quimpus."], "answer": "Eva is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "terpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "worpus", "quimpus", "fompus", "boompus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "numpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "dumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [13, 10], [1, 10], [0, 14], [12, 19], [2, 12], [8, 16], [16, 17], [5, 18], [18, 11], [8, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every felpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a chorpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every lorpus is a chorpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a shumpus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every rempus is a impus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Is Polly a kerpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a lorpus, so Polly is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a numpus, so Polly is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a kerpus, so Polly is a kerpus."], "answer": "Polly is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "rempus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "impus", "chorpus", "gwompus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [1, 9], [13, 12], [3, 13], [9, 13], [2, 9], [12, 13], [11, 10], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every timpus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Sam is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Sam is a rempus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Is Sam a vumpus or a kerpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a dumpus, so Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a chorpus, so Sam is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a sterpus, so Sam is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a vumpus, so Sam is a vumpus."], "answer": "Sam is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "jompus", "dumpus", "chorpus", "sterpus", "vumpus", "timpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "impus", "shumpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [3, 10], [10, 13], [4, 13], [9, 13], [13, 11], [14, 9], [0, 14], [0, 11], [8, 14], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Polly is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every scrompus is a rorpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Is Polly a wumpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a brimpus, so Polly is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yerpus, so Polly is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a scrompus, so Polly is a scrompus."], "answer": "Polly is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "timpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [2, 9], [14, 9], [0, 9], [9, 12], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a rempus. Every fompus is a rempus. Sam is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every yimpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a yimpus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Is Sam a zhorpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yerpus, so Sam is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a quimpus, so Sam is a quimpus."], "answer": "Sam is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "chorpus", "yerpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "quimpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "jompus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "dumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 13], [4, 16], [12, 15], [7, 14], [8, 17], [0, 16], [9, 10], [3, 14], [14, 16], [12, 17], [6, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every zhorpus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a brimpus. Is Sally a gorpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "wumpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "boompus", "storpus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "rorpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [7, 11], [12, 13], [11, 9], [13, 17], [15, 17], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a storpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a sterpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Is Tom a gorpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a lempus, so Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a zumpus, so Tom is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gorpus, so Tom is a gorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "numpus", "lempus", "storpus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "sterpus", "felpus", "impus", "brimpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "rempus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "tumpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 16], [3, 14], [3, 12], [6, 10], [10, 16], [2, 16], [8, 19], [14, 12], [18, 13], [3, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Max is a storpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Is Max a yimpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a gwompus, so Max is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a bompus, so Max is a bompus."], "answer": "Max is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "vumpus", "brimpus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "numpus", "boompus", "terpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "lempus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [6, 13], [8, 13], [7, 9], [14, 10], [11, 12], [10, 11], [9, 14], [8, 12], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every numpus is a gwompus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every yumpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every fompus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a rorpus. Fae is a boompus. Every yumpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a shumpus. Is Fae a hilpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rempus, so Fae is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus."], "answer": "Fae is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "numpus", "yumpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "worpus", "boompus", "timpus", "yimpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 15], [7, 9], [3, 11], [0, 12], [9, 11], [2, 15], [10, 14], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every rempus is a shumpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a felpus. Is Davis a quimpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a numpus, so Davis is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a quimpus, so Davis is a quimpus."], "answer": "Davis is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "terpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "jompus", "shumpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [11, 9], [4, 11], [5, 11], [7, 10], [8, 10], [8, 9], [7, 9], [4, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every wumpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a gwompus. Sally is a quimpus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a lempus. Is Sally a wumpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a tumpus, so Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus."], "answer": "Sally is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "felpus", "tumpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "kerpus", "sterpus", "lempus", "fompus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "rompus", "storpus", "wumpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [18, 17], [7, 16], [0, 14], [17, 11], [12, 18], [11, 17], [12, 14], [9, 17], [4, 15], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Is Gabriel a dumpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a wumpus, so Gabriel is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a dumpus, so Gabriel is a dumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "kerpus", "worpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "lorpus", "timpus", "hilpus", "tumpus", "grimpus", "rempus", "shumpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [10, 12], [10, 14], [13, 11], [2, 13], [8, 14], [5, 12], [14, 11], [4, 11], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a kerpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Sam is a gerpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every tumpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Is Sam a kerpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a zumpus, so Sam is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rempus, so Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a terpus, so Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a kerpus, so Sam is a kerpus."], "answer": "Sam is a kerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "chorpus", "zumpus", "rempus", "terpus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "gorpus", "gerpus", "tumpus", "impus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [13, 17], [0, 12], [4, 10], [2, 12], [6, 10], [13, 16], [17, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a kerpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a bompus. Every impus is a bompus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Bob is a terpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Is Bob a jompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus.", "Every impus is a bompus, so Bob is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zhorpus, so Bob is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus."], "answer": "Bob is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "numpus", "impus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "lempus", "kerpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "storpus", "yerpus", "terpus", "wumpus", "rorpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [7, 17], [9, 16], [6, 15], [16, 14], [0, 15], [12, 16], [16, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Max is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every bompus is a gorpus. Is Max a scrompus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Max is a yimpus."], "answer": "Max is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "hilpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "bompus", "zumpus", "storpus", "boompus", "scrompus", "gerpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [12, 11], [3, 10], [4, 9], [8, 14], [7, 12], [0, 13], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a rempus. Every fompus is a bompus. Oliver is a yimpus. Every worpus is a kerpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a shumpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Is Oliver a worpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a bompus, so Oliver is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gorpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "storpus", "shumpus", "fompus", "rempus", "boompus", "kerpus", "numpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 17], [4, 13], [12, 10], [3, 15], [0, 14], [18, 14], [17, 15], [16, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every felpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a rempus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every lempus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Is Fae a hilpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gerpus, so Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a lempus, so Fae is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus."], "answer": "Fae is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "grimpus", "gerpus", "felpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "brimpus", "yimpus", "impus", "dumpus", "worpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "gorpus", "rorpus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [7, 13], [4, 10], [15, 17], [1, 12], [5, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a bompus. Every numpus is a yimpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Tom is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every boompus is a impus. Every impus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a quimpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every boompus is a rorpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Is Tom a tumpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a storpus, so Tom is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a tumpus, so Tom is a tumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "terpus", "storpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "tumpus", "numpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "impus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [1, 11], [11, 13], [6, 11], [0, 13], [10, 12], [11, 14], [10, 11], [4, 10], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Alex is a tumpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every bompus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every jelpus is a timpus. Every bompus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Alex is a zumpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a tumpus. Is Alex a lempus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Alex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a quimpus, so Alex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a timpus, so Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a lempus, so Alex is a lempus."], "answer": "Alex is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "bompus", "rempus", "quimpus", "timpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "boompus", "tumpus", "felpus", "zumpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 13], [12, 9], [5, 13], [0, 15], [1, 9], [5, 14], [16, 11], [8, 15], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a fompus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every rempus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Jack is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a kerpus. Every jompus is a zhorpus. Is Jack a kerpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lorpus, so Jack is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a vumpus, so Jack is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a quimpus, so Jack is a quimpus."], "answer": "Jack is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "grimpus", "worpus", "lorpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "sterpus", "fompus", "rompus", "wumpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "rempus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 15], [2, 12], [3, 11], [0, 9], [8, 14], [15, 9], [5, 14], [11, 13], [10, 11], [9, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lempus is a lorpus. Rex is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Rex is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a scrompus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Is Rex a quimpus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a yerpus, so Rex is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a brimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "lempus", "yerpus", "shumpus", "storpus", "brimpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [17, 14], [8, 14], [17, 13], [14, 11], [0, 10], [1, 13], [15, 17], [1, 17], [11, 15], [8, 13], [0, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every fompus is a worpus. Every worpus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every fompus is a kerpus. Stella is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every worpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Stella is a impus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a wumpus. Is Stella a jelpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Stella is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a worpus, so Stella is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rompus, so Stella is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rempus, so Stella is a rempus."], "answer": "Stella is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "fompus", "worpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "rempus", "storpus", "jompus", "kerpus", "jelpus", "impus", "wumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 9], [8, 10], [2, 11], [3, 9], [3, 11], [10, 11], [0, 9], [0, 10], [2, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every terpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Oliver is a dumpus. Every impus is a worpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every impus is a storpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Is Oliver a dumpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a lempus, so Oliver is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gorpus, so Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a worpus, so Oliver is a worpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "terpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "worpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "impus", "sterpus", "storpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 11], [6, 11], [1, 11], [3, 11], [4, 10], [7, 11], [8, 11], [2, 10], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every yerpus is a rempus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Sally is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Is Sally a gerpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a yerpus, so Sally is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus."], "answer": "Sally is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "tumpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "rempus", "bompus", "wumpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 12], [8, 10], [0, 11], [12, 11], [2, 12], [1, 12], [1, 10], [10, 11], [3, 9], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lempus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Tom is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every yerpus is a jelpus. Is Tom a wumpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a grimpus, so Tom is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a boompus, so Tom is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a wumpus, so Tom is a wumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "lempus", "rempus", "grimpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "timpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "bompus", "felpus", "chorpus", "worpus", "jelpus", "zumpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 9], [4, 11], [15, 11], [0, 12], [9, 13], [1, 15], [7, 14], [1, 12], [6, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Is Bob a timpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a scrompus, so Bob is a scrompus."], "answer": "Bob is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "chorpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "brimpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "rempus", "fompus", "boompus", "storpus", "numpus", "hilpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [16, 10], [3, 10], [17, 18], [16, 17], [9, 14], [14, 17], [8, 14], [17, 9], [17, 16], [13, 16], [12, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every quimpus is a wumpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a impus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a impus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Is Davis a impus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a jompus, so Davis is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Davis is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a impus, so Davis is a impus."], "answer": "Davis is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "quimpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "grimpus", "impus", "zhorpus", "hilpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "shumpus", "brimpus", "chorpus", "vumpus", "tumpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 13], [5, 14], [6, 9], [16, 13], [14, 9], [16, 10], [9, 12], [8, 15], [4, 16], [12, 9], [1, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every tumpus is a jompus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a felpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every yerpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a gwompus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Is Bob a jompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a storpus, so Bob is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a shumpus, so Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gwompus, so Bob is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus."], "answer": "Bob is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "brimpus", "storpus", "shumpus", "gwompus", "jompus", "terpus", "lorpus", "tumpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "dumpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [6, 12], [15, 14], [7, 10], [17, 11], [1, 11], [10, 15], [15, 13], [6, 9], [14, 15], [7, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a gorpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a tumpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every bompus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a zhorpus. Is Davis a bompus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a tumpus, so Davis is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a sterpus, so Davis is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a bompus, so Davis is a bompus."], "answer": "Davis is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "rorpus", "tumpus", "sterpus", "gorpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "felpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 12], [7, 11], [4, 11], [12, 10], [10, 12], [3, 10], [5, 9], [1, 11], [9, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a wumpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every rempus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Tom is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a wumpus. Tom is a quimpus. Every rompus is a grimpus. Every bompus is a rempus. Is Tom a zhorpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yerpus, so Tom is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a terpus, so Tom is a terpus."], "answer": "Tom is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "rempus", "terpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [3, 9], [7, 9], [0, 9], [11, 9], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a shumpus. Every quimpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Is Stella a gerpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a brimpus, so Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a zumpus, so Stella is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gerpus, so Stella is a gerpus."], "answer": "Stella is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "scrompus", "brimpus", "zumpus", "quimpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "rompus", "wumpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "grimpus", "lorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 13], [13, 15], [3, 19], [6, 19], [17, 14], [15, 14], [6, 11], [14, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Davis is a numpus. Davis is a worpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a timpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Every grimpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every zumpus is a impus. Every lempus is a impus. Every lempus is a numpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a worpus. Is Davis a zumpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Davis is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a scrompus, so Davis is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus."], "answer": "Davis is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "jelpus", "scrompus", "grimpus", "lempus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "timpus", "worpus", "impus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [11, 9], [3, 11], [7, 10], [0, 10], [5, 11], [8, 11], [4, 12], [4, 11], [4, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Gabriel is a numpus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a fompus. Is Gabriel a tumpus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a fompus, so Gabriel is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "lorpus", "terpus", "fompus", "shumpus", "boompus", "bompus", "zumpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [4, 10], [0, 9], [8, 12], [11, 9], [7, 10], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a tumpus. Every vumpus is a tumpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Carol is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every terpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every felpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every boompus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Is Carol a felpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a shumpus, so Carol is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a zumpus, so Carol is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jelpus, so Carol is a jelpus."], "answer": "Carol is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "terpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "zumpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "boompus", "lempus", "felpus", "tumpus", "yerpus", "gwompus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [5, 11], [5, 9], [13, 10], [0, 10], [6, 10], [11, 13], [7, 10], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every wumpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every numpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Is Polly a terpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a shumpus, so Polly is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a numpus, so Polly is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "yimpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "boompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [9, 10], [15, 13], [11, 9], [9, 11], [6, 12], [9, 12], [12, 9], [2, 14], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every lempus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every tumpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a numpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every scrompus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Is Eva a numpus or a rorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lempus, so Eva is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a kerpus, so Eva is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a rorpus, so Eva is a rorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a rorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "tumpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "numpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "jompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 16], [13, 14], [11, 10], [15, 16], [13, 12], [2, 17], [5, 14], [6, 15], [4, 17]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a boompus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every worpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a lempus. Every worpus is a bompus. Every scrompus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a worpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Is Fae a wumpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Fae is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a timpus, so Fae is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a wumpus, so Fae is a wumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gwompus", "zumpus", "boompus", "timpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "storpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "bompus", "worpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "impus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [12, 16], [2, 9], [1, 12], [5, 10], [12, 11], [8, 14], [3, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every yerpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a storpus. Is Davis a zumpus or a lempus?", "steps": ["Davis is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a yerpus, so Davis is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a felpus, so Davis is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a storpus, so Davis is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a lempus, so Davis is a lempus."], "answer": "Davis is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "tumpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "storpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "rorpus", "fompus", "zumpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 12], [4, 9], [11, 9], [6, 12], [8, 12], [4, 11], [8, 9], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every boompus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every jelpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every tumpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a rempus. Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Every sterpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Is Polly a yumpus or a jompus?", "steps": ["Polly is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a scrompus, so Polly is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Polly is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a bompus, so Polly is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yumpus, so Polly is a yumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "kerpus", "scrompus", "boompus", "bompus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "jelpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [11, 10], [4, 9], [8, 11], [2, 10], [6, 11], [5, 10], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every gerpus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every jelpus is a chorpus. Is Stella a scrompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a brimpus, so Stella is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a grimpus, so Stella is a grimpus."], "answer": "Stella is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "gerpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "sterpus", "bompus", "rompus", "lempus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "numpus", "jelpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [10, 11], [8, 11], [16, 17], [9, 19], [19, 13], [18, 16], [15, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every yerpus is a lorpus. Bob is a sterpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every fompus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every boompus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every boompus is a yumpus. Every yerpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Is Bob a numpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a yumpus, so Bob is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a numpus, so Bob is a numpus."], "answer": "Bob is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "boompus", "yumpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "yerpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "brimpus", "gerpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 14], [7, 11], [8, 9], [13, 14], [0, 12], [4, 14], [11, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every yimpus is a timpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a felpus. Every timpus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every brimpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Is Gabriel a storpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a impus, so Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a yimpus, so Gabriel is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a storpus, so Gabriel is a storpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "brimpus", "jelpus", "impus", "yimpus", "storpus", "jompus", "boompus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "yumpus", "timpus", "felpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [16, 14], [8, 14], [4, 13], [7, 9], [12, 11], [5, 13], [12, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a gorpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a yerpus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a timpus. Alex is a timpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a brimpus. Is Alex a yerpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gerpus, so Alex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a brimpus, so Alex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yumpus, so Alex is a yumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "rempus", "gerpus", "zhorpus", "brimpus", "yumpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "jompus", "timpus", "yerpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [2, 11], [0, 9], [6, 10], [8, 9], [5, 11], [6, 9], [7, 9], [1, 9], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a jompus. Every terpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Jack is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Every jompus is a yerpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every jelpus is a quimpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a jompus. Is Jack a yerpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a hilpus, so Jack is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a jompus, so Jack is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus."], "answer": "Jack is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "gorpus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "bompus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "lempus", "zhorpus", "quimpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [3, 11], [8, 10], [8, 12], [6, 10], [0, 11], [1, 9], [13, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every storpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a worpus. Wren is a hilpus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Is Wren a scrompus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Wren is a scrompus."], "answer": "Wren is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "grimpus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "tumpus", "worpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "impus", "boompus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "storpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 11], [5, 11], [9, 16], [0, 14], [1, 13], [16, 14], [10, 12], [10, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every impus is a storpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every storpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Is Fae a rempus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a impus, so Fae is a impus.", "Every impus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yerpus, so Fae is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a quimpus, so Fae is a quimpus."], "answer": "Fae is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gerpus", "impus", "storpus", "yerpus", "quimpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "bompus", "rorpus", "brimpus", "dumpus", "terpus", "timpus", "gorpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [3, 9], [5, 16], [13, 14], [11, 18], [11, 16], [6, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every rempus is a fompus. Every impus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Is Tom a fompus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a rempus, so Tom is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a kerpus, so Tom is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a terpus, so Tom is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a vumpus, so Tom is a vumpus."], "answer": "Tom is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "rorpus", "rempus", "kerpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "felpus", "storpus", "impus", "boompus", "fompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [2, 10], [5, 11], [8, 11], [1, 9], [7, 11], [8, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a chorpus. Every gorpus is a storpus. Wren is a impus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Is Wren a boompus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rompus, so Wren is a rompus."], "answer": "Wren is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "storpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "gorpus", "chorpus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "boompus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [1, 9], [8, 11], [11, 14], [4, 12], [0, 15], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a fompus. Gabriel is a bompus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a tumpus. Gabriel is a felpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every tumpus is a lorpus. Is Gabriel a lorpus or a felpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a tumpus, so Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a lorpus, so Gabriel is a lorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "dumpus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "lorpus", "fompus", "grimpus", "chorpus", "impus", "shumpus", "yumpus", "worpus", "numpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [17, 14], [0, 14], [16, 18], [18, 11], [13, 12], [18, 15], [10, 13], [0, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every impus is a scrompus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every bompus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Is Tom a rompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a chorpus, so Tom is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a bompus, so Tom is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yimpus, so Tom is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rompus, so Tom is a rompus."], "answer": "Tom is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "hilpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "rompus", "fompus", "jompus", "impus", "scrompus", "timpus", "shumpus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "yumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [8, 12], [5, 14], [5, 12], [2, 9], [4, 14], [12, 13], [9, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every sterpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a brimpus. Every sterpus is a impus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every yerpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a rempus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Is Rex a yerpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a impus, so Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a scrompus, so Rex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus."], "answer": "Rex is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "sterpus", "impus", "scrompus", "rempus", "fompus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "tumpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "worpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [10, 12], [9, 14], [9, 16], [6, 14], [3, 16], [14, 9], [11, 16]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a felpus. Wren is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every yerpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a quimpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every gerpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Is Wren a hilpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gerpus, so Wren is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a felpus, so Wren is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a quimpus, so Wren is a quimpus."], "answer": "Wren is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "dumpus", "gerpus", "timpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "lempus", "scrompus", "rorpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "rempus", "yimpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [2, 13], [2, 12], [11, 10], [9, 10], [7, 9], [5, 11], [4, 11], [6, 9], [6, 11], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every boompus is a lempus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a lorpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a lempus. Every sterpus is a zhorpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Is Sam a lempus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a gwompus, so Sam is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zhorpus, so Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a terpus, so Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a numpus, so Sam is a numpus."], "answer": "Sam is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "jelpus", "gwompus", "zhorpus", "terpus", "numpus", "sterpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [4, 10], [6, 11], [5, 11], [8, 11], [1, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every jompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a dumpus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a felpus. Max is a felpus. Every jompus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a grimpus. Max is a gwompus. Every felpus is a impus. Every timpus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Is Max a gwompus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a brimpus, so Max is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a quimpus, so Max is a quimpus."], "answer": "Max is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "jompus", "brimpus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "numpus", "zhorpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "rompus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 12], [2, 13], [13, 11], [0, 12], [9, 13], [0, 13], [9, 10], [11, 10], [3, 10], [3, 14], [13, 15], [1, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rorpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Rex is a storpus. Every numpus is a rempus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Rex is a yimpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Rex is a bompus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every storpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Is Rex a storpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a dumpus, so Rex is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rempus, so Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus."], "answer": "Rex is a gwompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rorpus", "dumpus", "lempus", "rempus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "numpus", "boompus", "brimpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "storpus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [1, 13], [0, 12], [12, 9], [0, 14], [9, 14], [0, 10], [2, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every fompus is a worpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Fae is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every wumpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every wumpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a quimpus. Every numpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every rempus is a fompus. Every storpus is a fompus. Is Fae a worpus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a terpus, so Fae is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a storpus, so Fae is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a fompus, so Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus."], "answer": "Fae is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "wumpus", "terpus", "storpus", "fompus", "worpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "numpus", "quimpus", "gorpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 11], [10, 11], [0, 9], [10, 9], [4, 9], [9, 10], [11, 10], [8, 11], [2, 11], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a felpus. Every shumpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every worpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every hilpus is a dumpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every impus is a boompus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Is Max a lempus or a boompus?", "steps": ["Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a felpus, so Max is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a worpus, so Max is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus."], "answer": "Max is a lempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "shumpus", "felpus", "dumpus", "worpus", "lempus", "hilpus", "zhorpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "impus", "storpus", "wumpus", "boompus", "grimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [13, 10], [11, 14], [8, 15], [3, 9], [5, 10], [5, 15], [15, 14], [10, 14], [1, 10], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a yumpus. Every bompus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Is Bob a rorpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Bob is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a impus, so Bob is a impus.", "Every impus is a jelpus, so Bob is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a sterpus, so Bob is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus."], "answer": "Bob is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "chorpus", "impus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "rempus", "tumpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "bompus", "yumpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "storpus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "lempus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [17, 12], [17, 19], [8, 13], [15, 11], [11, 10], [10, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every terpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a tumpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Gabriel is a bompus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every yimpus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a bompus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a wumpus. Every gorpus is a wumpus. Every tumpus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Is Gabriel a yimpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a terpus, so Gabriel is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a tumpus, so Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rompus, so Gabriel is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a vumpus, so Gabriel is a vumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "hilpus", "terpus", "tumpus", "rompus", "vumpus", "brimpus", "impus", "gorpus", "yimpus", "bompus", "lempus", "jelpus", "wumpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 10], [12, 11], [0, 10], [4, 11], [5, 13], [10, 12], [9, 11], [8, 13], [12, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every timpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a fompus. Every wumpus is a rorpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every jompus is a rempus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every rorpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every wumpus is a timpus. Every rorpus is a bompus. Every wumpus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Is Carol a tumpus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Carol is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a timpus, so Carol is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a vumpus, so Carol is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a bompus, so Carol is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a tumpus, so Carol is a tumpus."], "answer": "Carol is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "wumpus", "timpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "tumpus", "terpus", "rorpus", "jompus", "rempus", "brimpus", "fompus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [5, 9], [10, 11], [8, 12], [2, 11], [8, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every worpus is a wumpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Is Bob a yerpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a tumpus, so Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a dumpus, so Bob is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a lorpus, so Bob is a lorpus."], "answer": "Bob is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "zumpus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "rorpus", "yerpus", "grimpus", "storpus", "fompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [4, 11], [5, 10], [7, 12], [12, 11], [7, 11], [5, 13], [2, 9], [5, 9], [11, 9], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every worpus is a rorpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Every vumpus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a felpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Is Eva a wumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a hilpus, so Eva is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Eva is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a wumpus, so Eva is a wumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "grimpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "worpus", "felpus", "impus", "numpus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "tumpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [19, 10], [17, 14], [17, 11], [10, 14], [10, 11], [1, 14], [3, 13], [11, 18], [7, 19], [16, 11], [11, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 18}, {"question": "Every storpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every boompus is a wumpus. Every impus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a scrompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a wumpus, so Oliver is a wumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "quimpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "wumpus", "gerpus", "impus", "lorpus", "terpus", "storpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "fompus", "worpus", "vumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 15], [14, 16], [14, 12], [8, 13], [8, 16], [17, 13], [17, 10], [3, 15], [1, 10], [12, 9], [10, 11], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a yumpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a shumpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every impus is a jompus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every jelpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every jelpus is a rompus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Is Max a jompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Max is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a yumpus, so Max is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a shumpus, so Max is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a impus, so Max is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus."], "answer": "Max is a jompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "jelpus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "impus", "jompus", "boompus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "timpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [8, 10], [1, 9], [3, 10], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every grimpus is a fompus. Every brimpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every gerpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a sterpus. Every gerpus is a gorpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a fompus. Every timpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a brimpus. Is Max a terpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a grimpus, so Max is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a lempus, so Max is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gorpus, so Max is a gorpus."], "answer": "Max is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "timpus", "chorpus", "grimpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "terpus", "brimpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [6, 11], [11, 10], [10, 11], [8, 11], [11, 12], [3, 9], [7, 12], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every boompus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Every bompus is a timpus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a bompus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a boompus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every storpus is a wumpus. Is Oliver a tumpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Oliver is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Oliver is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a tumpus, so Oliver is a tumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "storpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [1, 9], [5, 9], [11, 9], [12, 10], [5, 11], [2, 12], [7, 9], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every jompus is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every gerpus is a impus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Rex is a yumpus. Every brimpus is a jompus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Is Rex a yimpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a brimpus, so Rex is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "gwompus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "yumpus", "gerpus", "lempus", "yerpus", "storpus", "terpus", "chorpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 10], [10, 16], [8, 12], [2, 12], [0, 9], [4, 10], [15, 10], [12, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every chorpus is a wumpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a sterpus. Every grimpus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Every dumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every dumpus is a storpus. Is Fae a sterpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a chorpus, so Fae is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "dumpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "storpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "lorpus", "terpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 14], [2, 12], [2, 14], [1, 11], [3, 14], [6, 9], [15, 13], [1, 9], [5, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Every kerpus is a scrompus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Sally is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every wumpus is a grimpus. Every yerpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every numpus is a timpus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every sterpus is a timpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Is Sally a sterpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Sally is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a grimpus, so Sally is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a scrompus, so Sally is a scrompus."], "answer": "Sally is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "gerpus", "wumpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "numpus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "lorpus", "quimpus", "timpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "sterpus", "gwompus", "bompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 13], [1, 15], [0, 18], [7, 14], [12, 9], [6, 10], [3, 17], [17, 14], [14, 9], [16, 19], [13, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 17}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every grimpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a vumpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a scrompus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every lempus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a tumpus. Is Rex a grimpus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a gorpus, so Rex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "sterpus", "lempus", "terpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "worpus", "scrompus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "fompus", "yimpus", "brimpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [5, 12], [2, 10], [5, 9], [5, 13], [4, 11], [6, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a dumpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a impus. Every felpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every jompus is a vumpus. Every impus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a scrompus. Every chorpus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every yumpus is a impus. Is Wren a yumpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a fompus, so Wren is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lorpus, so Wren is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a yumpus, so Wren is a yumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "chorpus", "fompus", "vumpus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "jompus", "gorpus", "felpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "impus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [2, 10], [5, 10], [3, 11], [5, 11], [1, 9], [11, 9], [6, 9], [8, 10], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rompus is a vumpus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every dumpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every brimpus is a zumpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a brimpus. Is Max a hilpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Max is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a vumpus, so Max is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a dumpus, so Max is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus."], "answer": "Max is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "rompus", "vumpus", "storpus", "dumpus", "zumpus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "brimpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "boompus", "sterpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 14], [14, 9], [8, 11], [9, 10], [2, 12], [5, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a dumpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every felpus is a quimpus. Every dumpus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every quimpus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Is Rex a rompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a felpus, so Rex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a quimpus, so Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jelpus, so Rex is a jelpus."], "answer": "Rex is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "tumpus", "felpus", "quimpus", "lempus", "jelpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "worpus", "gerpus", "rorpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [13, 14], [9, 10], [7, 15], [15, 9], [3, 13], [5, 10], [6, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every worpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a yerpus. Carol is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a gorpus. Every yerpus is a jompus. Carol is a brimpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a yerpus. Is Carol a scrompus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a grimpus, so Carol is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yerpus, so Carol is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a jompus, so Carol is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a scrompus, so Carol is a scrompus."], "answer": "Carol is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "worpus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "jompus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "zhorpus", "gerpus", "gorpus", "rempus", "timpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [1, 13], [3, 11], [0, 14], [2, 10], [13, 11], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every fompus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every jompus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a jelpus. Every numpus is a jompus. Every worpus is a dumpus. Sam is a timpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a dumpus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every fompus is a zumpus. Is Sam a sterpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a vumpus, so Sam is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a dumpus, so Sam is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a jompus, so Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a sterpus, so Sam is a sterpus."], "answer": "Sam is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "fompus", "vumpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "sterpus", "worpus", "numpus", "zumpus", "kerpus", "lorpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "gerpus", "timpus", "brimpus", "boompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 18], [16, 9], [14, 15], [5, 11], [0, 15], [16, 11], [12, 17], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rempus is a gorpus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Every storpus is a jompus. Every jompus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Sam is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every rempus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every zhorpus is a rempus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every rempus is a terpus. Is Sam a jelpus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a yimpus, so Sam is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a storpus, so Sam is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a jompus, so Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a lorpus, so Sam is a lorpus."], "answer": "Sam is a lorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "zhorpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "jompus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "rempus", "fompus", "terpus", "jelpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 9], [3, 9], [1, 9], [0, 10], [7, 9], [8, 11], [7, 11], [11, 10], [4, 11], [10, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rompus is a impus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Jack is a tumpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a impus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Is Jack a timpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yerpus, so Jack is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a brimpus, so Jack is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a worpus, so Jack is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a impus, so Jack is a impus."], "answer": "Jack is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "scrompus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "worpus", "impus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "rompus", "hilpus", "boompus", "felpus", "tumpus", "storpus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 16], [11, 13], [6, 15], [16, 14], [4, 9], [12, 9], [9, 14], [0, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every bompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a bompus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every yumpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a terpus. Every tumpus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a gerpus. Every lempus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Is Bob a gerpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a lempus, so Bob is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gerpus, so Bob is a gerpus."], "answer": "Bob is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "tumpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "yerpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "scrompus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "terpus", "timpus", "boompus", "bompus", "hilpus", "zumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 12], [5, 11], [8, 13], [12, 11], [5, 17], [6, 16], [4, 18], [4, 17], [9, 16], [3, 12], [18, 14], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jompus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Every timpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a terpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Is Rex a gerpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a jompus, so Rex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a hilpus, so Rex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a boompus, so Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus."], "answer": "Rex is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "vumpus", "jompus", "hilpus", "boompus", "gerpus", "worpus", "timpus", "yimpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "felpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 17], [12, 15], [6, 14], [11, 12], [11, 13], [11, 15], [5, 17], [2, 13], [11, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Gabriel is a numpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a impus. Gabriel is a hilpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every jompus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a timpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a jompus. Every numpus is a impus. Every impus is a vumpus. Is Gabriel a wumpus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a tumpus, so Gabriel is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a worpus, so Gabriel is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "gerpus", "tumpus", "zhorpus", "worpus", "timpus", "bompus", "jompus", "scrompus", "wumpus", "numpus", "impus", "grimpus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "vumpus", "quimpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 11], [0, 14], [7, 13], [14, 11], [11, 15], [0, 10], [16, 12], [3, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every storpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every terpus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a terpus. Every chorpus is a gorpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every shumpus is a quimpus. Every felpus is a shumpus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Every quimpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Is Oliver a chorpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "felpus", "shumpus", "quimpus", "yerpus", "chorpus", "rorpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "terpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [2, 11], [5, 9], [8, 9], [6, 11], [7, 9], [9, 11], [1, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every fompus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a worpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every rorpus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a rempus. Every jompus is a storpus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every impus is a jompus. Is Oliver a rempus or a quimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a fompus, so Oliver is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a quimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "impus", "jompus", "hilpus", "fompus", "quimpus", "jelpus", "sterpus", "yerpus", "felpus", "rempus", "worpus", "vumpus", "storpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "kerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 11], [5, 9], [13, 10], [17, 16], [2, 13], [10, 15], [14, 17], [17, 10], [14, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Gabriel is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a impus. Every yerpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a felpus. Every yerpus is a hilpus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a zhorpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every yerpus is a brimpus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every felpus is a impus. Every numpus is a brimpus. Every yerpus is a worpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Is Gabriel a zumpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a yerpus.", "Every yerpus is a zhorpus, so Gabriel is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Gabriel is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a felpus, so Gabriel is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zumpus, so Gabriel is a zumpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a zumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "yerpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "felpus", "zumpus", "numpus", "worpus", "vumpus", "hilpus", "rompus", "shumpus", "impus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [0, 10], [1, 13], [12, 9], [1, 9], [6, 13], [5, 10], [4, 12], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Jack is a bompus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a yerpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Is Jack a brimpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Jack is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a numpus, so Jack is a numpus."], "answer": "Jack is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "wumpus", "zumpus", "grimpus", "zhorpus", "numpus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "chorpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "gerpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "brimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 16], [15, 12], [2, 14], [14, 9], [16, 12], [11, 14], [0, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every rompus is a worpus. Every worpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a wumpus. Every yimpus is a boompus. Every terpus is a shumpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every boompus is a shumpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a terpus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a rorpus. Is Wren a impus or a timpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a shumpus, so Wren is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus."], "answer": "Wren is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "yimpus", "wumpus", "terpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "rorpus", "boompus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "worpus", "impus", "bompus", "jompus", "rompus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 10], [6, 11], [4, 15], [13, 15], [7, 10], [9, 10], [10, 9], [9, 12], [2, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every storpus is a sterpus. Every brimpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every lempus is a zhorpus. Fae is a yimpus. Every fompus is a wumpus. Every zhorpus is a sterpus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Fae is a rompus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every lorpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a shumpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every shumpus is a brimpus. Is Fae a wumpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a dumpus, so Fae is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zhorpus, so Fae is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a wumpus, so Fae is a wumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a wumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "lorpus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "wumpus", "lempus", "storpus", "fompus", "brimpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "rempus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 16], [16, 9], [0, 10], [0, 11], [9, 13], [1, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every numpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a yumpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Oliver is a gerpus. Every rompus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every gorpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every quimpus is a gerpus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every numpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a dumpus. Is Oliver a terpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a kerpus, so Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a numpus, so Oliver is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a grimpus, so Oliver is a grimpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "gorpus", "kerpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "grimpus", "rompus", "quimpus", "fompus", "chorpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "sterpus", "terpus", "impus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "dumpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 16], [0, 16], [7, 15], [8, 13], [6, 16], [11, 17], [7, 16], [15, 16], [4, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every yimpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every scrompus is a brimpus. Every brimpus is a quimpus. Every rempus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a scrompus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every brimpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a boompus. Sally is a zumpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a quimpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Is Sally a yumpus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rempus, so Sally is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a brimpus, so Sally is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a gwompus, so Sally is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a yumpus, so Sally is a yumpus."], "answer": "Sally is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "yimpus", "rempus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "yumpus", "scrompus", "fompus", "grimpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "tumpus", "zumpus", "bompus", "vumpus", "rompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 13], [0, 12], [16, 9], [3, 10], [3, 14], [14, 13], [7, 14], [2, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a scrompus. Every jompus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a vumpus. Every tumpus is a numpus. Every hilpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a rompus. Every chorpus is a yimpus. Wren is a grimpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Is Wren a scrompus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rompus, so Wren is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a zhorpus, so Wren is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a scrompus, so Wren is a scrompus."], "answer": "Wren is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "jompus", "rompus", "vumpus", "zhorpus", "scrompus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "yimpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "storpus", "wumpus", "dumpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 9], [11, 9], [5, 17], [14, 9], [10, 17], [0, 15], [15, 11], [16, 14], [6, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every felpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every felpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Is Sam a gorpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a terpus, so Sam is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a hilpus, so Sam is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jompus, so Sam is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a jelpus, so Sam is a jelpus."], "answer": "Sam is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "felpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "chorpus", "wumpus", "storpus", "gorpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "boompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [4, 11], [4, 14], [14, 10], [3, 13], [1, 14], [9, 14], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a worpus. Every impus is a bompus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every terpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a shumpus. Every sterpus is a jelpus. Every kerpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a boompus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a lorpus. Every impus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a kerpus. Gabriel is a felpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Is Gabriel a boompus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a impus.", "Every impus is a sterpus, so Gabriel is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a jelpus, so Gabriel is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a kerpus, so Gabriel is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "impus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "shumpus", "terpus", "bompus", "tumpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "felpus", "hilpus", "yimpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "worpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 12], [8, 16], [4, 19], [11, 13], [13, 11], [14, 9], [6, 11], [19, 10], [13, 12], [13, 17], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every numpus is a impus. Every numpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a rompus. Every gorpus is a lempus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every lorpus is a fompus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Every gorpus is a lorpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every yumpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every gorpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Sam is a jelpus. Is Sam a impus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a lempus, so Sam is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a rorpus, so Sam is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yumpus, so Sam is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a impus, so Sam is a impus."], "answer": "Sam is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "gorpus", "lempus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "impus", "brimpus", "lorpus", "numpus", "dumpus", "jelpus", "fompus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 12], [4, 9], [7, 11], [3, 10], [8, 10], [4, 11], [0, 10], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every rorpus is a yimpus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a fompus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every grimpus is a shumpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every gwompus is a dumpus. Is Wren a dumpus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a gwompus, so Wren is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "rorpus", "yimpus", "gorpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "fompus", "yumpus", "lorpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "storpus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "impus", "brimpus", "rempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 17], [16, 13], [15, 14], [13, 11], [14, 13], [5, 14], [9, 10], [17, 10], [6, 9], [15, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every rempus is a chorpus. Every bompus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a worpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a shumpus. Every worpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a jelpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a bompus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every sterpus is a dumpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every impus is a yumpus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Is Rex a impus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a sterpus, so Rex is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a shumpus, so Rex is a shumpus."], "answer": "Rex is a shumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rempus", "zumpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "shumpus", "numpus", "bompus", "lempus", "impus", "yumpus", "worpus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "chorpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 9], [14, 10], [9, 10], [2, 11], [9, 12], [4, 16], [14, 13], [11, 10], [1, 15], [1, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every terpus is a tumpus. Every kerpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every tumpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a kerpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every numpus is a zumpus. Is Max a terpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Max is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a chorpus, so Max is a chorpus."], "answer": "Max is a chorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "boompus", "storpus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "hilpus", "numpus", "fompus", "terpus", "tumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [8, 9], [10, 11], [8, 11], [3, 10], [6, 10], [10, 9], [3, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a jompus. Every chorpus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a chorpus. Every jompus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a storpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a fompus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every boompus is a worpus. Every boompus is a yimpus. Every storpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every worpus is a timpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Is Rex a gwompus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a timpus, so Rex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gerpus, so Rex is a gerpus."], "answer": "Rex is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "boompus", "bompus", "chorpus", "timpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "worpus", "yimpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "brimpus", "jompus", "grimpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "lempus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [16, 18], [1, 9], [3, 13], [4, 9], [3, 9], [13, 17], [3, 14], [3, 10], [5, 17], [16, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every gwompus is a yerpus. Every vumpus is a impus. Every numpus is a gwompus. Every dumpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a timpus. Oliver is a gwompus. Every yerpus is a timpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Every impus is a grimpus. Every boompus is a numpus. Every impus is a worpus. Oliver is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a yumpus. Every boompus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a yumpus. Is Oliver a dumpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a kerpus, so Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Oliver is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "vumpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "yumpus", "boompus", "impus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "dumpus", "numpus", "yerpus", "timpus", "lorpus", "zhorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 11], [15, 16], [7, 16], [0, 9], [9, 12], [12, 13], [0, 15], [5, 13], [11, 9], [7, 10], [10, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a yumpus. Every chorpus is a boompus. Every sterpus is a felpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every gorpus is a yumpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every fompus is a boompus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every rompus is a boompus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every yimpus is a fompus. Is Fae a fompus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Fae is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a yumpus, so Fae is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a gwompus, so Fae is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a bompus, so Fae is a bompus."], "answer": "Fae is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "grimpus", "sterpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "bompus", "gorpus", "rompus", "storpus", "felpus", "gerpus", "boompus", "jelpus", "hilpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "fompus", "kerpus", "yimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 13], [15, 11], [18, 16], [18, 9], [7, 16], [3, 18], [7, 11], [16, 11], [2, 9], [6, 16], [12, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every sterpus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a rempus. Every rempus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Max is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a jompus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every jompus is a wumpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every rempus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a yimpus. Is Max a storpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Max is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jompus, so Max is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a wumpus, so Max is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a zumpus, so Max is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a storpus, so Max is a storpus."], "answer": "Max is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "hilpus", "jompus", "wumpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "rempus", "vumpus", "felpus", "yimpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 12], [0, 9], [7, 11], [1, 11], [3, 12], [8, 11], [10, 12], [4, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every jelpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a wumpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a terpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every zhorpus is a wumpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a yumpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every terpus is a vumpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Is Wren a yumpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a terpus, so Wren is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a vumpus, so Wren is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a yimpus, so Wren is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a dumpus, so Wren is a dumpus."], "answer": "Wren is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "zumpus", "terpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "timpus", "jelpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "worpus", "impus", "quimpus", "storpus", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 13], [7, 10], [16, 10], [10, 16], [12, 11], [15, 9], [2, 10], [15, 14], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every storpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every jelpus is a lempus. Every terpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a rempus. Every impus is a storpus. Sally is a rempus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every impus is a wumpus. Every impus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every storpus is a terpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a terpus. Is Sally a gwompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a impus.", "Every impus is a storpus, so Sally is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a terpus, so Sally is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a hilpus, so Sally is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a jelpus, so Sally is a jelpus."], "answer": "Sally is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "impus", "storpus", "terpus", "hilpus", "jelpus", "lorpus", "rompus", "wumpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "lempus", "shumpus", "rempus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [5, 11], [2, 12], [6, 12], [9, 12], [14, 13], [3, 13], [0, 13], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Every storpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a boompus. Every worpus is a yerpus. Every storpus is a fompus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every hilpus is a zhorpus. Every storpus is a yumpus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every lempus is a jompus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Is Oliver a gerpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a lorpus, so Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a gerpus, so Oliver is a gerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "storpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "jompus", "gerpus", "yumpus", "lempus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "vumpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "sterpus", "boompus", "yimpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 14], [2, 12], [9, 11], [7, 15], [2, 9], [16, 11], [10, 14], [15, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every rompus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a zhorpus. Every chorpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a brimpus. Rex is a chorpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a chorpus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every felpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a felpus. Is Rex a zumpus or a yimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a felpus, so Rex is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a yimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "quimpus", "grimpus", "felpus", "rompus", "yimpus", "rorpus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [7, 11], [8, 9], [3, 9], [10, 11], [9, 10], [2, 10], [8, 11], [0, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a yerpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every vumpus is a kerpus. Every yerpus is a vumpus. Every jelpus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every kerpus is a impus. Every zumpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every gorpus is a bompus. Every zumpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a hilpus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every jelpus is a grimpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a bompus. Is Polly a gorpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zumpus, so Polly is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a jompus, so Polly is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Polly is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus."], "answer": "Polly is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "jelpus", "zumpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "dumpus", "shumpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "bompus", "lempus", "impus", "yerpus", "kerpus", "timpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 10], [5, 9], [19, 9], [13, 11], [12, 16], [16, 17], [19, 13], [16, 13], [6, 12], [2, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every terpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a numpus. Every rompus is a hilpus. Every numpus is a impus. Every bompus is a impus. Every hilpus is a rorpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every impus is a terpus. Every boompus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every rorpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a hilpus. Every boompus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a bompus. Is Rex a terpus or a gwompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a impus, so Rex is a impus.", "Every impus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus."], "answer": "Rex is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "boompus", "grimpus", "numpus", "impus", "terpus", "quimpus", "bompus", "gerpus", "scrompus", "rompus", "fompus", "rorpus", "hilpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 11], [10, 12], [10, 13], [13, 12], [5, 16], [12, 15], [15, 14], [11, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a yerpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every bompus is a quimpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a rompus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every bompus is a zumpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a boompus. Every bompus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a impus. Alex is a jelpus. Every bompus is a yerpus. Every yumpus is a rorpus. Every shumpus is a sterpus. Every yumpus is a dumpus. Is Alex a grimpus or a dumpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a fompus, so Alex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a impus, so Alex is a impus.", "Every impus is a zhorpus, so Alex is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "bompus", "fompus", "impus", "zhorpus", "dumpus", "quimpus", "zumpus", "yumpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "rompus", "sterpus", "jelpus", "boompus", "rorpus", "storpus", "yerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 11], [5, 9], [10, 12], [0, 13], [1, 17], [5, 17], [4, 11], [6, 9], [10, 13], [15, 14], [8, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every boompus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a brimpus. Every dumpus is a jompus. Every quimpus is a zumpus. Every quimpus is a boompus. Every yumpus is a grimpus. Every yimpus is a brimpus. Every yimpus is a impus. Every dumpus is a brimpus. Every jompus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a grimpus. Every yumpus is a tumpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every brimpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a boompus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every dumpus is a quimpus. Is Jack a impus or a zumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a yumpus, so Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a tumpus, so Jack is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a boompus, so Jack is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a impus, so Jack is a impus."], "answer": "Jack is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "dumpus", "yumpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "impus", "jompus", "quimpus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "brimpus", "grimpus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 10], [7, 9], [8, 11], [10, 11], [1, 10], [7, 11], [4, 10], [8, 10], [2, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a brimpus. Every tumpus is a gorpus. Every rorpus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every hilpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a gerpus. Polly is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a rompus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Is Polly a rempus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a tumpus, so Polly is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a gorpus, so Polly is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a rompus, so Polly is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a rempus, so Polly is a rempus."], "answer": "Polly is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "hilpus", "tumpus", "gorpus", "rompus", "rempus", "fompus", "brimpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "gerpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 9], [8, 11], [0, 11], [6, 10], [11, 10], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every rempus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a bompus. Every felpus is a lorpus. Every gwompus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every felpus is a kerpus. Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every zhorpus is a jelpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every rempus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a felpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a storpus. Is Rex a grimpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a fompus, so Rex is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a gwompus, so Rex is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a kerpus, so Rex is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a grimpus, so Rex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Rex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "rempus", "fompus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "zumpus", "felpus", "zhorpus", "sterpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "yerpus", "numpus", "storpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 12], [12, 9], [10, 16], [8, 16], [6, 13], [7, 12], [4, 15], [3, 12], [3, 11], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 16}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every rompus is a yerpus. Every zumpus is a chorpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every gerpus is a terpus. Every numpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every dumpus is a chorpus. Rex is a impus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every rompus is a worpus. Every gerpus is a numpus. Is Rex a yerpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Rex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a terpus, so Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus."], "answer": "Rex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "gerpus", "terpus", "zumpus", "chorpus", "rompus", "felpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "yerpus", "impus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [5, 9], [0, 10], [8, 9], [4, 9], [5, 11], [4, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a yimpus. Every scrompus is a fompus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Every yumpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a jelpus. Every zhorpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a scrompus. Every fompus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a gwompus. Is Oliver a fompus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a jelpus, so Oliver is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a zhorpus, so Oliver is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a fompus, so Oliver is a fompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a fompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "yumpus", "impus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "gorpus", "vumpus", "scrompus", "chorpus", "gerpus", "yimpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 9], [6, 12], [7, 11], [5, 10], [8, 9], [4, 12], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every jompus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a jompus. Every worpus is a gerpus. Every kerpus is a grimpus. Every rorpus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a gwompus. Every felpus is a brimpus. Every rompus is a fompus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every lempus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every rompus is a lempus. Every fompus is a jompus. Every jompus is a rorpus. Is Bob a yimpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a fompus, so Bob is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a jompus, so Bob is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a rorpus, so Bob is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a worpus, so Bob is a worpus."], "answer": "Bob is a worpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "rompus", "fompus", "jompus", "rorpus", "worpus", "gwompus", "kerpus", "lempus", "grimpus", "felpus", "tumpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "timpus", "brimpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [7, 16], [7, 9], [5, 17], [14, 13], [3, 16], [10, 16], [4, 9], [7, 10], [11, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every lempus is a zhorpus. Every timpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a numpus. Eva is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a boompus. Every quimpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a scrompus. Every scrompus is a felpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a quimpus. Every lorpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a rompus. Every timpus is a scrompus. Is Eva a kerpus or a scrompus?", "steps": ["Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a rompus, so Eva is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a scrompus, so Eva is a scrompus."], "answer": "Eva is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "lorpus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "timpus", "scrompus", "lempus", "vumpus", "numpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "kerpus", "boompus", "grimpus", "rempus", "quimpus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 16], [4, 16], [9, 13], [5, 17], [0, 9], [16, 17], [16, 11], [3, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every terpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a lempus. Every numpus is a rompus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a storpus. Rex is a dumpus. Every terpus is a worpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every worpus is a rompus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Every yimpus is a dumpus. Every storpus is a grimpus. Every numpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a storpus. Every terpus is a chorpus. Every terpus is a yimpus. Every worpus is a hilpus. Is Rex a rompus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a yimpus, so Rex is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a storpus, so Rex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a numpus, so Rex is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a rompus, so Rex is a rompus."], "answer": "Rex is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "terpus", "yimpus", "storpus", "numpus", "rompus", "lempus", "chorpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "dumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [0, 11], [2, 11], [10, 11], [1, 10], [11, 9], [4, 9], [2, 10], [3, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every numpus is a jompus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every timpus is a sterpus. Every storpus is a vumpus. Every timpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Oliver is a jompus. Every vumpus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a timpus. Every storpus is a gwompus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every vumpus is a rempus. Every rompus is a rempus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every storpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Is Oliver a scrompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a vumpus, so Oliver is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a rempus, so Oliver is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a timpus, so Oliver is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a jelpus, so Oliver is a jelpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "storpus", "vumpus", "rempus", "timpus", "jelpus", "rompus", "gerpus", "gwompus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "scrompus", "numpus", "kerpus", "zumpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 15], [11, 10], [4, 13], [11, 15], [2, 14], [12, 15], [4, 10], [0, 15], [2, 9], [1, 11], [13, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a rempus. Every gorpus is a worpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every impus is a dumpus. Davis is a jompus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every zumpus is a gorpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every worpus is a jompus. Every gorpus is a jompus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every impus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a zhorpus. Every impus is a zhorpus. Every kerpus is a terpus. Every zhorpus is a rorpus. Every dumpus is a hilpus. Is Davis a rorpus or a terpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a impus.", "Every impus is a zumpus, so Davis is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a gorpus, so Davis is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Davis is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a terpus, so Davis is a terpus."], "answer": "Davis is a terpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "impus", "zumpus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "terpus", "dumpus", "vumpus", "kerpus", "zhorpus", "jompus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "rempus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [6, 15], [4, 14], [1, 9], [13, 9], [7, 12], [0, 10], [13, 10], [4, 9], [3, 13], [9, 12], [2, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every brimpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every chorpus is a gerpus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every vumpus is a brimpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every gorpus is a gerpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Gabriel is a felpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every yerpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a timpus. Every gorpus is a gwompus. Gabriel is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a felpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Is Gabriel a gerpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a brimpus, so Gabriel is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a timpus, so Gabriel is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a shumpus, so Gabriel is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a gorpus, so Gabriel is a gorpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "vumpus", "brimpus", "timpus", "shumpus", "gorpus", "chorpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "gerpus", "fompus", "felpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [0, 12], [6, 10], [5, 9], [4, 11], [0, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every fompus is a lorpus. Every brimpus is a boompus. Every rorpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every fompus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a rompus. Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a chorpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a hilpus. Every terpus is a zumpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every terpus is a yerpus. Every fompus is a brimpus. Every fompus is a terpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every lorpus is a boompus. Every yerpus is a chorpus. Is Fae a rompus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a brimpus, so Fae is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a boompus, so Fae is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a hilpus, so Fae is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a yerpus, so Fae is a yerpus."], "answer": "Fae is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "fompus", "brimpus", "boompus", "hilpus", "yerpus", "lorpus", "rorpus", "terpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [6, 10], [5, 11], [8, 10], [7, 9], [4, 9], [3, 11], [4, 10], [7, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a worpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every worpus is a grimpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every hilpus is a sterpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every quimpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a tumpus. Every grimpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a yimpus. Every zhorpus is a bompus. Every gwompus is a shumpus. Every shumpus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a bompus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every hilpus is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a yimpus. Is Oliver a yimpus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a gwompus, so Oliver is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a grimpus, so Oliver is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a sterpus, so Oliver is a sterpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "quimpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "hilpus", "bompus", "yimpus", "zhorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 10], [11, 9], [1, 9], [8, 10], [1, 10], [10, 9], [3, 11], [5, 9], [6, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a impus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every rorpus is a yerpus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every lorpus is a hilpus. Every scrompus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a scrompus. Oliver is a tumpus. Every lorpus is a grimpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a impus. Every rorpus is a numpus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every grimpus is a storpus. Every rorpus is a chorpus. Every chorpus is a numpus. Every grimpus is a chorpus. Is Oliver a yerpus or a chorpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a shumpus, so Oliver is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a scrompus, so Oliver is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a storpus, so Oliver is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a yerpus, so Oliver is a yerpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "lorpus", "shumpus", "scrompus", "storpus", "yerpus", "hilpus", "grimpus", "rorpus", "tumpus", "numpus", "impus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [12, 11], [7, 12], [11, 12], [8, 12], [12, 10], [10, 9], [8, 10], [0, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a shumpus. Every storpus is a zumpus. Every gorpus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a jelpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every yimpus is a felpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a storpus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every bompus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every lorpus is a rorpus. Every brimpus is a bompus. Every felpus is a storpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every rorpus is a storpus. Every jelpus is a felpus. Is Sally a felpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a shumpus, so Sally is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jelpus, so Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus."], "answer": "Sally is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "lorpus", "shumpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "felpus", "brimpus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "timpus", "zumpus", "storpus", "gorpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 10], [3, 13], [5, 11], [10, 11], [4, 10], [12, 10], [1, 13], [13, 11], [6, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gerpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every gerpus is a quimpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every shumpus is a gwompus. Every gerpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every quimpus is a gwompus. Every vumpus is a shumpus. Every chorpus is a jelpus. Every worpus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a tumpus. Every worpus is a lempus. Every gerpus is a chorpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a boompus. Fae is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Is Fae a lempus or a tumpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a vumpus, so Fae is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a shumpus, so Fae is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a jelpus, so Fae is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a tumpus, so Fae is a tumpus."], "answer": "Fae is a tumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gerpus", "vumpus", "shumpus", "jelpus", "tumpus", "worpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "quimpus", "gwompus", "lempus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [0, 9], [8, 11], [6, 11], [3, 10], [1, 11], [1, 9], [10, 9], [2, 11], [9, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every numpus is a timpus. Every vumpus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a zumpus. Every numpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a lorpus. Every timpus is a wumpus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a vumpus. Every hilpus is a impus. Every lorpus is a brimpus. Every impus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a storpus. Rex is a storpus. Every lorpus is a wumpus. Every hilpus is a numpus. Is Rex a timpus or a storpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a zumpus, so Rex is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a vumpus, so Rex is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a lempus, so Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a timpus, so Rex is a timpus."], "answer": "Rex is a timpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "hilpus", "zumpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "timpus", "lorpus", "impus", "numpus", "brimpus", "wumpus", "storpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 11], [6, 10], [0, 11], [3, 11], [6, 9], [8, 11], [4, 10], [5, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every impus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every lempus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a boompus. Every hilpus is a yumpus. Carol is a yimpus. Every quimpus is a storpus. Every vumpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a rorpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every quimpus is a rempus. Every rorpus is a yumpus. Is Carol a boompus or a lorpus?", "steps": ["Carol is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rempus, so Carol is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a lempus, so Carol is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a jelpus, so Carol is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a boompus, so Carol is a boompus."], "answer": "Carol is a boompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Carol", "quimpus", "rempus", "lempus", "jelpus", "boompus", "storpus", "impus", "hilpus", "yumpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "yimpus", "lorpus", "rorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [14, 13], [11, 10], [3, 9], [9, 12], [8, 9], [0, 12], [3, 14], [4, 10], [14, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a impus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every hilpus is a quimpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Oliver is a numpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Every rorpus is a quimpus. Every kerpus is a jompus. Every brimpus is a yerpus. Every kerpus is a numpus. Every brimpus is a vumpus. Every impus is a vumpus. Every kerpus is a brimpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every kerpus is a hilpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every numpus is a yumpus. Every kerpus is a gorpus. Is Oliver a shumpus or a impus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a brimpus, so Oliver is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a rorpus, so Oliver is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a impus, so Oliver is a impus."], "answer": "Oliver is a impus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "kerpus", "brimpus", "rorpus", "quimpus", "impus", "gorpus", "hilpus", "jompus", "vumpus", "fompus", "yerpus", "yumpus", "shumpus", "numpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 10], [0, 14], [5, 9], [14, 12], [7, 11], [2, 9], [2, 11], [1, 14], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every jompus is a rompus. Every yimpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a jelpus. Every gerpus is a felpus. Every grimpus is a quimpus. Every yimpus is a kerpus. Every wumpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a grimpus. Every rompus is a kerpus. Every shumpus is a yimpus. Every rempus is a grimpus. Every kerpus is a felpus. Every yimpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a wumpus. Bob is a terpus. Every shumpus is a gerpus. Is Bob a felpus or a grimpus?", "steps": ["Bob is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a wumpus, so Bob is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a rompus, so Bob is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a kerpus, so Bob is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a felpus, so Bob is a felpus."], "answer": "Bob is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "shumpus", "wumpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "felpus", "jompus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "jelpus", "tumpus", "rempus", "grimpus", "terpus", "quimpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 9], [12, 14], [6, 9], [0, 13], [7, 10], [7, 13], [5, 12], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a gerpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every brimpus is a chorpus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every rempus is a gwompus. Every tumpus is a jelpus. Every boompus is a yerpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every jelpus is a scrompus. Every gorpus is a jelpus. Every dumpus is a impus. Every rempus is a tumpus. Every dumpus is a boompus. Every vumpus is a yerpus. Every gerpus is a yerpus. Every tumpus is a rorpus. Is Wren a scrompus or a brimpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a timpus, so Wren is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gorpus, so Wren is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a scrompus, so Wren is a scrompus."], "answer": "Wren is a scrompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "rempus", "timpus", "gorpus", "jelpus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "tumpus", "gerpus", "rompus", "brimpus", "impus", "worpus", "dumpus", "yerpus", "rorpus", "lorpus", "chorpus", "boompus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [13, 18], [4, 18], [11, 17], [8, 14], [10, 17], [18, 14], [3, 18], [13, 11], [7, 15], [19, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a rempus. Every felpus is a yimpus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every terpus is a timpus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a rompus. Every felpus is a vumpus. Every yimpus is a sterpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every felpus is a boompus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every lempus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a terpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every chorpus is a zumpus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every boompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a chorpus. Is Eva a rompus or a rempus?", "steps": ["Eva is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a terpus, so Eva is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a chorpus, so Eva is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a rempus, so Eva is a rempus."], "answer": "Eva is a rempus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "felpus", "terpus", "timpus", "chorpus", "rempus", "boompus", "vumpus", "lempus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "rompus", "zumpus", "shumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [10, 12], [11, 9], [9, 14], [8, 12], [10, 9], [5, 13], [4, 13], [1, 11], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every tumpus is a scrompus. Wren is a gerpus. Every bompus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a jelpus. Every bompus is a gerpus. Every storpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a grimpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every zhorpus is a terpus. Every shumpus is a dumpus. Every tumpus is a wumpus. Every dumpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a zhorpus. Every tumpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a bompus. Every zhorpus is a storpus. Is Wren a scrompus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Wren is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a wumpus, so Wren is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a storpus, so Wren is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a bompus, so Wren is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a jelpus, so Wren is a jelpus."], "answer": "Wren is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Wren", "tumpus", "wumpus", "storpus", "bompus", "jelpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "shumpus", "dumpus", "numpus", "scrompus", "gerpus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 11], [9, 11], [13, 11], [6, 13], [1, 11], [8, 9], [2, 11], [0, 12], [4, 12], [7, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every timpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a scrompus. Every wumpus is a quimpus. Every gerpus is a tumpus. Every gwompus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every zumpus is a timpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every vumpus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a zumpus. Every gerpus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a timpus. Every gwompus is a gerpus. Every tumpus is a vumpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every zumpus is a scrompus. Every gwompus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a quimpus. Is Eva a scrompus or a vumpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a zumpus, so Eva is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a timpus, so Eva is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a tumpus, so Eva is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a vumpus, so Eva is a vumpus."], "answer": "Eva is a vumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "gwompus", "zumpus", "timpus", "tumpus", "vumpus", "lempus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "quimpus", "terpus", "scrompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 9], [10, 11], [7, 11], [1, 11], [2, 11], [2, 9], [8, 9], [4, 9], [5, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a zhorpus. Every zhorpus is a rompus. Every brimpus is a yimpus. Every felpus is a jompus. Every yimpus is a rempus. Bob is a storpus. Every brimpus is a rorpus. Every felpus is a worpus. Every zumpus is a hilpus. Every quimpus is a impus. Every rempus is a zumpus. Every brimpus is a yumpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every rorpus is a rempus. Every brimpus is a felpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Is Bob a hilpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Bob is a brimpus.", "Every brimpus is a yimpus, so Bob is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a rempus, so Bob is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a zumpus, so Bob is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a hilpus, so Bob is a hilpus."], "answer": "Bob is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Bob", "brimpus", "yimpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "yumpus", "felpus", "worpus", "storpus", "quimpus", "zhorpus", "impus", "scrompus", "gwompus", "bompus", "jompus", "gorpus", "rompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [4, 12], [15, 12], [8, 9], [0, 10], [11, 13], [8, 17], [12, 19]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 19}, {"question": "Every zumpus is a yerpus. Every scrompus is a zhorpus. Every yimpus is a zumpus. Every zhorpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every wumpus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every scrompus is a lempus. Every quimpus is a vumpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every zumpus is a rompus. Every scrompus is a jompus. Every zhorpus is a numpus. Every scrompus is a impus. Every fompus is a storpus. Every storpus is a impus. Every lempus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Is Oliver a quimpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a jompus, so Oliver is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a yimpus, so Oliver is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a zumpus, so Oliver is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a rompus, so Oliver is a rompus."], "answer": "Oliver is a rompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "scrompus", "jompus", "yimpus", "zumpus", "rompus", "zhorpus", "shumpus", "lempus", "storpus", "numpus", "fompus", "grimpus", "yerpus", "impus", "quimpus", "rempus", "rorpus", "wumpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 10], [13, 15], [4, 13], [12, 18], [9, 14], [11, 9], [1, 14], [15, 19], [18, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 15}, {"question": "Every storpus is a dumpus. Every numpus is a gorpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every zhorpus is a grimpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every yerpus is a rompus. Every kerpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a timpus. Every grimpus is a zumpus. Every yumpus is a storpus. Every yumpus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a gorpus. Every zumpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every yumpus is a lempus. Every grimpus is a dumpus. Is Jack a gorpus or a rompus?", "steps": ["Jack is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a zhorpus, so Jack is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a grimpus, so Jack is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a dumpus, so Jack is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus."], "answer": "Jack is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "yumpus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "dumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "storpus", "numpus", "rompus", "yerpus", "rempus", "zumpus", "shumpus", "timpus", "kerpus", "sterpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 16], [11, 15], [3, 14], [3, 12], [10, 9], [3, 15], [14, 13], [15, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every timpus is a rorpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every rorpus is a worpus. Every scrompus is a sterpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a rorpus. Every gorpus is a felpus. Every gorpus is a timpus. Every terpus is a gwompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a worpus. Every dumpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every gorpus is a dumpus. Every timpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a scrompus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Fae is a gerpus. Every worpus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a hilpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Is Fae a gwompus or a sterpus?", "steps": ["Fae is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a felpus, so Fae is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a rorpus, so Fae is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a worpus, so Fae is a worpus.", "Every worpus is a sterpus, so Fae is a sterpus."], "answer": "Fae is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Fae", "gorpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "sterpus", "timpus", "dumpus", "scrompus", "bompus", "terpus", "hilpus", "brimpus", "gwompus", "vumpus", "gerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 15], [2, 11], [15, 11], [4, 13], [7, 10], [10, 13], [13, 11], [0, 15], [6, 9], [8, 13], [12, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every lorpus is a zumpus. Every boompus is a sterpus. Every felpus is a zumpus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a gwompus. Every kerpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every zumpus is a yimpus. Every zumpus is a rorpus. Every sterpus is a worpus. Every yimpus is a gerpus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every yimpus is a worpus. Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every gerpus is a kerpus. Every boompus is a felpus. Every boompus is a lorpus. Sally is a kerpus. Is Sally a worpus or a gerpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a felpus, so Sally is a felpus.", "Every felpus is a zumpus, so Sally is a zumpus.", "Every zumpus is a yimpus, so Sally is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a gerpus, so Sally is a gerpus."], "answer": "Sally is a gerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "boompus", "felpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "gerpus", "lorpus", "gwompus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "rorpus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 10], [4, 11], [7, 9], [8, 9], [0, 9], [5, 9], [3, 10], [8, 11]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every storpus is a numpus. Every yimpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a yimpus. Every bompus is a storpus. Every hilpus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a impus. Every storpus is a kerpus. Every quimpus is a numpus. Every gorpus is a hilpus. Every yimpus is a chorpus. Every yimpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a yumpus. Every hilpus is a chorpus. Every yumpus is a yimpus. Every tumpus is a quimpus. Every impus is a gorpus. Every bompus is a tumpus. Every storpus is a gorpus. Is Stella a kerpus or a numpus?", "steps": ["Stella is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a yumpus, so Stella is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a yimpus, so Stella is a yimpus.", "Every yimpus is a quimpus, so Stella is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a numpus, so Stella is a numpus."], "answer": "Stella is a numpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "bompus", "yumpus", "yimpus", "quimpus", "numpus", "impus", "tumpus", "storpus", "kerpus", "chorpus", "gorpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 11], [4, 12], [6, 11], [3, 10], [12, 10], [12, 11], [8, 9], [3, 12], [11, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every scrompus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a gerpus. Every dumpus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a fompus. Every timpus is a shumpus. Every timpus is a jelpus. Every jompus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a gorpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a grimpus. Every gerpus is a storpus. Every timpus is a jompus. Every rorpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a gorpus. Every scrompus is a jelpus. Every timpus is a rorpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Is Alex a dumpus or a jelpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus.", "Every grimpus is a gerpus, so Alex is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus.", "Every storpus is a dumpus, so Alex is a dumpus."], "answer": "Alex is a dumpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "timpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "storpus", "dumpus", "jompus", "shumpus", "rorpus", "felpus", "fompus", "jelpus", "yimpus", "scrompus", "gorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 14], [13, 11], [13, 10], [6, 10], [7, 14], [10, 11], [1, 11], [5, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every yumpus is a chorpus. Stella is a numpus. Every fompus is a chorpus. Every sterpus is a lempus. Every yumpus is a impus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a jelpus. Every gwompus is a sterpus. Every rompus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a rompus. Every hilpus is a lempus. Every rompus is a impus. Every jelpus is a bompus. Every jompus is a boompus. Every jompus is a impus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every vumpus is a chorpus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every rompus is a chorpus. Every gwompus is a hilpus. Every lorpus is a yumpus. Is Stella a lorpus or a bompus?", "steps": ["Stella is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a sterpus, so Stella is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a lempus, so Stella is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a vumpus, so Stella is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a bompus, so Stella is a bompus."], "answer": "Stella is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Stella", "gwompus", "sterpus", "lempus", "vumpus", "bompus", "hilpus", "rompus", "jelpus", "boompus", "lorpus", "yumpus", "numpus", "fompus", "impus", "chorpus", "jompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [11, 15], [14, 15], [13, 15], [10, 11], [16, 14], [0, 12], [11, 14], [7, 15], [7, 14], [16, 9], [4, 15]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a tumpus. Every terpus is a rempus. Every impus is a brimpus. Every yumpus is a numpus. Every impus is a chorpus. Every hilpus is a wumpus. Every brimpus is a hilpus. Every impus is a felpus. Every boompus is a lempus. Every brimpus is a numpus. Every numpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a quimpus. Every chorpus is a yumpus. Every quimpus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every felpus is a yumpus. Every impus is a yerpus. Every yerpus is a quimpus. Every yumpus is a terpus. Is Oliver a wumpus or a hilpus?", "steps": ["Oliver is a impus.", "Every impus is a chorpus, so Oliver is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a yumpus, so Oliver is a yumpus.", "Every yumpus is a quimpus, so Oliver is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a hilpus, so Oliver is a hilpus."], "answer": "Oliver is a hilpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Oliver", "impus", "chorpus", "yumpus", "quimpus", "hilpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "brimpus", "rempus", "fompus", "tumpus", "wumpus", "numpus", "lempus", "boompus", "terpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 13], [5, 12], [13, 12], [8, 13], [6, 14], [12, 11], [3, 16], [15, 14], [16, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a sterpus. Every gorpus is a kerpus. Every jelpus is a gorpus. Sally is a sterpus. Every wumpus is a vumpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every gorpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a bompus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a bompus. Every sterpus is a shumpus. Every kerpus is a lorpus. Every worpus is a zhorpus. Every vumpus is a lorpus. Every rompus is a sterpus. Every jelpus is a wumpus. Is Sally a lorpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Sally is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a wumpus, so Sally is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a vumpus, so Sally is a vumpus.", "Every vumpus is a bompus, so Sally is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zhorpus, so Sally is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Sally is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sally", "jelpus", "wumpus", "vumpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "gorpus", "fompus", "worpus", "sterpus", "rompus", "kerpus", "dumpus", "lorpus", "shumpus", "chorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [15, 9], [11, 13], [9, 14], [0, 9], [6, 11], [3, 13], [10, 9], [1, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}, {"question": "Every rempus is a felpus. Every rempus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a bompus. Every tumpus is a chorpus. Every scrompus is a chorpus. Every rempus is a kerpus. Every vumpus is a felpus. Every numpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a scrompus. Every worpus is a lorpus. Every bompus is a felpus. Every rempus is a worpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a bompus. Every timpus is a tumpus. Every rempus is a numpus. Every chorpus is a worpus. Every kerpus is a worpus. Is Sam a bompus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Sam is a rempus.", "Every rempus is a numpus, so Sam is a numpus.", "Every numpus is a tumpus, so Sam is a tumpus.", "Every tumpus is a chorpus, so Sam is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a bompus, so Sam is a bompus."], "answer": "Sam is a bompus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Sam", "rempus", "numpus", "tumpus", "chorpus", "bompus", "timpus", "scrompus", "kerpus", "yimpus", "felpus", "vumpus", "worpus", "lorpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 13], [5, 11], [5, 10], [1, 10], [1, 12], [13, 12], [12, 13], [8, 12], [11, 10], [4, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a terpus. Every rorpus is a sterpus. Every kerpus is a quimpus. Every sterpus is a gerpus. Every boompus is a impus. Every gorpus is a sterpus. Every vumpus is a rorpus. Every lempus is a hilpus. Every felpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every quimpus is a rorpus. Every boompus is a quimpus. Every gwompus is a vumpus. Every gwompus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a kerpus. Every gerpus is a hilpus. Is Gabriel a sterpus or a shumpus?", "steps": ["Gabriel is a gwompus.", "Every gwompus is a boompus, so Gabriel is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a quimpus, so Gabriel is a quimpus.", "Every quimpus is a rorpus, so Gabriel is a rorpus.", "Every rorpus is a sterpus, so Gabriel is a sterpus."], "answer": "Gabriel is a sterpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Gabriel", "gwompus", "boompus", "quimpus", "rorpus", "sterpus", "kerpus", "vumpus", "gorpus", "lempus", "terpus", "impus", "rempus", "gerpus", "shumpus", "felpus", "yerpus", "hilpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [9, 17], [5, 10], [2, 11], [13, 17], [15, 9], [5, 13]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 14}, {"question": "Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every gerpus is a rorpus. Every gerpus is a dumpus. Every grimpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a gerpus. Every bompus is a vumpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every zhorpus is a dumpus. Every bompus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a fompus. Every chorpus is a lorpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every rorpus is a vumpus. Every gerpus is a bompus. Every lorpus is a bompus. Is Rex a sterpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Rex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a chorpus, so Rex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lorpus, so Rex is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a bompus, so Rex is a bompus.", "Every bompus is a zhorpus, so Rex is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Rex is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Rex", "lempus", "chorpus", "lorpus", "bompus", "zhorpus", "grimpus", "gerpus", "fompus", "rorpus", "dumpus", "sterpus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 12], [1, 11], [4, 12], [5, 10], [9, 12], [6, 11], [7, 9], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every gorpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a timpus. Every timpus is a worpus. Every tumpus is a timpus. Every zumpus is a zhorpus. Every jelpus is a zumpus. Every jelpus is a fompus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Every jelpus is a tumpus. Every zumpus is a gwompus. Every timpus is a gorpus. Every worpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a terpus. Every jelpus is a boompus. Every boompus is a gorpus. Every boompus is a terpus. Is Tom a zhorpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Tom is a jelpus.", "Every jelpus is a fompus, so Tom is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a timpus, so Tom is a timpus.", "Every timpus is a gorpus, so Tom is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a zhorpus, so Tom is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Tom is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Tom", "jelpus", "fompus", "timpus", "gorpus", "zhorpus", "tumpus", "boompus", "zumpus", "terpus", "worpus", "wumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [3, 10], [8, 12], [12, 11], [11, 9], [10, 9], [1, 12], [7, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every chorpus is a lempus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every dumpus is a zhorpus. Every lempus is a lorpus. Every chorpus is a fompus. Every vumpus is a grimpus. Every vumpus is a zhorpus. Polly is a sterpus. Every storpus is a dumpus. Every fompus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a kerpus. Every lorpus is a dumpus. Every lorpus is a kerpus. Every kerpus is a sterpus. Every lempus is a sterpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a storpus. Every lempus is a grimpus. Every chorpus is a vumpus. Every fompus is a lorpus. Is Polly a grimpus or a zhorpus?", "steps": ["Polly is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Polly is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a lorpus, so Polly is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a dumpus, so Polly is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a zhorpus, so Polly is a zhorpus."], "answer": "Polly is a zhorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Polly", "chorpus", "lempus", "lorpus", "dumpus", "zhorpus", "fompus", "storpus", "vumpus", "grimpus", "sterpus", "kerpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [2, 10], [8, 9], [2, 9], [3, 11], [1, 9], [9, 11], [4, 11], [6, 9], [4, 9], [11, 10], [0, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every gwompus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a fompus. Every zhorpus is a timpus. Every wumpus is a yimpus. Every dumpus is a grimpus. Every grimpus is a lorpus. Every kerpus is a zhorpus. Every fompus is a zhorpus. Every dumpus is a kerpus. Every gwompus is a gorpus. Every lorpus is a gorpus. Every zhorpus is a lorpus. Every dumpus is a gwompus. Every fompus is a timpus. Eva is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every lorpus is a yimpus. Every gorpus is a yimpus. Eva is a yimpus. Every gwompus is a wumpus. Is Eva a yimpus or a gorpus?", "steps": ["Eva is a dumpus.", "Every dumpus is a fompus, so Eva is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a zhorpus, so Eva is a zhorpus.", "Every zhorpus is a lorpus, so Eva is a lorpus.", "Every lorpus is a gorpus, so Eva is a gorpus."], "answer": "Eva is a gorpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Eva", "dumpus", "fompus", "zhorpus", "lorpus", "gorpus", "kerpus", "grimpus", "gwompus", "yimpus", "wumpus", "timpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [8, 9], [3, 11], [0, 9], [0, 10], [4, 9], [5, 9], [8, 10], [2, 11], [10, 9], [7, 10]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 9}, {"question": "Every sterpus is a timpus. Every lorpus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a fompus. Every fompus is a vumpus. Every rempus is a hilpus. Every fompus is a scrompus. Every lempus is a rempus. Every scrompus is a yerpus. Every timpus is a lempus. Every rempus is a lempus. Every bompus is a scrompus. Every lorpus is a rempus. Every sterpus is a kerpus. Every timpus is a hilpus. Every bompus is a hilpus. Every yerpus is a lempus. Every kerpus is a fompus. Every sterpus is a lorpus. Every sterpus is a bompus. Every gorpus is a rempus. Is Max a gorpus or a yerpus?", "steps": ["Max is a sterpus.", "Every sterpus is a kerpus, so Max is a kerpus.", "Every kerpus is a fompus, so Max is a fompus.", "Every fompus is a scrompus, so Max is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a yerpus, so Max is a yerpus."], "answer": "Max is a yerpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Max", "sterpus", "kerpus", "fompus", "scrompus", "yerpus", "timpus", "bompus", "lorpus", "hilpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "rempus", "vumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 9], [11, 12], [3, 13], [10, 12], [7, 9], [12, 10], [5, 10], [6, 9], [6, 10], [8, 12]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every wumpus is a felpus. Every wumpus is a gwompus. Every zumpus is a grimpus. Every wumpus is a zumpus. Every grimpus is a jelpus. Every felpus is a jelpus. Every fompus is a worpus. Every jelpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a jelpus. Every zumpus is a gerpus. Every hilpus is a jelpus. Every chorpus is a lempus. Every gwompus is a lempus. Every wumpus is a chorpus. Every lempus is a jelpus. Every lempus is a gorpus. Every felpus is a gorpus. Every wumpus is a fompus. Every gorpus is a grimpus. Every gorpus is a rorpus. Is Alex a grimpus or a worpus?", "steps": ["Alex is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a chorpus, so Alex is a chorpus.", "Every chorpus is a lempus, so Alex is a lempus.", "Every lempus is a gorpus, so Alex is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a grimpus, so Alex is a grimpus."], "answer": "Alex is a grimpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "wumpus", "chorpus", "lempus", "gorpus", "grimpus", "gwompus", "felpus", "zumpus", "fompus", "hilpus", "rorpus", "worpus", "kerpus", "storpus", "yerpus", "gerpus", "vumpus", "jelpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [10, 18], [11, 18], [5, 18], [3, 18], [4, 11], [18, 15], [9, 12], [8, 16], [1, 9], [7, 18]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 12}, {"question": "Every storpus is a fompus. Every storpus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a yimpus. Every jompus is a shumpus. Every boompus is a rompus. Every tumpus is a fompus. Every zumpus is a shumpus. Every rompus is a storpus. Every fompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a scrompus. Every zumpus is a boompus. Every scrompus is a boompus. Every gwompus is a storpus. Every scrompus is a shumpus. Every jompus is a zumpus. Every storpus is a lorpus. Every jompus is a gwompus. Every rompus is a lorpus. Every yimpus is a rompus. Every zumpus is a tumpus. Is Alex a storpus or a fompus?", "steps": ["Alex is a jompus.", "Every jompus is a scrompus, so Alex is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a boompus, so Alex is a boompus.", "Every boompus is a rompus, so Alex is a rompus.", "Every rompus is a storpus, so Alex is a storpus."], "answer": "Alex is a storpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Alex", "jompus", "scrompus", "boompus", "rompus", "storpus", "zumpus", "yimpus", "gwompus", "shumpus", "fompus", "lorpus", "tumpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [6, 12], [1, 9], [4, 11], [6, 9], [2, 9], [5, 10], [12, 10], [5, 11], [5, 9], [10, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 10}, {"question": "Every shumpus is a wumpus. Every grimpus is a jompus. Every shumpus is a scrompus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every timpus is a felpus. Every fompus is a jelpus. Every shumpus is a grimpus. Every shumpus is a timpus. Every shumpus is a fompus. Every grimpus is a wumpus. Every terpus is a felpus. Every worpus is a vumpus. Every gorpus is a terpus. Jack is a jelpus. Every lempus is a vumpus. Every rorpus is a gorpus. Every grimpus is a terpus. Every scrompus is a gorpus. Every timpus is a vumpus. Is Jack a felpus or a wumpus?", "steps": ["Jack is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a scrompus, so Jack is a scrompus.", "Every scrompus is a gorpus, so Jack is a gorpus.", "Every gorpus is a terpus, so Jack is a terpus.", "Every terpus is a felpus, so Jack is a felpus."], "answer": "Jack is a felpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Jack", "shumpus", "scrompus", "gorpus", "terpus", "felpus", "rorpus", "grimpus", "timpus", "jelpus", "vumpus", "wumpus", "jompus", "lempus", "fompus", "worpus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [1, 11], [7, 12], [13, 10], [8, 10], [14, 9], [15, 10], [7, 11], [0, 9], [1, 14]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 11}, {"question": "Every worpus is a scrompus. Every hilpus is a gerpus. Every scrompus is a gwompus. Every shumpus is a rorpus. Every rompus is a yumpus. Every impus is a gerpus. Every shumpus is a hilpus. Every worpus is a gwompus. Every wumpus is a jelpus. Every hilpus is a yerpus. Every rorpus is a wumpus. Every shumpus is a impus. Every gerpus is a wumpus. Every yumpus is a rompus. Every shumpus is a storpus. Every gerpus is a worpus. Every wumpus is a yumpus. Every storpus is a jelpus. Every storpus is a worpus. Every shumpus is a rompus. Is Davis a jelpus or a yumpus?", "steps": ["Davis is a shumpus.", "Every shumpus is a hilpus, so Davis is a hilpus.", "Every hilpus is a gerpus, so Davis is a gerpus.", "Every gerpus is a wumpus, so Davis is a wumpus.", "Every wumpus is a jelpus, so Davis is a jelpus."], "answer": "Davis is a jelpus.", "idx_to_symbol": ["Davis", "shumpus", "hilpus", "gerpus", "wumpus", "jelpus", "impus", "rorpus", "storpus", "worpus", "yerpus", "rompus", "scrompus", "yumpus", "gwompus"], "edges": [[1, 2], [2, 3], [3, 4], [4, 5], [1, 6], [6, 3], [1, 7], [7, 4], [1, 8], [8, 5], [12, 14], [4, 13], [1, 11], [2, 10], [9, 14], [11, 13], [9, 12], [13, 11], [8, 9], [3, 9]], "root": 0, "target": 5, "neg_target": 13}]